Move.
They thought this was
gonna be a street fight.
What are you waiting for, Toretto?
No!
Letty, stop!
What are you gonna do?
I don't know why you're doing this,
but I know one thing.
You love me.
And you are not gonna shoot me.
You should've given him the case,
'cause I won't chase you.
Okay.
I will just take it from a dead girl.
You willing to die for it?
Let's go, then.
Anything?
They're gone.
And DOD confirmed it was a nuclear football.
He's got an EMP and nuclear launch codes.
I don't know what it is,
but they're building towards something.
Deckard?
He didn't make it.
I'm disappointed in you, Dom.
When push came to shove, you were gonna
let Letty just walk away with the codes.
You got the codes!
Rhodes got the codes.
You made the choice to let her go.
And now I have to make one of my own.
They are adorable little things, aren't they?
God, I hope I don't hurt him.
Look, psychotic, I did exactly
what you asked me to do.
Don't do this.
This is your doing.
My doing?
Da-dada.
Dada.
Da-da.
Please don't hurt him, I'm begging you.
I don't want you to beg.
I want you to learn.
Learn what?
I understand why you did
what you did. I really do.
Da-da.
But it was the wrong choice.
This is the consequence of that.
No!
No! No!
Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
Save your son!
No!
Can you pull up the footage
from the guy in the alley?
Traffic cams.
I got you.
I knew it.
I recognize that guy.
That's Connor Rhodes.
I met him when I was working
with Shaw's brother.
He wanted us to get
the Nightshade device for him.
Connor Rhodes.
He's also linked to somebody
I'd quite like to forget.
It's Mose Jakande.
Warlord who tried to get God's Eye.
Which means that's twice that Dom
has messed up Cipher's business.
Everything you're feeling right now,
this rage, a sense of loss, it's not real.
It's a survival instinct
wired deep into our brains
to ensure continuation of the species.
When early man would visit a watering hole,
if they didn't watch their child,
and it got snatched by a crocodile,
our brains would create
a painful but instructional memory,
so it would never happen again.
This idea of "family"
that is so core with you,
that rules your world,
it's a biological lie.
You don't have to accept it.
I don't.
Did you really think you
could destroy two of my teams
without any repercussions?
I wouldn't have even looked
your way if you hadn't done that.
You didn't even know you had a kid.
You can thank me for that and start
doing the job I'm asking you to do.
Help you start a war.
Is that what you think I want?
That's so limited.
I didn't take that football to start a war
any more than I took
your son to start a family.
Taking your son got me the codes.
The codes will get me the nukes
and the nukes will get me what I want
today, tomorrow, and every day after that.
And what's that?
Accountability.
The second I fire off one of those nukes,
I put the superpowers
of this world on notice that,
when they cross the line,
I'm gonna be there to hold them responsible.
Because the truth is, Dom,
to the world out there,
I am the crocodile at the watering hole.
We've got one last job to do.
Cipher.
If I were you, I'd kiss my son.
Because whether
you value it or not, all of this,
your plane, your security, and you,
are still on this earth because of him.
The problem we've had with tracking
Cipher is there's nothing to trace.
But now, we have Rhodes' information.
And we're getting snapshots of his data
before it's scrubbed off the net.
That looks like somebody's bank account,
so why don't we just go ahead...
It's a longitude.
Given the fact that Dom
hit a Russian motorcade,
it's safe to say it's Russia.
Go ahead and bring up the map.
Good. Let's start here
and run the possibilities.
Yalta, Poltava...
It's like they just threw letters together.
Kronyurt.
It's "Vladovin."
- What are you doing here?
- What?
Told you I was gonna check in on you from
time to time to see how you were doin'.
By the way, not so hot.
But there's nothing in Vladovin.
It's just ice.
That's funny.
Could've sworn there was
a secret Russian naval base
where they retrofitted Cold War submarines.
Well, technically, it's not Russian anymore.
The base was taken over
by a terror group of military
separatists about a month ago,
and the Russians haven't taken it back yet,
so there is a little window
of opportunity here.
Russian submarines. Nuclear football.
It sounds like everything we do,
our legs gonna be blown off.
It sounds like you still
number 11 on the list.
It sounds like you've changed
since your little punk-ass
facial hairs done came in.
Guys, guys.
Hey, we gotta call this in.
All the way up the chain.
That's good thinking, champ,
except unfortunately,
the Russian Minister of Defense
got himself involved in a little
incident on US territory,
and the two governments aren't talking
to each other for a while.
By the time they do, it'll be too late.
So, any other suggestions?
Yeah. I got one.
How about we just stop them ourselves?
You're talking about a Russian military base.
Separatist.
Whatever. It's suicide.
It's stopping World War III.
What's it gonna be, rook?
You gonna close your eyes on this one, too?
Pray that the apocalypse doesn't come
knocking on your mama's front door?
Or, are you gonna saddle up, be a man,
and save the entire goddamn world?
You know, I think I figured it out.
What's that?
- Rule number three.
- Which is?
There are no rules.
What'd I tell you, Luke?
I knew he'd get it in three.
Aerial transport leaves in an hour.
Take whatever vehicle you want.
All bets are off.
- All bets are off?
- Bets are off?
Do svidanya!
Letty, I don't like telling you this one bit.
But the game's changed.
Before, we were just trying to catch Dom,
but now, after all this,
I want you to know, if I have to,
I'm gonna put him down.
Then you might have to take us both down.
I'm freezing, man.
This ain't for me.
I come from a different
kind of lifestyle, brah.
Ladies know me.
They know where I'm at with it.
I tried to take a piss,
I didn't even recognize myself.
Man, that's entirely too much information.
I'm just sayin'.
Well, one thing's for sure.
Dom's gotta be either working
with them or making a trade,
because no one would be this insane
to hit this place without a damn army.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Speak of the devil.
All right, Dom, you're one step
closer to that family reunion.
400 meters to base.
Prep the EMP. Let's take these defenses down.
We have a possible threat approaching.
Raise the barricade.
We've lost power, defensive positions now.
Gates are open. Let's get this party started.
- EMP is recharging.
- How long?
Sixty seconds.
All right, Dom, you have
one pulse left in that EMP.
That sub is heavily insulated.
You're gonna need to be right
underneath it for this thing to work.
Come on.
Engaging target. He's beneath the sub.
Mayday! Mayday! I've lost all power.
I'm going down.
Yes!
Two birds with one stone.
We've got control of the sub.
Dom, we are good.
Head over to the rendezvous.
Okay, Matty, let's take this baby for a spin.
Damn!
I think Cipher just rebooted that
sub to slave its command system.
What the hell is he talking about?
In layman's terms,
she just carjacked a submarine.
We can't let it get away.
There's the control room.
If you can get me into that wheelhouse,
I can tap the network
and counter-hack Cipher.
Keep it from lowering into the water.
No, what we need to do is get me on that sub.
I find the weapons room
and I can pull the launch chip
before she can fire any of those nukes.
That is too crazy.
What you're saying is too dangerous.
We'll do both.
Knock, knock.
Five vehicles just breached the base.
They just don't give up, do they?
All right, let's haul ass, team.
Double time, double time!
Letty, let's roll!
Go! Go, go, go!
Change of plans, Dom.
I'm sending you new coordinates.
Head there immediately.
I'm done. I want my son.
I'll tell you when you're done.
Your team is in play.
Now, meet Rhodes and follow my instruction.
I've got you covered! Go!
Move, move! Get outta here! Go, go, go!
Okay. How do you like this?
- Remote link has been severed.
- I'll take care of this.
Hi, Ramsey.
She's regained control.
Damn it. She's good.
They're entering the weapons room.
Oh, that's cute.
Pull! Pull!
Roman, Roman! We gotta find the chip, go!
Oh, she's slick.
Gonna have to do better than that, though.
Okay, now you're starting to piss me off.
Ramsey, how much time we talkin' here?
You're smart, but not smart enough.
She's locked me out.
Tej, I can't stop her.
You're gonna have to pull that chip.
I can't! This thing's gone into attack mode!
The door's not gonna open
until you pull the chip!
Tej, we got no idea
what the hell we're looking for.
I got it!
What in the hell are you guys doin'?
It wasn't me. It wasn't me, okay?
It'll be labeled "Guidance Go."
- Guidance Go, Guidance Go...
- Okay, I got somethin'.
- What?
- It says...
Do you understand that?
Wow. Nasty.
Quite a show.
We're arming the nuke.
(POWERING UP)
Nuke's going hot!
She's tryin' to fire this thing!
Roger that. We're moving out.
(OVER RADIO) Disable the nukes!
Roman, what are you seeing?
Come on, talk to me.
I don't see shit. I'm holding on!
And we have a countdown.
What the hell is goin' on, man?
We're about to launch a nuclear missile,
is what the hell is goin' on!
Pull the damn chip!
Countdown, countdown! Look for a countdown!
What countdown?
The missiles need to activate to launch.
The countdown timer won't be in Russian.
The countdown...
Let's show the world what we've got.
No, no, no! Don't press that!
I got it.
Something's wrong. It won't launch.
Get that sub outta there. Now!
Move your ass, Roman!
You all right?
There's nothing all right about any of this!
- Let's go!
- What about the missiles?
We got the chip. No nukes for her.
Hell, yeah. Let's roll.
Guys, we got company. A lot of company!
All right, team, here's the plan.
There's a sea lock at the opening of the bay.
We get there first and close it,
we can stop the submarine
from escaping into open water
and disappearing forever.
I've got the location.
It's 10 miles southwest.
Ten miles?
We're not gonna make it ten seconds!
No, no, no! This is not good!
What's the matter, Roman?
Forgot your snow tires?
Whoa!
You lovin' that Lambo now?
Whoa! Ah!
All right, everyone.
We'll deal with that launch chip later.
Right now, I want that sub
in deep water where no one can find it.
Find me the fastest route out of that bay.
Copy that.
Why are they shootin' at me?
Maybe 'cause you're in an orange
Lamborghini, I don't know.
Shut up, Tej!
Dom...
Do you really wanna put that car in gear?
Do it.
Huh?
I didn't think so.
They're heading for the sea lock.
They're trying to trap the sub in the bay.
I should have taken care
of this a long time ago.
Rhodes, take his team out.
I'm on it.
Roman, get in front of me!
Okay, y'all wanna play rough?
Now it's my turn.
Yeah, baby!
Guys, we got snowmobiles on the right.
They're gonna flank us!
No, they ain't!
Oh, shit!
Tej!
Roman, hold tight, I'm on the way!
I don't wanna go swimmin'! No!
Really, Tej?
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, shit!
Roman, grab your door!
Tej!
Grab the door, Roman!
- It's so cold!
- Shit!
Oh, shit!
Whoa!
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
What is going on?
Roman, hang on!
Tej!
Get me off of this thing!
Come on!
Argh!
All right. I've had enough of this shit!
Number 11, my ass!
Yo, shrinkage! We got a sub to catch. Get in!
What?
Depressurization alert in the cargo hold.
Drop it to 10,000 feet.
I know how much these people mean to you.
So I will let you pick the first target.
I don't pick a target from a mile away.
I stand face to face
and look 'em dead in the eye.
Okay.
The wife it is.
Nice plane. I'm gonna enjoy having this.
Hey, don't go gettin' any ideas.
You and planes don't have a good history.
No shit.
Okay, let's go, Scarface.
These assholes ain't gonna kill themselves.
Pull up surveillance right now.
Surprise.
You're supposed to be dead.
You're driving.
- I said from the beginning...
- No way.
- I am not going to drive.
- I'm not driving.
We have a security breach in
the cargo hold. Take care of it now.
Jesus, Mum.
You're supposed to avoid the nerves.
Oh, shut up. Don't be such a baby.
Get to the pilot.
He's got the second key. Wait for my signal.
Give Cipher my regards.
Did Toretto hold up his end of the deal?
He gave us this little thing here.
No, no, no. Don't touch.
You can track Cipher with this,
but you can't do this on your own.
There's gotta be two of ya.
Fine. I've got contacts.
No, you're gonna take your brother.
- Oh, dear...
- Yes.
Toretto knows where he is.
He's got this thing. It can see everything.
It's like... It's called
the Devil's Bum Hole or something.
It's called the God's Eye.
Yeah, well, whatever.
There's no way I'm using Owen, all right?
He's a lost cause.
He's your brother, Decks. He's my son.
He's our family.
And our family don't die in bloody cages.
How can you talk like that about Owen?
I can't believe you.
You've gone and upset me.
You've really upset your mother.
Call yourself a brother? You're...
Look, come here... Mum. Okay, okay.
Every time.
Owen.
In position.
Go.
I'm in.
I've got the package, Toretto.
All 12 pounds of him.
Ah.
Dada. Dada.
You made me miss my shot.
What you think you're doing?
Looking at you dead in the eye.
That was for Elena.
Rhodes.
He's no longer with us.
Rhodes picked the wrong target.
Congratulations, Dom.
You just killed your son.
You're wrong. I just saved him.
And you just took your foot
off the tiger's neck.
All right, governor, it's gonna get noisy.
This is for your ears.
Good?
Let's go.
No! Stop him!
Do not let him get off this plane!
We got another problem.
That truck's got
enough missiles to take us all out.
Then don't give 'em a target.
Everybody, get in front of us,
line up, and we'll take the hit.
What? I need to switch cars right now!
Target acquired.
- Roman, here comes the bad part.
- What?
Hang in there, guys.
We're almost to the lock.
It's easy for you to say
when your ass ain't on fire.
All right, little man,
this might be a little scary,
but it's gonna be a lot of fun.
How's the music, good?
Ah.
They're locking on.
Sorry, guys, I got no tricks left.
What do we do now?
We start prayin'!
Hell, yeah!
There's Dom!
What, is this guy on our side now?
Who the hell cares? He just saved our ass!
Good to be riding with you again, man.
Toretto just cleared the way for them.
Someone, give me something!
Torpedoes are ready.
Then launch them!
Shit.
- Take the wheel!
- I ain't takin' shit!
Take the wheel!
Where you goin'?
This is crazy!
Speed up!
- Left and back!
- What?
Turn the goddamn wheel
to the left really quickly!
Boom, baby!
Goin' for a ride.
Back in a sec.
- Where's that smile?
- Ah.
There it is.
You were gonna shoot a baby?
You sick bastard.
You're not gonna wanna see this.
Is that you or him?
Him. Good.
The torpedoes missed.
They're gonna reach the lock
before the sub does.
The hell they are.
Get ready for this.
Oh, shit!
We're gonna need a bigger truck.
It's right under us! Get out the way!
Get us out of here!
Why are you always yelling?
This bitch is crazy!
Look out!
That's not good.
Please tell me there's nothing
to worry about!
We got this.
That's my girl.
The sub's too close.
We ain't making it to the gate in time.
We're just going to let it get away?
Not if I know Dom.
You lose, Dom.
I destroyed two of your teams.
I killed your red-headed boyfriend.
And I put two killers
on your untraceable plane.
You lost the minute
you interrupted my honeymoon.
Now guess who I'm coming for.
Put a heatseeker on him now.
Now!
Fire!
That's a goddamn heatseeker coming at us!
Peel off! Head to the shore!
All right. Come and get it.
No, no, no.
Dive! Dive!
This...
This is for my son.
Dom!
You're out of bullets, Deckard.
Not like I'm gonna need a gun
to take care of you.
How did you find me?
You want to see the old Dom?
Watch.
Resourceful.
You have a lot to answer for, Cipher.
What you've put my family through.
My mother.
I'm gonna make sure that never happens again.
To anyone.
There is only one flaw in your plan.
What's that?
Only one of us has a parachute.
Told you this would be fun.
Time to land, boys.
You know I never left you, Letty.
I know.
And you know I never will.
I have so much to tell you.
Yeah, you do.
And you can start with that bitch.
Now, that's Dominic Toretto.
Hey, Dom!
I'm just throwin' it out there,
we need to get up outta here
'cause there's all kinda nuclearism
happening under this ice.
Relax. Without the trigger chips,
those nukes are harmless.
Okay. So we good, then.
Let me go on and get
my young selfie levels up.
You realize this is classified, right?
Not today.
Unbelievable.
All right, can we get up
outta here, now? I'm freezin'!
It's okay.
Don't worry. He's gonna be here soon.
I get it. Y'all got a lot in common.
Computer hacks, God's Eye,
geeks, nerd... You know.
But we got a lot in common, too, right?
Like what?
We walk in the room
and we're oozin' sex appeal.
Me and you, hip to hip, is a problem.
I'm askin' a real question right now.
Is it gonna be Revenge of the Nerds
or The Dark Knight? Huh?
To be honest, I like both of you.
But just before we get into all of that,
let me ask you one question.
You can ask me anything.
Anything.
What's my last name?
When you guys figure it out,
then, I guess you can let me know.
It's gonna be Parker.
That's all that really matters.
- Jones.
- Mrs. Parker.
- Right?
- Hey, Mrs. Parker...
Hey.
Letty.
I wanted to thank you.
No need.
Well...
Cipher's still on the loose.
There's been some reports she's in Athens,
but she won't be nuking
any cities anytime soon.
Thanks to you guys.
So, I got you a party favor.
This can't be good.
Your record's been cleared.
Full reinstatement.
You've got your job back.
That is, if you want it.
If I want?
Mmm-hmm.
You know, after 16 years,
I figure it's time for a little break.
Wow.
Daddy's stayin' home.
Nobody.
Keep in touch.
Ah. Hang on a second.
This could be interesting.
What made you think I'd do it?
Brotherhood.
I saw that look you gave Cipher,
knew you wanted revenge.
Glad I did it.
I can't believe you went to see my mother.
All this fuss over you.
Yes.
Elena, I promised to keep our son safe.
And now, he always will be.
I wanna introduce you to the most
important person in my universe.
One who never gave up on me.
He's beautiful.
You've heard me say that you
never turn your back on family,
and I wanna thank you all
for never turning your back on me.
You wanna meet them?
All right.
Everyone,
meet Brian.
To Brian!
Welcome to the family, Brian.
Okay, I guess it's my turn to say grace.
We thank you for giving us family.
We sit here in praise.
Thank you for giving us the strength...