That's the cleanup crew
up on the track,
and that's a lot of racers
involved there, folks.
Jack, you realize
you got this in the bag, right?
Season's wrapped up, man.
Doesn't matter where you place.
I'm telling you,
I got intermittent miss.
- Last two laps.
- On it!
Get those plug wires!
Jakob! Now.
Hey, pop.
Tell me what you see, Dom.
Got an oil spill
going into turn two.
Bell's driving safe.
Corbin's got a sponsor in
the stands, so he's pushing it.
Talking about me?
You got a real problem
with car 23.
- Linder.
- About to whip your ass, Toretto!
- Settle down, pretty boy!
- That's right.
- Shut up!
- Yeah, you. You want to tell your driver
- he's gonna get somebody hurt?
- What'd you say?
- Hey! Leave it!
- Go home! You suck!
He's just pissed I got that spot
in the Busch series
next season, not him.
Life's got no shortage of guys
like Kenny Linder.
You're good!
It's not about being
the stronger man, Dom.
It's about being the bigger one.
I swear to God, this guy.
Pop, turn two, turn two!
Got it. I'm walking him in.
Shit!
Tell me what you see, Dom.
He's gonna come at you for that.
Get ready on your left.
Dad!
He's gone! He's gone!
We got to get him out of there.
We got to get him out of there!
That's my dad!
That's my dad! That's my dad!
Get him out of there!
That's my dad!
There's a couple of release
forms we've got to sign.
Few clearances.
Everything else is down there
around the corner.
Hey.
Nobody's supposed to be
around here.
You Toretto's other son?
You're the useless one, right?
What is that?
Get out of here. Go.
So a man can't pay
his last respects?
That's what that is?
No.
No, not you.
You're the one that killed him.
No, racing killed him.
Look, he knew that I was gonna
pit him into the wall.
He knew that.
Now, I don't know if
he dropped gear. I don't know.
I swear... I swear to God,
- if you don't get out of here...
- What? What?
Go find Buddy.
Now!
All right, well,
now we got the golden boy.
Leave.
You here to make threats, too?
"Leave" is a simple word.
Man, what is it
with you Torettos
where you're all the heroes
in your own stories?
Look, I'm gonna
tell you a secret.
You, your dad, me...
We're all stuck,
going round and round
in the same shitty circle.
And we ain't never getting out.
You ain't half the man
my dad was.
- At least I'm alive, asshole.
- What did you say?
Get off me!
Dom! Dom!
Dom!
Dom, no! Dom!
No, man!
It's all gonna be okay, Jakob.
We got some rough times ahead...
but it's gonna be okay.
'Cause we're family.
Yo, what do you think?
¿Es una ilusión o es real?
It doesn't matter.
It's all about
how you choose to see it.
Shit. I told you I was right.
- I'm Leo.
- Santos.
Dom. What are you guys in for?
Driving while brown.
You see that?
Hairline crack in the fuel line.
Air gets in there,
you got a lean condition.
Lean condition?
Yeah! Yeah, Jakob!
That's what I'm talking about!
Who wants next?
I said, who wants next?!
I got next.
Dom.
Well, when'd you get out, man?
I said I got next.
Come on, Dom.
You don't want to race me
in Buddy's old charger.
Car don't make the driver.
Here's how this goes.
You win...
You can come back home.
You lose...
You keep driving,
you don't stop,
you don't ever come back.
Ever.
What do you mean, Dom?
I know what you did.
The day we lost him, dad kept
talking about a misfire.
Remember?
You were the last one
under his hood that day.
A minute later, he was gone.
Tell me why you killed dad.
Now let's race.
Armed robbery in echo park.
- Fourth street bridge is open.
- Clear, clear, clear!
Ready?
Set.
Go.
Too soon.
No!
How many calories
in each stick?
550.
How many grams of fat?
32 grams, but we do
cook it in vegetable oil.
I'll take two then.
Could I have mine extra crispy?
Sure. No problem.
It's not as hard as it looks.
All it takes is
the extra five minutes
reading the manual
after you get hired.
The way I saw it,
as long as it made it
on my college application,
it was all worth it.
You just can't count
on good grades
to get into a decent
school anymore.
Virgil and I have been friends
since the fourth grade,
when he moved to my school.
He was the other smart kid.
Let's go, you perv.
Dude, did you see the
fucking rack on that?
Man, middle-aged
hos are the finest.
This is Han, Virgil's cousin.
He's everything Virgil's not.
You ladies ready?
I shoot 215 free throws a day.
My goal is to beat
Calvin Murphy's record
of 95.8 percent.
That's 207 baskets.
Punctilious.
"Marked by or concerned
about precise, exact accordance
with the details
of codes or conventions."
To get a perfect score
on my next SAT
I needed to improve
my verbal score by 60 points.
I picked a new word every day
and repeated it over
and over again.
They say if you repeat
something enough times,
it becomes part of you.
Punctilious. Adjective.
"Marked by or concerned
about precise, exact accordance
with the details
of codes or conventions."
Stephanie Vandergosh.
It's girls like her
that make you realize
that life's not fair.
I swear, I saw her in a porn.
What are you babbling about?
Daric Loo, academic all-star.
But don't let the letterman
jacket fool you--
it's for tennis.
Hey, so we're using your
credit card, right?
If we get caught,
I'm saying you stole it from me.
Nigga, please.
The amoeba
is a primitive and simple organism,
which absorbs its prey
and incorporates it into itself.
Miss Vandergosh
and Miss Nabham,
is there something you would like
to share with the class?
I thought as much.
Uh, Mr. Farmer, please switch
seats with Miss Vandergosh.
Now that I have your
complete attention,
today we will see a movie.
It is entitled, The Amoeba.
Lunch time was club time.
This was where everyone loaded
up on their extracurricular
activities for their college app.
And, of course, Daric was
the president of every club.
...but, being part of an ecology
club, it's important that we do.
Unfortunately, all
the really worthwhile things
about high school
were few and far between.
She is right down the hall
Well, what I'm
most concerned about
are the abrasions
on her arms and her back.
It was my fault--
I fell down some stairs,
but I feel fine now.
Don't get me wrong.
I mean, I think there's some
pretty fine-looking
bitches in high school.
It's just that they're all
so fucking stingy
about giving it up.
Dude, you're a
fucking virgin.
Dude, I can get laid
whenever I want to.
Any time, anywhere, any place.
Yeah, by who, your
middle-aged aunt?
No, but your mom's been
looking mighty fine lately.
Hey, shut the fuck up.
Especially with those...
what was that thing
she bought the other day?
Okay, it comes to $482.82.
Is your brother Carl?
Yeah.
I thought you looked familiar.
I-I'm Virgil.
I was in, uh, Cub Scouts
with your brother.
Oh, this is my friend, Ben.
Hi.
Hey.
So, uh, what are you
doing these days?
I just got out of college.
Oh, what was your major?
Theater.
Theater. That's, that's...
I love the theater, you know.
It's a...
Sign here.
That makes you, like,
a thespian, right?
You know, you-you have that,
like, kind of an "X" factor,
that charisma thing.
You definitely got it going, really.
Thanks.
Well, it was nice
seeing you again.
Yeah. So... plays.
Let me know if
you're ever in one or...
Hey, Virg...
So.
Okay.
Yeah. Yeah, cool.
Yeah, di...?
What the fuck was that?
What?
You're gonna get us caught!
Watch it!
Like she's gonna go for you.
At least I try.
That's enough, girls.
We were always pissed at Virgil,
but we always let it slide.
We had to--
he's like the little puppy
that keeps shitting on the carpet.
Hey, Virg.
What color is the sticker today, man?
Wake up!
Orange.
Give 'em up.
Let's go.
Fuck you.
Hi.
It's my little brother,
and he came home
with all this computer stuff
he can't afford.
So my mom...
Yeah. Do you have a receipt?
It started with
a pack of baseball cards,
and then it snowballed.
I guess it just felt good
to do things
that I couldn't put
on my college application.
Besides, it was suburbia...
we had nothing better to do.
Our straight A's were our alibis,
our passports to freedom.
Going to a study group
would get us out of the house
until 4:00 in the morning.
As long as our grades
were there, we were trusted.
We had it all.
Well, almost.
"Uncap the needle."
"Swab the finger
with the rubbing alcohol."
"Prick the finger."
Come on, Ben.
On three.
One...
See, that wasn't so bad.
All right, let's go.
Come on, now.
Good job. Run! Come on, now.
Get down, get down,
run, run, run.
Stay low when you make
that pass.
Got to get in front of him.
In front of him!
Dive, come on!
Who wants that ball?
Who wants it?
Don't stand up.
Do not stand up.
Make two, we'll go home.
Hey, Stephanie.
Oh, hey, Ben.
How's it going?
Good.
How's your finger?
Oh.
I'll live.
You have a Band-Aid on it.
Yeah.
It's a pin prick.
Don't you want to be
a doctor or something?
If I don't play pro basketball.
Aren't you a little short?
Only the size of your heart matters.
That's corny.
What about you?
What do you want to be?
A cop.
Really? Aren't you
a little too short?
Not when I have this.
Ooh.
You're late.
Sorry.
And you're
not wearing a helmet.
Oh. Ben, this is
my boyfriend, Steve.
Steve,
this is Ben, my lab partner.
Oh, yeah.
I have something for you.
What is this?
This isn't even due until next week.
I had some free time
so I thought that--
We're lab partners.
We're supposed
to do this together.
Give me a call.
We'll meet to do the assignment.
Let's go.
Later.
It's amazing what the right
piece of clothing
can do for your image.
I knew it was all bullshit,
but, hell, I was milking it
for all it was worth.
At first it didn't matter
that I rarely saw
any playing time.
I was part of the team.
But like everything else
in life, you get sick of it.
At least it'll look good
on my college app.
Okay.
Ain't no party
like a Wildcat party
like a Wildcat party.
Look at that ass.
Yeah. What's up, Ben?
Hey, Daric.
Hey, you got a sec?
I'm trying to finish up
this assignment.
Okay.
Cool.
So, Ben, how do you feel
about being a benchwarmer?
What?
Well, you don't get
to play much, right?
Yeah, but we all have
our roles on the team.
And what is your role?
I don't know.
I just hustle.
Well, then how come
you don't get to
play in the games?
Well, it's up to the coach.
Well, how do you feel
about being the token
Asian on a team?
What?
It's obvious to everyone
the only reason that
you're on the team
is for cosmetic ones.
That's bullshit.
I bust my ass
to be on this team.
But you never get to play.
So what?
I'm still on the team.
Well, your coach
could've picked anyone
he wanted to just
to sit on the bench.
Maybe you should
just ask him then.
Okay. Awesome.
Thanks, buddy.
Hey, Takeshi, can you, uh,
give me a few close-ups
and a couple wides?
Yeah, you got it.
Hi.
Is Stephanie home?
Hey.
Stephanie, I just want
to apologize for...
Ben, I'm in
three honor classes,
and I have a 3.8 GPA.
I know and I'm sorry.
I couldn't find the traits
to phylum chordata in the book.
Um, it's not in the book.
It was in his lecture.
See? It was
last Tuesday's lecture.
...cells. This one is
more of a non-sexual
cell division.
Right. Okay.
And that's when mitosis happens...
That was one, anaphase?
Anaphase.
And then metaphase,
interphase and prophase.
You got it.
Yes. Okay.
I think you're right.
Let me just make sure.
When I'm right, I'm right.
You're right.
Hello?
Hey, Steve-o.
Oh, Ben and I are working
on our bio homework.
Yes, I'm sure.
Can you hold on a minute?
I'll be right back.
Yeah. What?
Do you want something to drink?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Where are you going?
It's getting pretty late.
But we haven't gone
through meiosis yet.
Well, I could stay.
Thanks.
Uh, okay. Meiosis.
Hey, Ben.
Be there for you, man,
every game.
We want Ben! We want Ben!
We want Ben!
Daric ended up writing
an article about me.
He even won some kind
of journalism award for it.
It was some bullshit article
about affirmative action
in school sports
to rile everyone up.
We want Ben! We want Ben!
But I had to give it to him...
The article worked.
If anyone at school didn't know
what affirmative action was,
they did now.
Aw sh... Ben, Ben, get in.
Go on. Get the fuck in there.
Yeah!
Math or verbal?
What the fuck do you want?
So how does it feel
to be famous?
Come on.
Why'd you quit the team?
I was doing my job.
You call that piece-of-shit
article journalism?
You didn't even interview
my coach for his views.
I did.
He, uh, didn't say
what I wanted him to,
so I didn't put it in the story.
Fucking prick.
It's just an article.
If you really liked
what you were doing,
you should have
just kept on playing.
And have everybody think
I'm on the team
because I'm some token player?
Who cares
what other people think?
Oh, yeah?
Well, people also think
that you gave Mr. Reid head
to be the editor
of the school paper.
Well, I still am the editor.
God. Fuck off.
You know this is all bullshit, right?
It's just a game.
People like you and me,
we don't have to play
by the rules.
We can make our own.
Do this by tomorrow,
you get a fifty.
What?
Hey, I don't just ask anyone
to do this.
Cheat sheets?
It's easy money.
Ben,
it's easier than fuck.
It's better than
this sorry-ass job.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, Ben.
Hey.
Uh, I'm getting my Diet Coke.
You guys want anything?
Uh, yeah.
Give me a root beer float to go.
I got it.
Trig?
Uh, yeah.
Excuse me.
There's no smoking
allowed in this cafe.
California state law.
Sorry.
Can't wait till I get out.
What are you majoring in
in college?
Bio.
Doing any internships?
No.
I know some people.
I'll give them a call.
Cool.
You like Steph.
What?
You want to take her
to the winter formal?
Isn't that your job?
I don't get into
all that bullshit.
Why, you a fag or something?
What do you think?
Hey.
Thanks.
Thanks, honey.
Okay. Okay, I'll
see you soon?
Okay. Which species
should we start with?
Um, I was... thinking
about the, uh, Chapter Eight.
Temerity. Noun.
"Unwise boldness;
rash or reckless behavior."
Oh-oh.
Nice.
Good job.
Oh, shit. Sorry, dude.
Hey, man. What's going on?
Popcorn?
So how much did we actually
earn last year at the car wash?
Like $400 and something.
So that's only like $400.
We only got that
one day to do it, so....
Uh, you guys mind
if we have a moment?
Uh, me and Ben?
Oh.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, but we got
to talk about this.
Sure. Thanks.
What's up?
Hey.
Oh. Sweet.
Aren't you gonna check it?
Nah. I trust you.
Get going?
Yeah.
All right?
Academic decathlon was huge.
The most prized entry
on a college application.
This was not like
some community service club
where you just
walk in and sign out.
You had to earn your spot.
Pygmy mouse
lemur.
Excellent.
Tetrahydrocannabinol.
Jersey, Guernsey
and Albany.
Hands by your side.
Check.
Portugal!
I didn't ask a question.
Sorry!
Bohemia, Moravia
and Silesia.
Correct.
Johnson.
Excellent.
You're right.
Another language that...
Tokyo,
Japan.
Excellent.
Ahh!
Correct.
Hey.
See you in class.
Good job, man.
What are you
talking about?
I got my ass kicked.
No, you knew the answers.
You just got to get
the timing down.
50 bucks if you
do it by tomorrow.
Dude, I think
we got enough.
Stop bitching.
Just a few more blocks.
Did I tell you?
I got it.
Got what?
Remember I told you
I saw Stephanie
Vandergosh in a porn?
Yeah.
I got it.
Shut the fuck up.
I'll show you right now, fool.
Oh, my God.
Oh...
So you've been hanging around
that Daric guy, right?
Yeah.
Is it true that he
has his own house?
I don't know.
Hmm. Han told me that his
parents don't live here.
They're in, like,
Vancouver or something.
So what?
You know what I could
do if I had my own pad?
Jerk off at the dinner table?
Ha-ha.
Your turn.
Fucker.
What?
No hot tub?
Well, you tell them,
if they want me,
they're gonna ante up
with that hot tub!
Tracy, what are you doing here?
Well, I can give you
a special Tracy massage.
See? I told you, punk ass.
No.
It's just the uniform.
Uh-uh. It's got to be her.
Oh, yes, Tracy.
Yeah.
Work those pom-poms.
I dare you to ask her boyfriend.
White dude, right?
No.
Thank God.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
Shake those pom-poms.
Ben?
Huh?
You think you can
talk to Daric for me
about doing the cheat sheets?
Mm-hmm. Uh-huh.
How do you know about it?
I hear things.
Han told me.
Fucking Daric's a senior.
Someone's got to take
over when he leaves.
All right. The topic is
population control,
why retarded children
and handicapped people
should be executed
in order to keep
the population down. Ready?
Is that true?
I think it was.
'Cause it didn't sound
like you knew it.
Make sure your glasses
are anti-glare, okay?
Let's see.
Oh...
Decathlon practices were always
held at Daric's house.
Finish it!
His methods were
definitely unconventional
but effective.
Beautiful.
Rock, scissors, paper.
Oh, fuck.
I'm so unworthy
at this moment.
Ah...
Dude. Dude, dude,
you're gonna explode, man.
Don't light that shit.
Come on.
Oh.
Good-bye, guys.
Study hard.
Come on.
Oh.
Not bad for academic
decathlon, huh?
Han had a friend named Jesus
who helped him steal, bribe
or do whatever it took
to get the test sheets for us.
I talked to Daric
and he was cool
with Virgil coming on board.
Between the five of us,
there wasn't anything
we couldn't do.
The money was really good,
but I don't think that's
what attracted me the most.
Okay, okay.
They got lucky.
But, you know,
there is no reason
a team of that caliber
should be able
to beat us. God.
Mary!
Where's your tie?
I mean, our presentation
absolutely sucked.
We looked like idiots.
Rich, privey fucks.
Press the button.
Wait till
the question is asked.
We're getting locked out
and we can't even
answer the question.
God! Ben.
Fucking twinkie.
American history specialist.
The answer was 1973, not '76.
How many more, Ben?
Would you shut up?
I told you guys not to come.
Woo!
So how's Stephanie?
Virg.
Stephanie Vandergosh?
I'm going out
with her Friday night.
I asked her out last week.
Does she know it's a date?
Why? Want to lay
some money down on it?
Yeah.
How 'bout an even hundred?
Okay, you got it.
Fucking A.
You motherfucker.
This is fucked.
Hey, Daric wanted us to see it.
You know she has a boyfriend.
Well, this'll teach that fuckhead
to keep his mouth shut.
Oh, fuck.
Is that the guy
from the privey school?
What does he think he is,
some Chinese movie star?
Hi, I am Chow Yun-Fat.
Hi. I-I-I thought
I was gonna be fucking your
girlfriend tonight.
I-I guess not.
I guess I better go home
and stroke myself really good.
Let's go.
Really, really good.
Ahh!
Hey, hold on,
I'm just getting started.
Get the fuck off my car.
Ow.
Damn, dude.
Dude, you got to tell Stephanie
her boyfriend's boning
some white chick.
It's none of my business.
What the fuck are
you talking about?
You tell her and
you get bonus points.
I'm not gonna be some rat.
Besides, I don't
even know for sure.
Come on, Ben. Look...
This... is for buddies.
So?
And this is where
he had his hands...
which is for lovers.
God! Get off me!
Am I right, Han?
Daric, where you going?
Mm. Oh, sh...
Yo, fuck her, man.
Let's go drink.
Hey!
Shit. No, Daric!
Whose party is this?
Susie Berk's.
Are we invited?
You don't need an invitation.
Just hear about
it and you go.
They're all fucking
drunk, anyway.
So, is everyone buzzed?
Yo, can I have a light?
Thanks, dude.
Let's go around back.
Hey, how's it goin'?
Ah...!
Now I'm gonna throw up.
Hey, what's up, boys?
I think they have...
bible study's next door, right?
Oh, shit, no, look at this!
It's the Chinese Jordan!
Hey, so,
what's up, man?
Where's all your
fan club at, man?
I'm going to go
check on Virg.
Yeah, what's
up, shithead?
Are you going
to step up?
You know, you got
to play a real sport
to wear that jacket.
Yeah, fuck him up, Brian!
Want your mom?
Huh? You want the cops?
You're what?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
What?!
I'm sorry.
Shoot him in the face.
If I ever see any of you
and your fuck
jock friends again,
I'll fucking kill you!
Back off, man,
back off!
You want some of this?!
Back off, man!
Ben, come on!
Back off!
Come on, Ben!
Fuck you, man!
Screw you!
Let's go!
Fuckin' A,
that was better than sex.
Just shut the fuck up.
Did you see the look
on that guy's face?
You put the fear
of God in him, man.
The fear of Gods.
I went jihad
on his ass, man.
You see this
blood on me, man?
It's not my blood.
Did you see his face
when we worked on him?
It was like...
Fuck, man, when you
pulled out that gun,
it was fucking awesome.
That was, like, boom!
Right in your face.
He probably pissed himself
right then
in front
of all his homies.
Not me, man.
I was going off.
I felt so...
I felt like
surging through my body.
How smooth was that?
Man, you had fucking balls!
That was fucking smooth!
The next minute, the gun
was right in his face,
and I was going off--
ah, yeah!
Shit.
If my dad finds out,
he's going to kill me.
Man, I'm going to juvie!
By Monday, the word had spread
and pretty much everyone
knew about it.
I was sure the cops were gonna
come and get us that morning...
but it never happened.
Meeting today at 3:00.
Why?
We have to do
this chem test.
It's a big one,
about a hundred students.
Guys...
Hi, guys.
Hey.
Ben, can I talk to you?
Yeah.
He's fuckin'
whupped already.
What's up?
I just talked to Steve.
Yeah...
What?
He said you're taking me
to the formal.
You're fucking with me, right?
He said that you guys agreed
to have you take me
to the formal.
He did ask, I didn't agree.
The whole thing
was pretty weird.
You should have
at least told me.
Well, he's your boyfriend.
I didn't want to get involved.
Ben, that's what friends do.
God, I don't believe this.
Why do I always get shit on?
You know, Steve,
he's the one that
needs to stop...
Ben, I'm just trying
to understand this.
I'm out of here.
What the fuck?!
Woo!
What? The formal?
Oh, what, got a hot date
with Barbie that night?
Look, I'm not gonna
say anything,
all right, it's none
of my business.
I just think
she deserves better.
You're probably right.
As our reputation grew,
scams started coming to us.
Usually through Jesus.
There they are.
What I liked about it was
that we were in control.
If someone came to us
about doing a scam
and we didn't like them,
we'd tell them to fuck off.
Having that kind of power
quickly became an addiction.
What's up?
How's it going, man?
What's going on?
How are you doing?
Man, not too bad.
This is Peter.
So, what's up?
Peter's got a sweet deal.
The school's getting in all new
computer parts next week.
So?
So they've got to store them
for a while
until they can install them.
Peter's got the school codes.
Can they trace the code?
No, it's all the same number
for everyone.
What about that
fucking family
that lives in the trailer
guarding the school?
That's me and my dad.
He's out by 10:00.
It's easy.
I don't know.
Sounds too easy.
Dude, I guarantee.
No offense,
I don't give a shit
about your guarantee.
Me and Ben checked it out.
Seems legit.
Han, think you can
sell this shit off?
I can always sell
the shit off.
We'll think about it.
Peter, let's go.
You got the phone?
Uh-huh.
Ah, God. Fuck.
It's clear.
We had the run of the place.
Rumors about us came
and went fast and furious.
One had us linked
with some Chinese Mafia.
And it was fine with us
because it just put more fear
in everyone.
Along with that power
came greed.
It just made sense to expand
our business into drugs,
putting the law of supply
and demand into practice.
I think our teacher
would've been proud.
Whoa.
Let me see this thing.
Fuck off.
It's got no
name brand on it.
Aw...!
Shit.
Sorry, Virg.
Fuckin' dick.
Stop crying.
It's a piece-of-shit
CD player anyway.
Fuck you!
Here.
Now you can buy three of 'em.
I soon learned that along with
an image, came maintenance.
I needed something
to help expand my days.
It's literally a full-time job
just to make people believe
who you're supposed to be.
Four cheat sheets a day,
the drugs, the scams--
between this and
all my club commitments,
I couldn't even start
my homework until 1:00 a.m.
We were making so much money,
we couldn't spend it
fast enough.
If it was for sale, you could
bet we tried to buy it.
Is that enough?
Mm-hmm.
All right.
Hey, Tracy.
Thanks, it's all there.
Thank you.
So, what are you guys?
A club.
Oh, like a math club
or something?
We partied every weekend
and hung out
with different crowds.
It's funny,
the more notorious we became,
the more invitations we got.
We didn't know half the people
we partied with...
but they knew us.
Quixotic. Adjective.
Extravagantly idealistic;
unpredictable;
unrealistic or imaginary.
Shit.
You look like shit.
Fifty.
Oh, yeah.
Here's the number
for that internship
I was telling you about.
Thanks.
Yeah. You want some?
You happy, Ben?
I'm serious.
You happy?
I don't know.
Fuck.
That's the most truthful thing
I've ever heard.
At least you have a choice.
You're not happy?
I'm very happy.
Isn't it obvious?
I have everything.
Loving parents, top grades,
Ivy League scholarships,
of course, Stephanie.
Of course.
Right there.
That's it.
I'm so fucking happy
I can't stop it.
Why not?
It's a never-ending cycle.
When you got everything
you want, what's left?
You can't settle
for being happy,
that's a fucking trap.
You got to take life
into your own hands.
Do whatever it takes
to break the cycle.
That's what it is,
breaking the cycle.
You're fucked.
I envy you.
What?
What? What?
It was my 17th birthday.
No shit, man.
Fuck, man.
I don't want to touch that.
I don't want to touch it
with my hands, man.
There he is.
Hey, ass-wipe,
you're the one that organized
this "Keep the Beach Clean"
shit and you're late.
I need to talk to you guys.
Grab a bag.
Where's Han?
Sleeping.
What's up?
This better be
fucking good.
I want out.
Out of what?
I can't handle this anymore.
Look, I woke up and my sheets
were covered in blood.
Well, why don't you stop
OD'ing on that shit,
you fuck?
Yeah, too much of that shit
will get to you.
I don't want to do it anymore.
All of it.
Fuck, Ben, stop being a pussy.
Whatever, Virg.
So is that it?
Yeah, I just...
I just want to concentrate
on my own stuff.
Hell, I was thinking
the same thing.
Give it up?
Yeah.
Fuck it. It's like a job, man.
The only reason I did
it was for you guys.
What are you saying?
Have you two lost
your fucking balls?
Fuck it.
Han and I will do it.
Right, Han?
It's all yours, man.
We got to talk.
Just shut the fuck up.
More money
for us.
I'm gonna call Jesus
right after this.
Organize this shit.
Well...
Happy birthday, man.
Thanks.
We all chipped in.
Pretty cool, huh?
Jesus Christ!
Shit!
Fuck!
Hey.
Temperance. Noun.
Signifying self-restraint
or moderation
in action and statement.
Hi, Stephanie.
Hi.
You need help?
I'm okay.
You know, I hate
doing those S's.
The curves
make it tough,
but I know a trick.
You work it inside out.
See?
So, what's this I hear
about you, gangster boy?
Oh, God, that's
such old news.
Rumors have it you guys
did a number on Ryan.
Do you believe them?
Let's put it this way,
there's also a rumor
that I am in a porno.
Oh, yeah, I've seen it.
Shut up.
Yeah, I have.
Really?
Yeah.
So the shooting arm
is perpendicular
to the body?
Mm-hmm.
Bend your knees
and follow through.
Is that it?
I'm hungry.
Excuse me, sir.
There's no food
allowed in the store.
Oh, uh, I'm sorry.
I'm hypoglycemic
and I just need
a little something
to get my blood sugar going.
I just got a couple
more bites left.
Okay.
You think you can get away
with anything, don't you?
No.
Well, yeah, if you're
clever enough.
You sound just like Steve.
You don't like
him much, do you?
Speaking of Steve,
um, you still need
a date for the formal?
Are you asking?
Well, if you'll go with me.
Oh, yeah.
Holy shit.
I guess I was clever enough,
thank you very much.
A week later Han
got suspended from school
for distributing cheat sheets.
It appeared
that Virgil's new position
as head of the outfit
had gone to his head.
He was babbling
to so many people about it,
the school had to do something.
The funny thing was,
Han didn't really care
that he got suspended.
I think it just gave him
yet another excuse
to beat the crap out of Virgil.
Hey.
You look great.
Jinx.
Two for flinching.
Ow!
Here.
Thank you.
Jeez.
So, do you know
your real parents?
Do you want to?
My parents I have now
are my real parents.
I don't know.
Maybe when I get older.
I still have to find out
who I am.
Yeah.
You sound so mature.
That's what my therapist
tells me, at least.
Thanks for asking, though.
Uh, I had a wonderful time.
Thanks again.
Yeah.
All right, question six:
name of the largest
commercial transport jet.
Virgil!
The Space Guppy.
Where the fuck is he, man?
Jesus.
Hey, open up, man.
Where the fuck you going, man--
on a honeymoon?
No, man; I got my accessories.
Yeah, what, your anal intruder?
No, my lubrication.
You're just so dry, Daric.
Don't slam the
trunk either, man.
Hey, yo!
Motherfucker.
As we headed off to Vegas
for the decathlon nationals,
Stephanie
was all I could think about.
I finally decided that there
were two things I could do--
go on agonizing over Stephanie,
or just say fuck it and have fun.
Vegas sucks.
Hey, turn that down.
The sound is the best part.
Oh, yeah!
Ben, Virgil,
I want you to meet Rachel.
Hey.
Hi.
You're Ben?
Yeah.
What are you studying?
Um... Econ.
Econ?
Yeah.
Brother, today
is your lucky day.
What?
Yeah!
Whoo!
Go get 'em.
All right, sweetie,
here are the rules.
No kissing,
and I always lead.
Come on, sweetie.
How was it?
Oh, you bad, bad boy.
That is so disgusting, man.
Come on, man.
Actually, it was...
incredible.
I just couldn't believe
I had finally done it.
It was such a relief.
I had prayed every day
up until that moment
that I would have sex
before I died.
Thank you.
Dude, man, wasn't
she awesome?
Wasn't she awesome, man?
Mmm...
Dude, what the fuck?
Here you go.
Fuck! God damn it!
Your little friend
pulled a gun on me.
Calm down!
Shut up, Virg!
Fuck you.
Look, this is more money
than we owe you.
Fuck all of you.
What are you doing, Virg?
You crazy?
She said she wanted
to play rough.
You want to play fucking rough?!
Stop it!
Put the gun down!
I want to play rough.
Virgil, put the gun down.
Put the gun down.
What do you think now, hotshot?
Virg, put the gun down.
Get the fuck off me.
The morning after
I lost my virginity,
we won the national title.
I don't sell that shit no more.
That's cool.
How have you been?
Haven't seen you
since the... Formal.
Right.
Hey, by the way,
I never got a chance
to thank you
for taking Stephanie.
She said she had the best time.
Maybe you can take her
to all the school functions.
You should try it.
You might like it.
It's all a superficial,
bullshit waste of time.
Yeah, you mentioned that.
I have a proposition for you.
Actually, for you
and your buddies.
Look, that's all in the past.
Listen, you guys are definitely
going to like this.
It's too sweet.
No, thanks.
Well, give me
the other guys' digits.
I thought we were friends.
That has nothing
to do with this.
There's going to be
a lot of money involved.
You already got all
the money you need.
Change.
I don't give a shit
about the cash.
It's what
we've been talking about.
It's time to break the cycle.
What?
Listen, this is going to better
everyone involved.
Just trust me.
Ben, did he tell you
what this is all about?
No.
Fuckin' rich boy.
Let's talk outside.
Steve,
this is Virgil...
Hey.
...and Han.
David, right?
Daric.
Sorry.
How's your stroke?
My stroke?
You guys want
something to drink?
Yeah, I'll take a beer.
Beer.
Okay.
Have a seat.
I'll be right back.
What's up with that guy?
Stroke?
Hey, by the way, congrats
on winning the Nationals.
Thank you.
What happened to you guys?
Too many freshmen.
Their fuckin' brains froze
in the semis.
What are you going to do?
The streak had to end sometime.
So, why are we here?
You're looking at it.
What?
We do my parents' house.
Yo, that's fucked up.
Why?
It's none of your fuckin' business.
Okay.
Let's go, guys.
Everyone needs a wake-up call.
I love them.
That's why I'm doing this.
"I love them.
That's why I'm doing this."
That dude's fucked up.
Let's do it.
Let's fuckin' do it.
No.
No. We're not gonna rob anyone.
Everyone needs a wake-up call.
That's what he said, right?
Let's fuckin'
give it to him.
Look, that shit is just weird.
Oh, yeah, it is.
We're gonna play along
for a while,
and then we're gonna teach
that fucker
a lesson.
Virg, don't you see the way
that guy talks to you?
That dude doesn't even think
you're on the same level.
Think about it.
What about you, Han?
That rich motherfucker wants
to punish his own family?
Why?
Because Mommy and Daddy won't
pay enough attention to him?
And you.
He thinks
you're fuckin' dickless.
No? Well, why else
would he let you take
his girlfriend to the formal?
No. No!
We'll just rough 'em up
a little bit.
Mostly... we'll scare
the shit out of him.
Dude, this is brilliant.
After we fuckin'
beat the shit out of him,
we could turn him in
to the cops
for conspiring to rob
his own family.
Exactly.
Oh, yeah!
Ooh.
Come on, guys.
I don't know.
Come on!
Let's do it!
Yeah.
It'll be fun.
All right, man,
I'm just doing this
so you don't fuck
this up, all right?
Yeah.
Yeah!
No, I can't.
This'll be our blueprint.
Let's start on page three.
By the way,
I'm going to need a gun.
I know. I'm working on it.
Can I get one of those
semiautomatics?
It'll cost you.
Just take it out of my share.
No. We'll need the
money up front.
All right.
Just let me know how much.
No problem.
Steve was meticulous.
He had mapped out each of
our paths for the robbery.
He made us do it
over and over
until he felt we got it.
I just don't know what
Stephanie found so attractive.
So...
At all!
...Han, you think
you can break in?
Fuck, yeah.
That's it.
I can't handle it anymore.
I ain't going
to the meeting tomorrow.
Shut up!
Look, we all have to do it,
or it'll just fuck it all up.
Well, I still ain't going!
Dude, why?
'Cause Chrissy's throwin'
a party tomorrow.
Why don't we just
invite him to come?
He's the one who said
we should get to know
each other.
Whatever.
You think he'll show?
Who cares, man?
At least we don't have to sit
through all that bullshit.
I can't wait till
this is all over.
You watch.
It'll all be worth it.
Be right back.
Hey, Steph.
Hey, Ben.
Where's Steve?
I don't know.
He told me to meet him here.
He's on time as usual.
Hey.
Whoa. Is it real?
Just got it done this morning.
What does it mean?
It's my Chinese name.
Why you guys hiding out
from everyone?
Hey.
Hey. Hello.
Yo, D-Rock!
Is that a new tattoo?
Yeah.
You gonna show me?
Later.
When did you get it?
This morning.
You all right?
Hey, Steph.
What up, man?
Hi.
What up, dude?
So this is where
the Asians hang out.
Yup. Library was closed.
Hey, you're a funny guy.
For an Oriental.
He's been drinking.
Hey, Daric, where you going
to go to college
next year, man?
I just turned in
my apps last month.
What about you?
Ah, it'll be
an Ivy League for sure.
I don't know which yet.
You already got in?
Yeah, of course.
You'll have to excuse Steve.
He gets cocky when he's drunk.
Only when he's drunk?
Excuse me, guys.
Too much testosterone.
Did I say something?
So, this is like
the "I love Stephanie" fan club.
You know, Daric,
you're a pretty cool guy.
I can't believe Steph thought
you were a stalker or something.
Yo, what'd you think
of her friend?
What friend?
The one she brought
to mini golf.
All right.
Yeah. Isn't Steph the best?
You want a drink?
Yeah,
whatever you get.
All right.
Ben?
I'm good.
Thanks, D-Rock.
Anytime, Stevie-boy.
Why you hang out
with him, Ben?
He's got something up his ass
all the time.
He's all right.
Yo... Steph's the one.
Steph's the one.
You were right.
She deserves to be treated better.
I'm going
to treat her better.
I owe it all to you, man.
Thank you.
Steve, you're wasted.
Thanks, man.
Okay. You're welcome.
You're welcome.
All right.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
All right.
Thank you.
At that point,
by the look in Daric's eyes,
I knew it was on.
It was New Year's Eve.
Jesus said we could use
his house
if we paid him a hundred bucks.
His parents had left for Tahoe
a day earlier.
I still thought it was
a bad idea,
so the guys and I
made a compromise.
All I had to do
was be the lookout.
Hey.
They're right around back
in the garage.
I'll be in there in a sec.
Fuck!
What's up, fellas?
So you got the cash?
Of course.
Got my gun?
This...
is your wake-up call.
For your mommy and daddy.
Fuck!
Get the gun!
Han, get the gun!
Shit!
Oh, God.
Fuck!
Don't!
Ben.
Ben!
What the fuck?
We didn't agree to this.
This is going to cost you extra.
We're going to have to get rid
of the body.
What do you mean?
Jesus, what about
your backyard?
No way.
I promise no one
will ever know.
$300.
Come on, guys, dish it up.
Shit!
You guys got any money?
Virg?
Here. 150.
I'll get you the rest tomorrow,
all right?
Fuck no.
You pay me now.
Here, three hundred.
Can I have
the wallet too?
Fuck!
Oh, shit.
He's still alive.
Someone hold him up.
Virg, please, hold him up.
It's going to be okay, Ben.
It's going to be just fine.
Oh, fuck.
You got him, Virg?
Yeah.
All right.
Hold him up.
Hold his head up.
Hold it up. Tilt
it back, okay?
Okay.
Let me open his mouth.
All right.
It's going to be fine, Ben.
It's going to be just fine.
Oh, shit.
Just hold him down.
Christ!
Virg, it's okay.
Listen to me.
Just hang on, okay?
It'll be just fine.
Just hang on!
Just hang on to him!
Whatever you do!
I'm holding him!
Jesus fucking Christ!
Just hang on!
Whatever you do,
just hang on!
It's okay.
It'll be okay.
It'll be okay, Virg.
Okay, Virgil, just
a few more seconds.
Just breathe.
Just hang on!
Hang on.
Are you all right, Ben?
It's okay, man.
Shh. Shh.
Ben.
Hey, Stephanie.
Hi.
Happy New Year.
Are you okay?
I'm just mad at Steve.
For what?
He totally stood me up.
I know he hates these things,
but still...
All right, everybody!
Let's get crazy!
It's almost New Year!
Ten...
Ten, nine, eight...
I guess neither of us
are getting a kiss tonight, huh?
...five, four, three, two,
one!
I-I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to...
No.
Don't apologize.
I need to talk to Steve.
Uh, well, uh, guys are waiting.
Thanks, Ben.
Happy New Year.
Aw, shit.
Ben, will you take him
out of here?
Aw, fuck!
Fuck, man!
Get the fuck out
of here.
Jesus, would you help us, please?
Fuck it.
Ah, Jesus.
You clean that shit up, man.
God damn, it's hot.
Are you done yet?
Early admissions?
Ivy Leaguers love it.
Gets 'em all wet.
All that studying
finally pays off,
and you get to leave
this hellhole a year early.
Damn, what is it,
like 95 degrees?
Can't wait to go
to college, man.
It's like natural selection.
Every hot chick
you meet's got a brain.
Not mine.
You never forget
the sight of a dead body
but then again,
I was experiencing
a lot of things
for the first time.
I guess it's just
part of growing up.
I knew what I had to do.
Of course,
the right thing to do
was to call the police
and tell them everything.
It was right...
but it didn't mean it was easy.
Yo, Virg, I'm here.
Let's go, man.
Stop jerking off; let's go.
Yo, Virg,
stop fucking around, man.
Open the door.
Virg!
Open the fucking door, man!
I said open the door!
Virg! Open
the fucking door, Virg!
Virg! Virg!
Han said Virgil
had called him over
to watch some new porn.
I guess Virg just didn't have
enough balls to do it alone.
Open the fucking
door, Virg! Virg!
Fuck you, Virg!
Open this fucking door!
So... what,
is he going to be retarded,
or something?
Ben, get him the
fuck out of here
before I kick his ass.
Come on, Daric.
Come on.
Wait, Ben, you think Virg
is going to talk?
No. What if he does?
Dude, what
are we going to do?
Nothing.
Okay. Let me think.
Why did you write
that article about me?
What?
The newspaper article.
Why did you write it?
What are you talking
about, man?
I'm trying to
fucking think here.
Wait.
Do you think Han
will be with us?
Later, Daric.
Ben... I'll call you later.
Nice.
You haven't seen
Steve, have you?
Steve?
Get in.
He's been gone
for a couple days,
and he's got everyone worried.
Are you worried?
Yeah, but you just never know
what Steve's up to.
Ben, thanks for putting
up with this.
What?
The whole thing
with me and Steve.
You know how you make decisions
that lead to other decisions?
Yeah.
Then you realize
you don't remember
why you made those decisions
in the first place.
Yeah.
When I saw you
on New Year's Eve,
I knew there was only one
right thing to do.
For the first time in my life,
I don't know
what my future will hold.
I don't even know what
the other guys are going to do.
All I know is that
there's no turning back.
Just packed up a real money load,
and it's coming your way.
Look for "Rodgers" on the truck's side.
Don't forget my share of the deal.
Shit!
- Tuna on white, no crust, right?
- I don't know. How is it?
Every day, for the last three weeks,
you've come here, asking how the tuna is.
Now, it was crappy yesterday.
It was crappy the day before.
And guess what? It hasn't changed.
- I'll have the tuna.
- No crust?
No crust.
Thank you.
Talk to me, Jesse.
This ain't working, brother.
It's your fuel map. It's got a nasty hole.
- That's why you're unloading in third.
- Told you.
I lengthen the injector pulse a millisecond.
Just tune the NOS timer, you'll run nines.
What's up with this fool?
Is he sandwich-crazy?
- No. He ain't here for the food, dog.
- Chill out. He's slinging parts for Harry.
- I know what he's slinging.
- He's trying to get in Mia's pants, dog.
- What's up, guys?
- How you doing, Mia?
- How you living, girl?
- Hey!
Hey, Dom. You want something to drink?
- He's beautiful.
- I like his haircut.
Vince!
- What?
- Can I get you anything?
You look good.
- Thanks a lot, Mia. See you tomorrow.
- Sure.
- Tomorrow?
- I love this part.
Try Fatburger from now on. Get yourself a
Double Cheese with fries for $2.95, faggot.
- I like the tuna here.
- Bullshit. No one likes the tuna here.
Yeah, well, I do.
Jesus Christ, Dom! Would you get out
there? I'm sick of this shit.
I'm not kidding, Dom. Get out there!
- What did you put in that sandwich?
- That's funny.
- Dom!
- All right.
- Hey, man. He was in my face.
- I'm in your face.
Relax! Don't push it! You embarrass me!
Get over there!
Jesse, give me the wallet.
"Brian Earl Spilner."
Sounds like a serial killer name.
- Is that what you are?
- No, man.
Don't come around here again.
Hey, man. This is bullshit.
- You work for Harry, right?
- Yeah. I just started.
You were just fired.
Hey, Dominic.
I appreciate what you did, in a big way.
Dominic, I owe you.
Brian, you're messing with my business.
When Dominic drives, he's golden.
Kids pour in. They want everything he has.
Every performance part. They pay cash!
- What did Dominic say?
- You don't want to know.
- He wants you out of here.
- He wants me out of here?
- Yes.
- And what did you say to Dom?
- What do you think I said?
I told him, "Good help is hard to find."
Relax.
I need NOS.
- I need NOS.
- No.
My car topped out at 140 miles per hour,
this morning.
Amateurs don't use nitrous oxide. I've
seen how you drive. You've a heavy foot.
- You'll blow yourself to pieces.
- I need one of these.
One of the big ones.
Actually, let's make it two.
And, Harry, I need it by tonight.
Hold up, hold up.
Look at this snowman right here, man.
Sweet ride.
What you running under there, man?
- Going to make me find out the hard way?
- Hell, yeah.
You brave. You brave.
They call me Hector.
I got a last name, too,
but I can't pronounce it.
- Brian Spilner.
- Typical white-boy name.
Know what I'm saying?
See that over there? That's mine.
My baby. I ain't cutting her loose tonight.
- Why not?
- I'm going legit, homey.
Trying to get on the NIRA circuit.
Heard about that?
- Hell, yeah.
- So, what's up with you, man?
- I'm just waiting for Toretto.
- Shit. Better get in line. This yours?
- I'm standing next to it.
- That's funny.
You know,
Edwin happens to know a few things.
And one of the things Edwin knows is:
It's not how you stand by your car...
...it's how you race your car.
You better learn that.
Oh, shit. Here they come. It's on.
- Dom.
- Marvin.
- Hey, Dom. How you doing?
- Hey, Camille. You been doing yoga?
You did? Of course you did. Monica.
I smell skanks.
Why don't you girls pack it up,
before I leave tread marks on your face?
Okay.
- Letty, I was just talking.
- Yeah. Whatever.
- Okay, Hector.
- Yeah? What's up, man?
- Yo. What's up?
- Edwin.
- How we doing this tonight?
- One race.
$2,000 buy-in. Winner takes all.
Hector, you're going to hold the cash.
- Why Hector?
- Too slow to make away with the money.
- Okay. Good luck, guys.
- Hey, wait. Hold up.
I don't have any cash.
But I do have the pink slip to my car.
You just can't climb in the ring with Ali,
'cause you think you box.
He knows I can box. Check it out.
It's like this.
I lose, the winner takes my car.
Clean and clear.
But if I win, I take the cash,
and I take the respect.
Respect.
To some people, that's more important.
That your car?
I see a cool air intake. It's got a NOS
fogger system and a T 4 turbo, Dominic.
I see an AIC controller.
It has direct port nitrous injection.
Yeah. And a stand-alone
fuel management system.
Not a bad way to spend $10,000.
You see that shit?
He's got enough NOS in there
to blow himself up. Period.
- So, what do you say? Am I worthy?
- We don't know yet.
But you're in. Let's go.
- All right.
- Let's go!
- What the hell is going on around here?
- Street's closed, pizza boy.
- Find another way home.
- Goddamn street racers.
Log on, 22. Code 3. Tension is high.
They've blocked the street.
Edwin.
This is yours, whether you win or lose.
But if you win, you get her, too.
You're going to win.
I'm going to win.
We had a reported homicide.
187, at Barabian Liquors.
I've got a 187 in Glendale.
Cops are all over it. We're good to roll.
- All right.
- Let's race!
Right.
Go!
Hell, yeah!
Damn, that guy's fast.
Let's go! Ménage!
No! Monica!
Shut up!
Well done, baby!
Come on. Come on. Back up.
Here's what you won, right here.
There you go.
You were racing a bunch of skateboards.
Know what I mean?
My sister holds the money. Count it.
And you're my trophy.
- Hey, Monica. What's up, baby?
- What's your problem? You didn't win.
Fuck you then!
Was that fun?
Got a problem there, buddy?
- What are you smiling about?
- Dude. I almost had you.
You almost had me?
You never had me.
You never had your car.
Granny-shifting.
Not double-clutching, like you should.
You're lucky that 100-shot of NOS
didn't blow the welds on the intake.
- Almost had me?
- You tell him, Dominic. Get out of here.
Now, me and the mad scientist
got to rip apart the block...
...and replace the piston rings you fried.
Ask any racer. Any real racer.
It don't matter if you win by an inch
or a mile. Winning's winning.
Yeah!
All available units,
we have street-racing along Hawthorne....
Oh, shit! We got cops. Cops!
Go!
Cops! Get in the car! Go!
Toretto, stop right there!
Toretto!
Get in!
You're the last person in the world
I expected to show up.
I thought if I got in your good graces,
you might let me keep my car.
You are in my good graces,
but you ain't keeping your car.
You drive like you've done this before.
Are you a wheelman?
- No.
- You boost cars?
- No. Never.
- Ever done time?
Couple of overnighters. No big deal.
What about the two years
in juvie for boosting cars?
Tucson, right?
I had Jesse run a profile on you,
Brian Earl Spilner.
He'll find anything on the Web.
Anything about anybody.
So, why bullshit?
So, what about you?
Two years in Lompoc.
I'll die before I go back.
- Oh, great.
- What?
It's going to be a long-ass night.
That's what.
Follow us.
I thought we had an agreement.
You stay away. I stay away.
Everybody stays happy.
We got lost.
What do you want me to tell you?
- Who's "we?"
- My new mechanic.
Brian, meet Johnny Tran.
The guy in the snakeskin pants.
That's his cousin. Lance.
So, when are you going to give me a shot
at that Honda 2000 of yours?
- This your ride?
- It was. It's his now.
No, it's not. I haven't taken delivery.
Then, it's nobody's car.
But somebody put in the wrench time.
- What do you think, Lance?
- It's an amazing machine.
Yes, indeed.
Let's go.
I'll see you in the desert next month.
Be ready to have your ass handed to you.
- You'll need more than that crotch rocket.
- I got something for you.
- What the hell was that all about?
- Long story. I'll tell you later.
Let's get out of here.
NOS!
- So, what the hell was that all about?
- It's a long story.
Well, we got a 20-mile hike. Humor me.
A business deal that went sour.
Plus, I made the mistake
of sleeping with his sister.
Take care.
Yo, Spilner.
- You want a beer?
- Yeah, sure.
Oh, shit.
We were all there, right? Falling behind.
- With all that nitrous.
- Yeah.
Yo, Dom. We were just about to go
looking for you, brother.
Where were you?
There were mass cops there. They came in
from every direction. It was orchestrated.
- This your beer?
- Yeah, that's my beer.
Yo, Einstein. Take it upstairs.
You can't detail a car with the cover on.
- Can't even get that right.
- You all right?
- Am I all right?
- It was just a question.
Yo, Dom.
- Why did you bring the buster here?
- 'Cause he kept me out of handcuffs!
He didn't just run back to the fort!
The buster brought me back.
You can have any brew you want,
as long as it's a Corona.
- Thanks, man.
- That's Vince's. So, enjoy it.
You.
- Hey, bro. You got a bathroom?
- Upstairs. First door on the right.
He's got no call being up in here.
You don't know that fool for shit.
- He's right, Dom.
- There was a time when I didn't know you.
That was in the third grade!
- Yeah. So, what girls are here?
- You name it. You want mine?
- You need to shut the....
- You want two?
- You don't have anything?
- You look a bit tired.
I think you should go upstairs
and give me a massage.
- Look at all our guests.
- How about you give me a massage?
Crazy lady.
You know you owe me
a 10-second car, right?
Oh, shit.
Did you wipe the seat?
Jesus Christ! Would you cut this shit?
Come on!
- Come on. Let's go get me a drink.
- We were just about to get along.
- So, what do you want?
- Anything, as long as it's cold.
You know, my brother likes you.
He usually doesn't like anybody.
- He's a complicated guy.
- Yeah? What about you?
- I'm simpler.
- You're a shitty liar.
Well, I'll take that as a compliment.
- But there's a problem.
- What's that?
You need to get some sleep.
And you definitely,
definitely need a shower.
Come on. I'll take you home.
Show me your hands.
Very good. Now open the door.
Put your hands on your head.
Behind your head.
Face the front of the vehicle,
walk backwards towards the rear.
Take two steps to your right.
Stop right there.
- What did I do?
- Shut up. He's clean, Sarge.
Damn!
Muse, will you take these things off?
- Shit. You put them on so tight.
- I like realism.
You never know who's watching, Brian.
Nice crib, Sergeant. It's a lot nicer
than the last place you confiscated.
Ain't it? Eddie Fisher built this house
for Elizabeth Taylor in the '50s.
You see, even the cops
are Hollywood in Hollywood.
Okay, here he is,
fresh from Toretto's hot rod heaven.
That was an $80,000 vehicle, Officer.
- You told him what happened?
- He knows.
- Send the bill to Johnny Tran.
- The kid's giving me attitude?
It doesn't speak well
for police/FBI relations, Tanner.
- I walk in the door and the guy's already--
- All right, all right.
We'll talk, okay? Let's talk about it.
Muse, why don't you make us
four iced cappuccinos, please?
- Come on.
- Regular or decaf, Sarge?
Decaf, I think.
Four hijackings in two months,
and we have nothing.
The DVD players and digital cameras
are worth $1.2 million...
...which brings the grand total
to $6 million plus.
We're in the political crosshairs now, Brian.
That's why you're undercover.
You want that detective badge fast, kid.
And you want to know something?
The FBI can help,
if you come through for us.
What does the truckdriver say?
He gave us the same M.O.:
Three Honda Civics, precision driving...
...the same green neon glow
from under the chassis.
Lab says the skid marks came back
the same: Mashimoto ZX tires.
So, we know it's somebody
in the street-racing world.
If we don't make this case, the truckers
will take matters into their own hands.
I tell them we're close.
Are you going to make me a liar?
Look, what do we know?
We know this world
revolves around Toretto, right?
I'm not saying that he's the one
that's popping these trucks...
...but I can guarantee he knows who is.
It's just a matter of time until I win--
You want time, buy the magazine.
We don't have time.
Just get me something I can use.
Is Harry cooperating?
Like a guy that'll do time
for receiving stolen property if he doesn't.
What kind of vibe
is he getting from Toretto?
He's scared of him,
but he doesn't think he's jacking trucks.
- He's too controlled for that.
- Wait.
Not that I want to contradict
Harry's fine judge of character...
...but Toretto did hard time
for nearly beating a guy to death.
He's got nitrous oxide in his blood
and a gas tank for a brain.
Do not turn your back on him.
Tanner, I'm gonna need another car.
- What about parts and service?
- Hold off on it.
Dom, I don't know what to do with it.
All right, what the hell is this?
What do you got there?
- This is your car.
- My car?
I said a 10-second car, not a 10-minute car.
You could push this across the finish line,
or tow it.
You couldn't even tow that
across the finish line.
No faith.
I have faith in you,
but this isn't a junkyard.
- This is a garage.
- Pop the hood.
- Pop the hood?
- 2JZ engine. No shit.
- And what did I tell you?
- I retract my previous statement.
- You know what?
This will decimate all
after you put about $15,000 in it.
Or more,
if we have to overnight parts from Japan.
- We'll put it on my tab at Harry's.
- Yes!
I gotta get you racing again
so I can make some money off your ass.
There's a show down in the desert
called Race Wars.
That's where you'll do it.
When you're not working at Harry's,
you're working here.
If you can't find the right tool
in this garage, Mr. Arizona...
...you don't belong near a car.
He owns you now.
Tell me what you think about this.
Koni adjustables.
Gonna save us about 2 pounds.
And they're gonna give us
better traction for the hole shot.
All right?
This is your basic layout of the car.
And that's pretty much
what it could look like when it's finished.
Red, green.
- You should be going to MIT or something.
- Yeah, right.
No, I got that.... What's it called?
That attention disorder--
- ADD?
- Yes, that shit. Yeah.
You know, I was good in algebra
and like math and shit.
Everything else I failed.
Dropped out of school.
I don't know.
It's just something about engines...
...that calms me down, you know.
- I'm outta here.
- Come on, dog.
- Yo, Dom.
- Vince, get over here and give us a hand.
Looks like you got
all the help you need, brother.
- Mia! The chicken's dry.
- All right. I'm coming out already.
Here you go.
Hey, hold up.
Because you were the first to reach in
to get the chicken, you say grace.
- Dear heavenly....
- Spirit.
Spirit. Thank you.
Thank you for providing us
with a direct port nitrous injection...
...four core intercoolers
and ball-bearing turbos...
...and titanium valve springs.
- Thank you.
- Amen.
- Not bad.
He was praying to the car gods, man.
He's not the best.
- What do you want?
- Practice.
Thank you, girl.
Look who it is. "Old Coyotes 'R' Us."
I thought you weren't hungry, pumpkin.
- You know, I gotta eat.
- He's always hungry.
All right, sit down.
How you doing, Mia?
Here you go.
- Jesse, hand me that chicken.
- Let's eat some grub, man.
- Want some of that chicken?
- What, you rent a movie or something?
Need a hand with anything else?
No, I'm good. You can go join the boys
and watch the movie.
- The cook doesn't clean where I come from.
- I'd like to go there.
- I think we should go out sometime.
- No, I don't date my brother's friends.
That sucks.
- I'll have to kick his ass then.
- I'd love to see that one.
I would pay to see that one, actually.
Wash my car when you get done.
- What was that?
- No, Mia. I'm talking to the punk.
Wear your favorite dress,
'cause when you're done...
...I'm putting you on the street
where you belong, cutie.
Is this thing broken?
What's wrong with this thing?
What was that Cuban restaurant
you wanted to take me to?
The one with the picadillo and--
- With red candles, wooden tables--
- The plantain, food all over the place.
- What it's called?
- Cha Cha Cha.
- Yeah, that's it.
- Yeah.
Well, you can take me there.
Friday night at 10:00. Is that good for you?
- Yeah, it's perfect.
- Good.
- There's no popcorn.
- Make your own goddamn popcorn!
All right. Now that's valet parking.
- Harry. What's up, dog?
- Nice to see you.
Excellent. Come on in, man.
- Check it. It's yours.
- Damn. What do we got here?
- Hired some new help?
- Don't even think about it.
- What's up?
- What's up, Brian? How you feeling?
- Pretty good. What do you need?
- What's up, man?
I need you to hook me up.
Three of everything. I made a list.
Why don't you look that over?
- When do you need this stuff by?
- Tomorrow, today, now.
- Right.
- White boys work fast, don't they?
That's right.
- You said you need three of each?
- Yeah, three of everything.
What do you think about that?
Check this out.
He moans like a cop.
Brian, this is one of those times
you need to be clear about what you say.
Nod if you understand me.
Nod!
Sit up.
Tell me what the hell you're doing
down here.
Shit. What I'm doing?
Dom.
I owe you a 10-second car.
And what this is about,
this is about Race Wars.
I just went in there,
and Hector is gonna be running...
...three Honda Civics with Spoon engines.
And on top of that,
he just came into Harry's...
...and he ordered three T66 turbos,
with NOS...
...and a MoTeC system exhaust.
So, what are you saying?
You're gonna check everybody's shit out,
one garage after another?
Yeah.
Because, Dom, you know I can't lose again.
He's a cop.
He's a cop!
You a cop?
Let's go for a little ride.
Walk!
Okay. You stand watch.
Yo, Dominic.
There's no engines.
What are they planning on racing with,
hopes and dreams?
I don't know, but they're sneaky as shit...
...and they've got enough money
to buy anything.
What?
We got a wolf pack.
It's Johnny Tran,
and he's coming your way really fast.
All right, we got company. Spilner.
Come on. Move!
Let me ask you a question, Ted.
- Do you see anything wrong here?
- No.
- We got no engines, do we?
- Do we?
- No.
A couple of Nissan SR20 motors
will pull a premium...
- ...one week before Race Wars, huh?
- Yeah, probably.
You're a smart fence, Ted.
Maybe too smart.
What are you feeling, Lance?
40-weight?
50-weight?
A 40-weight sounds nice.
Where are they, Ted?
- Where are they?
- Enough!
- They're in a warehouse.
They're in a warehouse, man!
Ted.
Kiss my shoes?
Let's go get our engines.
My superiors are flying in from D.C.,
in two days.
I want something to show.
We've got a fence
with a lube hose in his mouth...
...automatic weapons,
priors on every one of these Asian punks...
...a garage full of DVD players
and generally psychotic behavior.
Tell me why we shouldn't move
on Tran now and figure it out later?
Because all we have is behavior.
Let me get hard evidence,
because what we have now is just--
What we have is probable cause.
And truckers arming themselves for some
good old-fashioned vigilante mayhem.
- Tell us about Hector, Brian.
- Latinos with spear guns. Give me a break.
Hector's still working on the engines,
but the tires don't match.
Will somebody give me a cigarette?
- Get him a cigarette.
- Don't give him one.
- I thought you quit.
- I did. Just give me one.
- Get him a cigarette.
- No!
Tell me about Toretto.
I told you,
I think he's too controlled for this.
Going suicidal on semi-trucks? No way.
Maybe Vince. But he's too dumb to do it.
- I think the kid sister's blurring your vision.
- What did you say?
I don't blame you.
I'd get off on her surveillance photos, too.
Knock it off!
What? Are you going native on me, Brian?
Have you read Toretto's file lately?
- Yeah. I memorized that file.
- Read it again.
No, better still, take a look at these.
Remember I told you about the guy
he nearly beat to death?
Toretto did this
with a three-quarter-inch torque wrench.
He's a model of self-control.
I need a few more days.
Got a TR7 here,
with a ball-bearing upgrade.
What it's going to do is,
it's going to spool up really quick.
- I got this set up for 24 psi.
- Got it.
You got big plans tonight?
Yeah. We're going out to dinner.
You break her heart, I'll break your neck.
That's not gonna happen.
I want to show you something.
Me and my dad built her.
Nine hundred horses of Detroit muscle.
It's a beast.
- You know what she ran in Palmdale?
- No. What?
Nine seconds flat.
- God.
- My dad was driving.
So much torque,
the chassis twisted coming off the line.
Barely kept her on the track.
- So, what's your best time?
- I've never driven her.
Why not?
It scares the shit out of me.
That's my dad.
He was coming up
in the pro stock-car circuit.
Last race of the season.
A guy named Kenny Linder
came up from inside, in the final turn.
He clipped his bumper
and put him into the wall at 120.
I watched my dad burn to death.
I remembered hearing him scream.
But the people that were there
said he had died before the tanks blew.
They said it was me who was screaming.
I saw Linder about a week later.
I had a wrench, and I hit him.
And I didn't intend to keep hitting him,
but when I finished, I couldn't lift my arm.
He's a janitor at a high school.
He has to take the bus to work every day.
And they banned me
from the tracks for life.
I live my life a quarter-mile at a time.
Nothing else matters.
Not the mortgage, not the store...
...not my team and all their bullshit.
For those 10 seconds or less...
...I'm free.
So, how is it, anyways,
that the gang came to be?
- What?
- The gang.
The gang?
No, they don't call themselves a gang.
- What do they call themselves?
- They're a team.
- They call themselves a team.
- All right. How did the team come to be?
Well, that's a whole lot of history.
- I've got time.
- Okay. Vince grew up with my brother.
Actually, he didn't ever actually grow up,
as you can tell.
But they were friends as kids.
And Letty, she just lived down the street.
Always into cars, though.
Ever since she was, like, 10 years old.
So, naturally, you know,
my brother always had her attention.
- And then she turned 16--
- And then she had Dom's attention.
Yeah. It's funny how that works, isn't it?
Yeah.
How does Jesse fit into the whole thing?
Jesse. Well, Jesse and Leon just sort of
showed up one night and never, ever left.
It's just the way my brother is, you know.
Dom's like....
He's like gravity.
Everything just gets pulled to him.
Even you.
No.
The only thing that pulled me in was you.
Being friends with your brother
is just a bonus.
That's good.
That's good. It's nice to come first
every once in a while.
Want to go for a drive?
- Yeah?
- The hijackers have hit again.
Bilkins has decided that we're gonna move
on Johnny Tran and his guys at 17:00.
Unless you say otherwise.
If you agree, just say yes.
- Yeah.
- Who is that?
It's just a wrong number.
Yes, sir. Yeah, I know, but--
Yeah. Yes, sir.
Yeah. I got it.
The DVD players were purchased legally.
All we've got are a couple
of low-rent weapons charges...
...and some outstanding speeding tickets.
- So, they're out.
- Yeah.
Father bailed them out.
Is this the kind of intelligence
I can expect from you, O'Conner?
- You're gonna put this on me?
- I can put it on whoever I want to.
- Perks of the job.
- No, you can't put this on me--
No, wait a minute. Let me tell you.
I don't care if you have to aim at someone
and blow your cover to smithereens.
You've got 36 hours to crack this bastard...
...or you might want to think
about another career.
It's Toretto, Brian.
It always has been Toretto.
Tran and Hector are....
They're just fumes.
I know you've been lying to me.
My question is this:
Have you been lying to yourself
because you can't see past Mia?
He won't go back to prison.
Well, that's a choice
he's going to have to make.
There's all kinds of family, Brian.
And that's a choice
you're gonna have to make.
You ready for this?
Nice car.
What's the retail on one of those?
More than you can afford, pal. Ferrari.
Smoke him.
So, what's wrong, Brian?
Nothing, man, I'm fine.
Come on. Obviously something's off.
Look, I have my good days and bad days
just like anybody else.
Brian, don't lose that cool of yours.
That's your meal ticket.
My meal ticket?
I can't pay for my own shrimp?
I got the shrimp.
No, that's one thing about me
you don't understand.
I don't take handouts.
I earn my way, every step.
I need something extra on the side,
like you.
What do you mean, like me?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- That's what I mean.
- What does that mean, like me?
- Don't try--
I'm not stupid, all right?
I know that there's no way you paid
for all that shit you got under the hood--
There's no way you paid for
what's under the hood of those cars...
...by doing tune-ups and selling groceries.
Whatever it is you're in on,
I want in on it, too.
- Well, what is this?
- Read it.
- What is this for?
- It's directions.
To Race Wars.
We'll see how you go.
Then we'll talk.
- How's it going?
- What's up?
- Welcome to Race Wars.
- Great. Thanks a lot.
Baby. Hey, baby.
You should watch from the side.
I wouldn't want to get exhaust
on that pretty face.
- Put your money where your mouth is.
- I'll race you for that sweet little ass.
You want ass,
why don't you hit Hollywood Boulevard?
You want an adrenaline rush,
it'll be two large.
Right here. Right now.
What's it gonna be?
You got it.
"Another one bites the dust"
Come on. What you got?
See ya.
- What's up?
- Hey, what's up, Jesse?
What's in your hand?
Throwing down the pink slip, just like you.
- The pink slip to what? The Jetta?
- Yeah.
- You can't bet your dad's car.
- It's all right.
I ain't losing.
This fool is running a Honda 2000.
I'll win.
That way, me and my dad can roll
when he gets out of prison. It's all good.
They're gonna throw him right back
in prison after he kills you.
You visualize the win.
Visualize the win, Jesse. I'm serious.
You got to listen to me, man.
Who are you racing?
Jesse, don't do it.
I bet you he's got more than $100,000
under the hood of that car.
Too soon, junior.
No!
Shit!
Oh, God!
Yo! Heads up, bro. We got problems.
- What?
- Jesse.
Where's Jesse going?
- He just raced Tran for slips.
- Oh, shit.
- Where's he going?
- He went to the car wash.
Whatever. Go fetch my car.
Go fetch your car?
We're not on your block.
You better watch who you talk to like that.
Toretto!
SWAT came into my house...
...disrespected my whole family,
because somebody narced me out.
And you know what? It was you!
Get off of him, man.
Dom, chill out, man. Come on!
I never narced on nobody!
Mia.
I have respected you
and I haven't said shit.
Now I am asking you not to go.
- I'm doing this for both of us.
- Don't give me that crap.
You're doing this for you.
Why are you insisting on doing this?
Dom, please, just don't.
- Mia, what's going on?
- What?
- You know what I'm talking about.
- No, I don't.
You always have tears in your eyes
when Dom drives away?
What's the matter with you?
What's he racing off
in the middle of the night for?
- You know about the trucks?
- No, Brian! What trucks?
- Jesus Christ. What?
- Listen to me.
Mia, I'm a cop.
What are you talking about, Brian?
What is this?
Ever since the first time I met you,
I've been undercover.
I'm a cop.
Oh, you bastard.
You bastard.
- Mia.
- Get off of me, Brian!
Mia! Listen to me!
Everything I ever said
I felt about you was real.
I swear to God.
You have to believe me, Mia.
But this isn't about you and me.
Your brother's out there to pull a job.
We're running out of time. Those truckers
aren't laying down anymore.
Maybe they'll make it through tonight,
but every law enforcement agency...
...is coming down on them.
If you don't want anything to happen
to them...
...you have to get in that car
with me right now and help me.
Mia, you are the only person
that can help me right now.
Please, Mia. Please help me.
Civics are stashed somewhere
outside of Thermal.
They wouldn't double back,
and Highway 10 is too well patrolled.
- So, what does that leave us with?
- All this.
- Nextel.
- This is Officer Brian O'Conner.
Serial number 34762.
I need a cell phone trace.
- Okay. What's the cell number?
- Mia, what is it?
Come on, Mia.
She needs Dom's cell phone number now.
323-555-6439.
Thank you. Yeah, you get that?
All right, we're one man short.
Letty, I need you on the left side.
Your sister's right about this one.
This don't feel good.
- Don't do that.
- Something's wrong.
- Stop.
- We shouldn't be doing this without Jesse.
This is the mother Iode.
We've been on this for three months.
After this, it's a long vacation for everyone.
- Let's go.
- I hope so.
Listen, the other night I had a dream...
...that you and I were
on the beach in Mexico.
- Really?
- Really.
Come on. Let's make this happen.
- Leon, keep on those scanners.
- Copy that.
All right, let's go.
Okay, we traced the number
to the northbound 86.
Mile 114, outside Coachella.
We'll keep the trace open, Officer.
Let me see this.
I think we're about 40 miles away.
What are you gonna do?
Okay! Go time!
We're all good.
I got nothing on the scanners.
Keep going.
Vince!
Vince, don't! Get back in!
He's got a damn shotgun! Leon!
Back off! Get him off of there!
Oh, shit!
Get me off this thing! Pull up!
Unhook yourself. Do it!
- Do it!
- I can't get--
You can do it!
Come on, Vince!
Dom! I'm pulling up to distract him!
Come on, boy!
Shot doesn't get better than this.
Son of a bitch!
Take me off here,
or I'll have to unhook the wire!
Try it again. One, two, three!
Unhook yourself!
I can't get my arm free!
- Vince, grab my hand!
- My arm!
Listen, give me your hand.
I'm gonna pull you off the rig!
Vince!
Hold on!
Give me your hand! Listen to me!
Dominic!
Shit!
- Dominic!
- Hang on!
Dom! Move out of the way.
I'm coming to get him.
Letty!
Leon!
Pull back for Letty.
Get her out of there!
I'm on it! Go!
I've got her! You get Vince off that truck.
Letty! Come on, baby.
You okay?
Oh, shit. Come on, girl, you all right?
Come on, let me look at you.
Come on. We got to go. Let's go.
Vince!
Take the wheel.
- What do you mean?
- Put your foot on the gas!
I'm gonna get him.
Put your foot on the gas!
Okay!
- Come on. Keep it steady.
- I got it!
All right, hold on, Vince.
He's having a hard time holding on.
Get me a little closer.
All right.
- Closer.
- I'm moving in.
Hold it right there!
Go!
You got to hang in here with me now!
We'll get you off. Give me your arm!
Vince, look at me! Don't let go!
Come on, Vince!
Throw this arm around me!
Vince, don't let go!
Come on, Mia. Get closer!
Mia, get closer! Come on.
Come on, Vince. Here we go!
Shit.
It's gonna be okay, Letty. I love you.
- Watch her.
- I got her.
Come on, Vince! Hang in there! Come on!
If he doesn't get to an ambulance
in 10 minutes, he's dead.
- Hold the pressure. Hold his arm up.
- I got it.
Yeah. Yeah, this is Officer Brian O'Conner.
I'm off-duty MAPD.
I need a life flight roll out right away.
My 20 is Highway 86, mile marker 147.
I got one trauma victim,
about 24 years of age.
Six-foot, maybe 200 pounds.
He's got a deep laceration to his right arm
with arterial bleeding.
And he's got a shotgun wound
close range to his left flank.
Yeah, he's going into shock!
Dom, put the gun down now!
- Move your car.
- No bullshit!
Put it down now! No more running!
I'm not running!
- Where's Leon and Letty?
- They're long gone!
Then it's over.
I didn't call the police, but don't push me!
- Put the gun down. I swear to God!
- You are the cop!
You're a cop!
Brian, I got to find Jesse before they do.
- I'm all the kid's got.
- I'll call in the plates.
PD will pick him up way before
Johnny even gets near him.
- Move your car.
- Dom, stop it! It's over. Please.
Mia, stay out of it!
Dominic, I am so sorry.
I don't know what I'm doing, Dom.
I'm so scared right now.
I don't know what's going on.
What were you thinking, man?
I don't know! I panicked! I'm sorry.
I'm scared!
I don't know what I'm doing!
Will you please help me?
Dom!
Jesse!
No, Jesse!
No, Dom, no!
Call 911. You call 911!
I used to drag here back in high school.
That railroad crossing up there
is exactly a quarter mile away from here.
On green, I'm going for it.
That's not what I had in mind.
You know what you're doing?
I owe you a 10-second car.
I live my life a quarter-mile at a time.
Nothing else matters.
For those 10 seconds or less...
...I'm free.
Yo, Jimmy, man. Give me the status.
Tell me we good.
- You got it, man.
- Beautiful.
It's gonna be an all-timer tonight.
All right, fire them up!
We go live in five!
It's time for ignition
and straight automobile pimping.
- Girl!
- Sorry! My bad!
All right, ladies! We're good.
We're good.
That's it, babies.
Come on, Tej!
Let's get this race going!
Wait a second, man.
You cats are first wave.
Where's your fourth at?
It was Joaquin, but he had
to work the graveyard shift.
What? Graveyard shift, man.
- Why don't you run with us, Tej?
- Hell, I'm not running with y'all.
I tell you, either you find a fourth
or you don't race. How about that?
We should find two, so we don't have
to roll with skirt here.
Whoa, wait a second.
Why don't I find you a fourth
and we settle this on the streets?
- Bring him on.
- Anybody I want?
No matter who it is?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, man. You want to race tonight?
I could use the money.
You got four minutes.
I'll be there.
The race starts in four minutes.
All right, girls, let's do this.
- You think you'll win, baby?
- What do you think?
- You better. We got rent to pay.
- I know this.
I'll get you when you
get a car worth racing.
There's our fourth.
Shit. It's Brian.
- What's up, Tej?
- What's happening, dude?
- Thanks for the invite.
- No problem at all, man.
Just remember me
when you wax, all right?
They got deep pockets?
Real deep.
- What's up, Suki?
- What's up, Bullitt?
What do you say we kick it a nickel?
Nobody mentioned raising stakes.
If that's the case,
ask these nice people...
to back off the line
so you can go home.
Okay. $3,500.
$3,500?
Either that
or you can go home, bruh.
It's all there.
Better be.
Damn, Suki, when are you
going to pop my clutch?
As soon as you get
the right set of tools.
All right.
All right, back up. Let's go.
Back y'all asses up!
Back up before
you turn into barbecue around here.
It's not a game. This is serious.
All right, back up.
Get off the street. Let's go.
Back it up. Everybody keep
your heads real clear, all right?
'Cause I got a surprise
for y'all this evening.
Go, Slap Jack! Go, baby!
I got this.
Ready?
Go!
Oh, hell, no!
You ain't passing me, dawg. Come on.
What you got?
I told you, you wouldn't pass me!
Move, bitch!
Not tonight, baby!
Bend over, boy.
Damn, girl!
Last turn.
Too wide.
Home stretch, baby.
Got to go, dawg!
Yes!
I can smell you!
Yo, Jimmy, hit it, baby!
All right. Y'all see that?
I told y'all I had a surprise.
How you like that for a finale?
Bridge.
Yeah!
Shit!
Oh, hell, no!
Smack that ass!
Yes!
I saw that, man.
Bullitt and Suki sprayed the bridge.
I need to start making
y'all pay to see this shit.
I got over $10,000
for my man here, all right?
That's what I'm talking about, man.
Play with it.
- Smells good, don't it?
- How about that?
Right. Y'all see this?
Everybody take a good look.
This is what you call mutual
respect. All right, let's clear out.
Anybody down for another race?
Shit.
Make sure you bring that body
by the garage later...
so we can work
on that front end of yours.
Watch out.
Maybe I will.
Where are you going?
- Time to get out of here.
- Why is that?
Nissan Skyline! Got him!
Shit!
Damn!
Let me see your hands!
Put them up!
Yeah, this is him.
We got him.
So, how long
you been in South Florida?
A while.
Before that?
We know you're Brian O'Conner,
formerly of the LAPD.
- You got the wrong guy.
- Really?
How you doing, O'Conner?
Let's take a walk.
Carter Verone.
Born in Argentina, but he's lived
most of his life in Miami.
Now he owns the biggest
import-export business in the state.
Unfortunately, the cartels have been
successful getting drugs into Miami.
But they've had a hard time
getting the cash out.
We've surveilled him for a year.
But we haven't been able to put him
and the money together.
- We've swept his house, warehouses-
- Nothing.
Customs here has done a great job
of getting us this far.
I'm here to help get them
over the top.
I was able to get
an agent in undercover...
working travel and
logistics for him.
Verone's put her in charge
of finding new drivers.
Right, although we can't confirm
her status right now.
- You think she's flipped?
- She's one of mine. She's all right.
She's been in with Verone a year.
Even lives at the compound with him.
Look, it was the FBI's idea
to bring you in. I'm against it.
But we need good drivers to put
this asshole and his money together.
You're gonna roll with Agent Dunn.
And if I don't?
Here's a list of the laws
you broke in L.A.
Obstruction of justice, aiding and
abetting. You know the rap sheet.
We can make this all go away
in the interest of justice...
if you're willing to play ball.
What's the idea here? Dunn and I
are supposed to be street racers?
That's right.
So, Dunn...
looks like we're
going to be partners, bro.
Tell me, what would be
a better motor...
for my Skyline,
a Gallo 12 or a Gallo 24?
Twenty four.
I didn't know
pizza places made motors.
See, man, come on, I can't do this.
If this is what you'll give me,
I'll take my chances in Chino.
We'll get someone else.
No way, man.
The only way I'll do this is
if I get to pick the driver.
All right, O'Conner.
Who you got in mind?
- A dude I grew up with in Barstow.
- Who's that?
Roman Pearce.
That him in the Monte Carlo?
That's him.
He's got some skills.
And he's crazy as hell,
I'm telling you.
In a good way, though.
He's the man for the job.
And he has quite a record,
including three years upstate.
Says here,
he's on house arrest now.
Can't go more than
100 yards from his home.
He always said he'd be famous.
Pearce!
Roman Pearce!
Whatever happens next,
just let it go.
I ain't in it.
Rome!
Only my homeboys call me Rome...
pig.
- I'm not a cop anymore.
- Is that true?
Blondie here is not a cop anymore?
That's true. No badge.
Here we go.
You still fight like shit.
You better chill.
- Why are you here?
- I'll choke you.
I told you to stay away from me.
You should have told me.
I did three years, Brian.
I told you it wasn't my fault.
Why did you come here?
I got a deal for you.
When I needed your ass,
you were nowhere to be found.
Now you're trying to hand out deals?
I need you to come to Miami
and drive with me.
If you do, they'll take off
that anklet and clear your record.
I did three years in jail.
Three years over you, Brian.
- I know you better than you think.
- Maybe you don't.
Maybe you don't.
You guys finished?
Is this deal legit?
That's right.
If you do this job for us.
- I told you.
- Shut up, punk.
So you'll clean my record
and get this thing off my ankle.
That's right.
I thought you couldn't wander
more than 100 yards from your home.
Why do you think
I'm parked so close to the derby?
Quit playing
like you'll pass this up.
You stupid...
Wait. Hold on.
Bro, what's going on?
I don't know if
I should be trusting you, man.
Think of it this way. It's a chance
for a fresh start. Let's do this.
I wouldn't need a fresh start
if it wasn't for you.
You've been using that
since you got busted.
- Let's just chill out and do this.
- I don't need to chill out.
Yes, you do. And you need to stop
blaming me for your mistakes.
Roman Pearce needs to start taking
responsibility for his actions.
- You need to go to hell.
- You need to go back to Barstow.
I'm not going back
to Barstow.
Brian O'Conner,
Roman Pearce, meet Monica Fuentes.
- They have background on Verone?
- They've been briefed.
Good.
All right, here's the deal.
Verone's looking for drivers.
I arranged for you two to join.
I also hired some thugs
to make it legit.
- When do we start?
- Right now.
What are we driving?
Don't even think about
taking the convertible.
It might loosen your mousse.
That's cool.
Too much chrome for me anyways.
Damn! Where do you all
confiscate these rims from, man?
Check in with us after you meet him.
- You okay with these knuckleheads?
- I can handle them.
- If they trouble you, let me know.
- Thanks, Markham.
I ride with you, cowboy.
Why she gotta ride with you?
You get the convertible.
Let's go.
Turn right here.
- So, you used to be a cop?
- Yeah.
How long you been under?
I lost track.
You all right?
You might want to keep
your eyes on the road, playboy.
- You think we're gonna crash?
- I haven't decided yet.
What are you doing, Brian?
He did the "stare and drive" on you,
didn't he? He got that from me.
Once we get in here,
you're on your own.
Look at that one.
Where'd you get them cars?
At the bottom of a cereal box?
Real funny, Fonzie.
Ass.
Roberto, Enrique,
I need pictures of the drivers...
their license plates, cars,
and anything else you can find.
Let's go.
Keep your mouth shut
and follow my lead, all right?
- I got this.
- No, I'm serious.
Handle your business.
I'll handle mine.
Watch your hands, bruh.
Go in line.
Let's go.
Carter.
The drivers are here.
Good.
Come on.
Stay.
What's going on here?
Tell me.
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
My red Ferrari was confiscated.
It sits in an impound lot
in Little Haiti.
It's about 20 miles from here.
The car isn't important. The package
I left in the glove box is.
The first team back here
with the package...
will have an opportunity
to work for me.
What are you saying?
We got to audition?
Nobody has a gun to your head.
That's it.
Driver's licenses. Pass them up.
Before Christmas, guys.
Let's go!
Come on, cuz!
Let's see what this thing can do.
Agent Markham.
They're heading south on I-95.
I got it.
They're running. What a surprise.
Stick with me, Rome.
Why must I chase the cat?
Smart-ass.
You think you're the bomb, Rome?
Let's see if you still got it.
I got something for your ass.
Watch this, bro.
Shit.
How do you like them apples?
Show-off!
That's the Brian O'Conner
school of driving, baby!
Crazy-ass white boy!
Shit!
Bumbaclot.
You better get out
of the street!
That's some bad shit.
What do we got?
That's good. Show me his partner.
Where are the cars?
Stinking boats. Where are the cars?
I need the cars.
Where are the cars at?
Look in the center.
What?
Cha-ching!
- Now put your blouse back on.
- Hater.
Shit!
- Don't let him get away.
- Not a problem.
Sit on it, Fonzie!
What the hell?
Shit. Cops.
What are they doing here?
Rome, no!
Time to go.
Son of a bitch!
Juvy record
for popping cars. Two years in J.D.
Another year for aiding and abetting
an armed robbery.
He's clean. Dirty, but clean.
All right.
Hey, man. You got something
to eat up in there?
We hungry.
Sit them by the pool.
Nice. Come on.
- What are you checking her out for?
- I'm not checking her out.
- Yes, you were.
- No, I wasn't.
- I seen you checking her out.
- Okay, I was. Now shut up.
You shut up.
Don't tell me to shut up.
Both you girlies shut up.
Unbelievable.
You sure are cozy
in this big old mansion.
Sleeping with the enemy.
No, no. Sit down.
Nice Ferrari you got
in the driveway.
I'm glad you like it.
Darling, will you hold that?
We did all that for a damn cigar?
No. You did that for a job.
Do you really think that
I would let somebody impound my car?
The boatyard is mine.
By the way, you two owe me a gate.
I'll take it off your cut.
- Off our cut?
- Yeah.
I like that.
Good.
What's this job
you got for us, anyway?
Come with me.
The house has ears in it.
I have something I want you to carry
from North Beach to the Keys.
What is it?
Just put it in the car,
drive it to me...
and don't let anybody
stop you. Understand?
Any chance of cop trouble?
I'm buying you a window of time,
but it won't be open very long.
You make it...
and I'll personally hand you
$100,000 at the finish line.
Make it $100,000 apiece.
Look, man...
obviously...
your pockets ain't nervous.
- Don't ever touch me.
- Ours are empty.
Like I said...
we hungry.
I got an idea. Why don't you boys
join us at the club later tonight?
Yeah. Pearl at midnight?
- Get to know each other better.
- Sounds good.
See you tonight.
See you.
Hey, you!
- Your pockets aren't empty.
- Damn.
I'll take my cutter back.
Stupid ass.
Hey, man, I figured you
had 12 or 13 of these.
You're not too bright.
Get out of here.
- You're doing the same stupid shit.
- Get off me.
Look, running your mouth?
Insulting people? Stealing his shit?
You think I'd let someone
stare me down?
I didn't let nobody
stare me down in jail, homeboy.
You think I'm gonna
let it fly on a beach?
"And you, I'll take my cutter back. "
His rich ass.
- And you're packing.
- Like you ain't.
Exactly.
- From here on, I do the talking.
- You want to do more than that.
What does that mean?
It means you always get in trouble
over a female, Brian.
Tej's garage is ridiculous.
He has everything.
Snap-on tools. These lifts are new.
They're only a couple of months old.
- Jimmy. What's up, man?
- What's up, Bullitt?
That's Rome there. Do me a favor.
When you get a second, I want you
to check out the Evo and Spyder.
Where'd you get an Evo from?
- It's a long story.
- I got you, man.
Thanks, Jimmy.
It's so hot and humid,
I can't even wear drawers.
Tell me about it.
Look at all this potential out here.
Ray, don't do that, man.
You're making me lose money.
Come on, stop that.
I know you're better than that.
Damn.
Your boy can help put that fire out!
Look at the bubble-
Let's go.
Serious.
Ray, you're making me
lose money.
Don't do that.
Don't do that to me, now.
Come on, Ray. Do it.
Tej Parker? This is Roman Pearce.
Basically, he's the man to know in
Miami. Has his finger in everything.
It's just the way it is.
- What's going on?
- What's up?
- How you doing?
- Good.
What's this?
What's the latest?
It's a work in progress.
It's not finished.
That's some artistic shit.
You got talent.
Ray, it's do or die now!
Bring it home, Ray!
Yeah, baby!
Pay up! Pay up!
That's how they do it out here?
- Every day.
- That's crazy.
Right here. Right now.
You don't look too happy.
Expeditiously, man. I need it quick.
Thank you. Thank you.
How you feeling, man?
You all right? Thank you.
Not too bad.
I see you're about your money,
homey. You race, too?
No, man. I hit a wall doing
like a buck 20 a couple years ago.
Ever since then, I've just been
organizing and collecting.
Check it out. He'll be in town
a while. Can he use that cot?
What's wrong with your place?
I don't want to stay with him.
He has bad habits.
All right. Show him around.
I'll be up there in a minute.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Who wants a chance
to win their money back?
So, Jimmy? You ever seen
anything like this before?
No. Both of them
are wired like I never seen before.
What?
They got us wired with GPS.
That's why Markham knew
we were at that impound lot.
You the master mechanic.
Can't you just yank that shit out?
I'll try, but this ain't LoJack.
The DIS box, the engine management
system, the main harness...
The GPS is spidered into all that.
Tell me something, man.
Do I even want to know
where the Skyline is, dawg?
Or where you've been or where
the hell you got these rides from?
- They're hot.
- Yeah, they hot.
Wired so hot, anyone tracking them
knows if you wear your seat belt.
All right, Jimmy.
- Just do what you can do, bro.
- I got you.
Thanks, man.
We need to get these
on the street ASAP.
Check it out.
See that Cadillac across the street?
They've been on us
since we left Verone's house.
Elian and Fidel!
Can I clean your windshield?
What are you doing, man?
Is everything copasetic?
Kiss my ass.
Shit.
Let's go!
He'll blow our cover
before we even get started.
- What went wrong?
- That's what I want to know.
Show me your hands.
Keep them up!
- What's this about?
- What's going on?
Hold this. You think you can
shoot at me? I'm a federal agent.
What are you talking about?
Get your damn hands off me!
Get him away from me, dawg!
'Cause you wear a badge doesn't mean
you can mess shit up for us!
Get your hands off me!
- Lucky I didn't shoot you!
- Shut up!
Don't tell me to shut up!
You almost blew our cover, old man!
You shouldn't have shown up
like you did.
You didn't know
Verone was testing us?
I thought you punks were running!
That's great. That's real great!
And if Rome wanted to shoot you?
You wouldn't be here right now.
We got to get this under control.
That's mine!
So?
- Tell me what you know.
- We're making a run for Verone.
I'm not sure when or where...
but he said he bought us a window,
I assume from the local cops.
I can talk to some guys
at the local P.D.
No good. If Verone has some
of them on payroll...
we can't let
them know our operation.
Exactly.
In addition, Verone told us that
he himself will be at the drop.
That's good news.
If you're delivering drug money,
we can get him for laundering.
- Now, there's only one problem.
- What's that?
Fuentes.
- Verone's tapping her.
- Tapping her?
- Tapping her how?
- That is crap.
What you talking about?
We know what we seen.
What do you think, O'Conner?
She's compromised? You should know.
- What does that mean?
- Your pal O'Conner didn't tell you?
He flipped on Bilkins in L.A.
He gave his mark his car keys
and let him disappear.
That's why he's not a cop anymore.
So what do you think, expert?
I don't know.
All right. We'll keep an eye on her.
We're out of here.
Let your man go?
Drop it.
I don't wanna talk about it.
Drop it, hell.
I want to hear about this, homey.
Forget about it, cuz.
We got Fuentes in with Verone...
Markham trying to blow our cover...
and we got two wired cars no better
than that ankle bracelet of mine.
I'll tell you, bruh, you let Markham
do that again in front of Verone...
that'll be our ass!
I know, man.
It's getting thick real quick.
We need a way out, got to
come up with an exit strategy.
- Exit strategy?
- Yeah.
I like the way that sounds.
What you got in mind?
I don't know.
But we need two more cars.
Here they come.
Fonzie and Fabio.
Glad you could join us.
We hear you want to get rid
of those Cracker Jack toys.
No, we figured your cars...
deserve better drivers,
so we'll take them off your hands.
Why don't we settle this now?
Wait. How about we settle
this on the blacktop?
Each car does a down-and-back,
tag-team style. For slips.
Loser walks home.
- We came to race.
- Load them up then.
Let's get these cars.
Check it out. There's no way
we'll beat these guys straight up.
That Hemi's putting out about 425...
and that Yenko will snap
a speedo in five seconds flat.
We have to pull something
out of our ass.
I think we should save
the spray for the way back.
Done deal.
Let's do this, bro.
I'm getting that orange one.
You ain't ready, Fabio!
All right.
You each got a barrel to go around
down at the end of the road.
Second wave's got to sit tight till
your partner crosses this line here.
First team to go down and back twice
wins the race.
At which point...
the losers will hand over them keys.
Or you'll be eating breakfast
through straws from now on.
I get it.
This means you, too.
I got it.
All right. Let's race.
Come on, baby, you got this, Rome!
This dude ain't serious.
Yeah, you gone, homey.
I got this. This is done.
You about to lose your car.
- Do it, Rome!
- Come on, you got it, man.
Think I'm worried about this fool?
This is nothing!
- Oh, no.
- American muscle.
Your engine ain't as big
as your mouth.
Got to smoke him.
All right, here we go!
- It's all right, I'll handle this.
- Handle it.
Ready, and... go!
You ain't ready!
I run these streets!
Romey Rome! You ain't heard of me?
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah!
I'm gonna get you.
Where's your big mouth now?
That car's going home with me.
Shit. Eat this, sucker!
Shit!
Yeah, boy! Go, Korpi!
Sorry, blondie,
how does that dust taste?
I don't know.
Come on, Rome.
What the...
Good move, kid.
Let's see if you got the balls.
Shit, come on.
Come on, Brian, bring it home, man!
We got two new cars!
Damn!
Y'all ain't ready!
Get to walking, Fabio!
Use them bus tokens!
How are you?
What's your name?
We're Mr. Verone's guests.
It's a hoasis in here.
Yeah, lots of potential.
Damn. You got a pen?
It's about to get serious.
Look at that girl on the swing.
You guys did something right.
He never socializes with hired help.
Now what's that make you?
- Where's he at?
- He's on his way.
You and Verone
don't go everywhere together?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
- I'm gonna go take a piss.
- You go do that.
What is his deal?
He doesn't trust people
who carry badges.
You talk like you know.
I'd been a cop about two months when
Roman was busted in a garage raid.
He had eight sets of wheels
in his possession, each of them hot.
So you busted him?
I didn't know it was going down.
But that doesn't really matter.
Once I became a cop, Roman saw me
as a friend who became the enemy.
Is there anything I can get for you,
Mr. Verone?
Just tell them
to come join me.
I was admiring this.
Damn.
I'm not giving it to you. What's up?
He's here.
Where's he at?
He's over there. Don't look.
Excuse me, Mr. Verone
would like for you to join him.
Let's do it.
See what I'm talking about?
It's all right, let them in.
Go sit down,
I'll talk to you in a second.
- How you doing?
- Good. Enjoying your night?
- Yeah, I'm having a good time.
- Good.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
Yeah.
She's gorgeous.
You got balls, kid.
I appreciate that.
Women are a powerful force.
You see the blonde sitting
with the gentleman right here?
Five minutes of her time, and she
can get anything she wants from him.
I love your hair.
Watch.
I wonder where they're going?
Sit down.
So you lit my man's car on fire.
Is that right?
Yeah.
I did.
I got a problem with authority.
I have that same problem.
For me, it's cops in particular.
Let's take a walk. Come on.
We just got here.
And now we're leaving.
Let's go.
Hey.
Come on.
What's all that?
We're going to have a little fun.
Thank you.
- It'll be fun. Let's stay longer.
- Yeah.
Hey, Carter.
Meet Detective Whitworth.
One of Miami's finest.
Thank you, sweetheart.
You enjoying yourself, Detective?
Yeah, I was.
I mean, you know me.
Yeah.
I do know you.
You've been on my payroll
a long time.
- Verone, that ain't right.
- Shut up.
I've got one last job for you.
You hear me?
- We've been through this.
- Yeah?
And I said I can't do it.
That's the wrong answer.
The table.
I'm a detective, Verone!
You do anything to me, the whole
force'll be on your ass in a minute.
Shut your mouth,
you fat piece of shit.
Stop right now.
What the hell?
Sit down.
You're going to regret this.
Stop right now!
Once the bucket
gets hot enough, Detective...
the rat is gonna want out.
And the only direction it can go,
is south.
Hold that.
Get it off me!
I'll forget it-
Shut up.
Did you know that your average rat
can chew through a steel drainpipe?
You have nothing to worry about
when he's screaming.
It's when he goes quiet
that he goes to work.
Stop it!
You can't be this stupid!
Stop it now!
You're in charge of the units
that are watching my properties.
What I want is a 15-minute window...
where everybody,
and I mean everybody, disappears.
- I can't do it!
- You can't?
Stop it.
Okay. Monica, come here.
Help!
Shut him up.
It's biting me!
What?
Got something you want to say?
It bit me. Jesus.
- I'll do it!
- Do what? Say it.
I'll do it.
I'll give you your window.
Just get it off me.
Get it off!
You betray me...
and my rat here...
is gonna visit your wife, Lynn...
your son, Clay,
and your daughter, Lexi.
Do you hear me?
Do you understand me?
- Hear me?
- Get it off.
I'll burn your fucking eyes out!
I'll burn them out.
Now, you can go.
Get rid of him. Let's go.
Get it off.
You boys enjoy the show?
Fifteen minutes, and then every cop
in Florida's gonna be on you.
Be at Versailles Café at 6:00 a.m.,
day after tomorrow, ready to drive.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
Don't play games with me...
or you'll be next. All right?
Help yourself to a little champagne.
Let's go.
That was a damn rat.
You ever touch another man again,
and I'll kill you.
You hear me?
Look at me. You hear me?
She was into it.
What's that about?
You seen the way she grabbed
the dude's head.
She had to. He was testing her.
Her ass is on the line, like ours.
You're feeling this girl
way too much.
She's like that trailer rat
from back in the day, Tanya.
Tanya? Man, you went out with her
after I did.
I couldn't let it go to waste.
I got you.
Is that right?
We go race for cash,
but when I step on the gas...
my nitrous go blast,
leave your ass in the past.
Tej, you about
to lose your garage.
Whatever, man.
I'm a low-budget mechanic,
but I overcharge.
Pay me! Let's go, man.
Pay me my money.
I'm glad you're happy.
This is my garage.
Royal flush. Give me this, man.
Talk to him.
Put that money back on the table.
You know it's mine next hand.
Jimmy, how're you gonna pay me back
if you keep losing to Tej like that?
I'm going to crash, Tej.
I'll catch you tomorrow.
What are you doing here?
They're gonna kill you. I heard him
telling Enrique and Roberto.
Once you finish the run, they're
putting a bullet in your head.
You sure you heard him right?
I'm sure.
Verone's boys is outside...
I see what they're looking for.
Your little girlfriend here.
- They don't know. I snuck out.
- What are they doing here then?
I don't know.
Maybe they're guessing.
Go stall them for,
like, two minutes.
Check her, homey.
Found what you're
looking for?
Hey, buddy. Hi, guys. How you doing?
Y'all still mad about y'all car?
Don't even trip.
Come on, man, can't you take a joke?
This isn't about being a good cop
or doing your job.
They're gonna kill you.
You gotta pull out.
Verone pay you
to keep a straight face like that?
'Cause if I was making money,
I'd remove that mole off my nose.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
How much he pay y'all anyway?
Every time I see y'all,
y'all got the silk shirts on...
jewelry, looking real Miami.
I caught you walking up in the club,
the hamburger meat all hanging out.
Don't make that run, Brian.
Be careful.
Where are you going?
You stay right here with us, buddy.
Don't even think about it.
Stay your ass off my homeboy's boat.
Put the gun down now!
You first, asshole!
I'll shoot the shit out of him!
Put down the gun!
Enough.
Shut up.
It's over. Come on.
It's over. Let's go.
It's our gun. Come on, let's go.
I'm glad to see you boys
are getting along so well...
because tomorrow, Roberto and
Enrique'll be riding along with you.
Just so we don't have any problems.
I'll see you guys in a bit.
What the hell
was she doing in there?
Where'd you go this morning?
I went to breakfast
with some friends.
With friends?
I do have friends, Carter.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Nice shirt, Bilkins.
It's my day off.
Well, anyhow, this is the deal.
Last night, Verone threatened a cop
into giving us a window.
We're driving to an airstrip
in the Keys, off Nallwood Avenue.
Verone has a plane there
and he's taking off for good.
Wait a minute. How do you know this?
Monica.
She's doing her job. She warned us.
She warned you about what?
Verone plans to kill us
after we give him the money.
Driving into an ambush
wasn't the deal. I'm calling it off.
Like hell you are.
This is a Customs case, Bilkins.
No one's calling this off
unless I do.
Look, this is real simple.
Make the run, get Verone and his
cash together, so I can move in.
You don't, I'll file enough charges
on you to make you disappear.
Take these.
We're gonna have GPS on you
so you don't get any cute ideas.
And to make sure
nothing happens to them, right?
Yeah, right.
That guy's a dick.
Let me get this right.
If we don't do this,
then we go to jail.
But if we do it,
then Verone's going to kill us.
- It's a hell of a deal, huh?
- Yeah.
Maybe it is.
This guy's got an ass full of loot
that he's ready to dump in our cars.
I can think of two reasons why
he doesn't need that money anymore.
Here we go.
You and me.
Just like the old days.
- What do you think?
- They messed with the wrong guys.
- Tej, what's up, bro?
- What's up?
How quickly can you organize?
Look, if y'all really want
to carry out this plan...
this is the best place to do it.
What do y'all think?
I think it's perfect.
So, what do they store here?
This thing is clean.
Distributor cap.
Jimmy, do we have any half-empty
bottles of nitrous lying around?
Sure, but I've already
loaded you for spray.
I'm thinking we may need it
for something else...
'cause our cars may get
a little crowded, you know?
When did you start eating so much?
I was in jail, bruh.
I know how shitty the grub is
on the inside.
The way things are shaping up
out here right now...
it'll be a matter of time
before I'm back in there, or dead.
So I'm trying to eat all I can
while I can.
Plus, the doctor tells me
I got a high metabolism.
You remember us growing up?
Playing football in the dirt?
Getting into trouble.
All the stupid things we did?
When you got busted,
whether I was a cop or not...
if there was anything
I could have done...
I would have done it.
I just want you to know that.
Is that why
you let that dude go in L.A.?
Yeah, I think
that had a lot to do with it.
When I got busted...
it wasn't your fault.
It was all on me, Mr. Roman Pearce.
Wild and out. Crazy man.
No one could tell me nothing.
Riding solo.
Yeah, well, not anymore.
Not anymore, bro.
I've got Verone's Navigator
leaving the residence.
Copy.
Sir, we've got Verone on the move
to the airstrip.
Let's get a bird in the air.
Tell him to keep his distance.
- Ready.
- Thanks.
- You're all set.
- All set?
- Yeah. Let's do it.
Report.
What's going on
out there?
Team One, checking in.
- Team Two, checking in.
- Team Three, checking in.
Team Four,
all clear here, too.
Team Five, checking in.
Team Six, all clear.
- Here we go.
- Yeah, so you know what to do.
Stay cool. Keep focused.
Remember the airstrip's
off Nallwood Avenue.
It's the third exit
after the bridge.
Got it.
You ready for this?
Come on, man.
Guns, murderers, and crooked cops?
I was made for this, bruh!
Come on.
I got activity
at Verone's trailer property.
Do not move an inch
until I tell you to!
Load up.
All units...
move on the trailer property.
Right now! Move!
Shit. Local P.D.
is moving in on our guys.
- Three bags in one car?
- Guess so.
The cops.
I am not going back to jail.
Where are you going, man? Let's go!
What is he doing?
Now let's get the chopper over them.
I want eyes right on top.
You got it.
Lima 2-5...
follow GPS.
Do you know what you're doing?
Stay with me, Rome. Come on, man.
I've got them heading south
on I-95.
Bring in the aerial ESDs.
Oh, shit!
- They're catching up, man!
- Shut up, man!
Nice driving, Rome.
I got you, Brian.
Check it out!
What was that?
Oh, shit!
- Come on, man. Take the wheel.
- No. I can't drive.
Just hold the wheel!
Put your hands on it! Hold steady!
What are you doing, man?
Yeah, man!
Hold.
Bilkins, the bird's in place.
Yeah.
We've got Verone's Navigator.
All right. Money's in transit.
Sit tight.
You're a good driver, man.
Thanks, bro.
We've got the area blocked ahead.
They've got nowhere to go.
What was that?
I've got a visual.
Video should be coming through.
I got it. Looks good.
Where are they going?
Shit.
All right, Miami's finest,
let's see what you got.
Come on. Stay with me, boys.
Hey, man, everyone's here.
Time for the show.
Let's give it to them.
All right, let the party begin.
Let's go!
This is unit 25-99.
We have the suspects surrounded.
Holy shit!
It's a scramble, baby! A big one!
Yeah! Let's do this!
Check this out.
We're not tracking them
on the video.
We must have lost them
in the scramble.
Yo, let's break.
Yeah!
All right, we got them going west
on Beach.
Roger that! I've got them!
Customs has a fix on two cars
going west on Beach.
Roger. Follow those cars.
Roger that.
Shit.
They're cornered.
Keep your hands
where I can see them!
Hands up!
I know my tags are out of date,
but damn.
What the hell?
Where are they?
How about them apples, man?
Yeah! That's some driving
for your ass, baby!
Good job, man.
- What are you talking about?
- Whatever.
You're supposed to be
a stone-faced killer!
You were grabbing your seat belt!
Hey, Tej, thanks a lot, bro.
You're clutch. I owe you big time.
Yeah, Brian, you really do owe me.
You really do...
Us.
Suki says you owe us, all right?
- Rome, you there? Come in.
- What's up, man?
Looks like we got
just one trick left.
My pleasure, buddy!
Let's do it, baby!
Maybe we should grab Verone
while we still can.
No! Not yet!
What?
You lost them?
Shit!
Those little pricks are running!
It's your call.
What do you want to do?
We're gonna take him down.
He is not leaving here.
Enjoying the ride?
It's a fast car, huh?
It's a classic. Old school.
American muscle.
This car can do all kinds of things.
Want to see?
Check this out right here, homey.
Hey, what are you doing,
man?
Ejecto seato!
It worked! I love this button!
Stay on your toes!
Mr. O'Conner, it worked!
Blow and go. I'm all clear.
Meet me at the point!
Hurry up! It's on!
All right. 10-4, man.
Are you ready? Let's go!
Let me see your hands!
Freeze!
Clear!
- It's not Verone and Fuentes.
- What do you mean?
Then where the hell are they?
Get off at Tarpon Point.
Tarpon Point?
There's no airstrip at Tarpon Point.
Who said anything about an airstrip?
Brian?
What's the hold-up, bro?
Yo. There's a new plan.
What the hell?
We meet him at Tarpon Point exit,
not the airstrip.
- So, what are you saying?
- Like I said, there's a new plan.
Brian?
Brian? Hello, you there?
Damn!
What the hell is he doing?
The feds are in the wrong place.
Brian's woman is on her own
with Verone.
So...
So Brian's not coming!
- Let him out.
- Get out.
Pop the trunk.
Hurry up.
Where's the rest?
- The other car.
- Another car?
- Where's the other car?
- On its way.
- On the way?
- Yeah.
Here's your money.
So you know nothing about the agents
that stormed my jet?
The funny thing is, I only told
one person about the airstrip.
Customs agents sure
are getting pretty, aren't they?
Put her on the boat.
- Let's go.
- Get on the boat.
Hide the cars and get rid of him.
Back in the car.
End of the road.
You know, I like you.
But I still got to kill you.
It's my job.
What's that?
It's Barstow, baby!
It's about to get ugly!
Let's go.
Come on.
You had me.
You slipped.
Eleven and a half months,
and you slipped once.
Put her downstairs.
See you in a second.
I thought you was dead.
Me, too. Thanks for saving my ass.
What are you doing?
If Verone sees a helicopter
or Customs boat, she's dead!
Boat.
Car. Boat.
You're not gonna do
what I think you're gonna do?
- Yeah, I think so. You got my back?
- Yeah.
All right, put on the seat belt.
Show him some Dukes of Hazzard shit!
We're gonna do this big!
Hold on, Rome!
Brian, you're crazy, man!
What the hell are you doing?
I think I broke my arm.
Get the gun.
It's over, Carter.
You okay?
Yeah!
I'm great.
We got him, man.
We got him. Let's get out of here.
Go, go.
That ought to do it.
So, there were three bags total?
The three from the boat?
So we're good, right?
Our records are clean?
You held up your end.
Your records are clean.
So maybe there were six bags.
I guess we can call it even.
Agent Dunn?
We found some more evidence.
Let's take it inside.
Don't drop the soap, big homey.
I hope you know when he gets out,
he's going to kill your ass.
He ain't getting out.
I'll see you soon.
- You think he's going to get out?
- He'll be out.
Not for real.
You think he's getting out?
We took care of your decoys.
They're free and clear.
There's a sedan
out on the road for you.
Try to bring it back in one piece.
Thanks a lot, Bilkins.
You're all right.
Thanks for looking out.
Do you trust me now?
You're all right.
Sorry.
Nice working with you, O'Conner.
Same here.
I might have to stay here in Miami,
and keep you out of trouble, bruh.
You know what I'm talking about.
You're going to kick it
in Miami?
I love Miami.
Miami is off the hook!
Open a garage together.
A garage?
How are we going to do that?
Pockets ain't empty, cuz.
And we ain't hungry
no more, either.
Han!
Hello man.
Welcome to the D.R.
Put your suitcase in back here.
'Sup Boss!
I bring you something.
Can you explain to me
who is the Chinese guy?
Looks like you have been really
moving up in the world.
Who's this guy?
Santo, Han.
Han, Santo.
- You look like shit.
- That is a lot coming from you.
How come we can't stay in a hotel, huh?
Oh, complaining already!
I like air-conditioning, you know?
And room service.
- So, you guys love each other.
- With TV!
Dig in.
Welcome to our island, Han.
Island in paradise.
Tonight we go speak to Elvis.
See if we can fix this problem.
- First we pick up Leo.
- Leo?
So where are we actually picking
up this Leo friend of yours?
Prison.
Yo! My God!
Move! Move, man!
And that's why you're
always impressive man.
- Hey where you going?
- I'll be back, one second.
Or you could drive around the corner.
Park and come through the front.
Hey.
Wait, wait.
I ain't goin' out there like this.
Do you wanna wear my shirt?
No man. I got it covered, man.
Somebody's coming to bring my shit.
Don't worry.
I got it covered.
Who is this guy we're meeting?
Elvis.
He's a politician who gives a fuck about the people.
Beautiful.
Hey Han.
I bet this is a lot different than China.
- Never been.
- Or Japan, wherever you're from.
Like I said I never been
east of the Atlantic.
- He asked you where you're from.
- States.
- Is that where you met Dom?
- Nah, I met him in Mexico.
Used to hear about him in the racing scene.
But didn't start running with him until then.
And?  You guys are hungry?
Or you want me to get you guys a room?
That's cool.
So you've been running with him for a while?
Hey you know.  Here and there.
South America.  Tells me for all the fun stuff.
Wow.
Leo.
Have a seat.
- Hello.
- How you doing my friend?
Well this is the guy I was telling you about.
This meeting gonna be good.
For the island.
Well you know, my friend that I don't
like having unexpected guest.
I already got my crew here.
He knows how I like to do business.
Now, I tell you why.
When the merchandise gets here...
Shut the fuck up!
Like I was saying my friend.
I'll protect the merchandise
until it's out of the port.
Once it gets out...
If you wanna do something freaky
that's none of my business.
Okay.
Between the arrival...
and its destination...
there's a very slight window open.
Yeah, don't worry about that.
You know at the end of the day people
are gonna get what they need.
You can't move forward without fuel.
And no one wants to be left behind.
She can get it and give it to the people.
God bless.
Here baby, I got you a beer.
It ain't that hard to track you down.
All I gotta do is follow the odor of skanks.
Letty.
Life has a way of changing those plans.
Change of plans.
Where do we sleep?
Excuse me ladies.
That's right.
All the way from Mexico, sucker.
What?
Who is this?
Did I just hear you speaking Dominican?
It's been a while since I've
been back in the States.
- You know that.
- You're missed.
She's alright.
So what's going on?
I know you're not training
these boys for nothing.
Have I arrived just in time
for a new adventure?
Letty you always get here just
in time for something.
Come on, what is it?
I'll block you. You can't see.
What are you gonna do?
Oh my God, we're gonna crash.
Oh no!
What's gonna happen?
This place is crazy.
Rain one minute. Clouds the other.
Sunlight next.
Where you taking me?
Wait 'til you see.
Come here.
You feel that?
How could you be 3,000 miles away from that?
Can't.
Will this do?
We have eternity in this moment.
You will never be alone again.
I vow wherever you go, I go.
You ride, I ride.
You fight, I fight.
And if you ever die on me,
Dominic Toretto,
I'm gonna die with you.
I love you, Letty.
I will always love you.
All right,
we're good to go.
You got this? You bet your ass, bubba.
Let's make some money!
Everyone in position.
I thought we'd be
robbing banks by now,
not some gas truck
in the middle of nowhere.
Down here, gas is gold, bubba.
Kill the chatter!
Game time.
I wouldn't piss him off, guys.
Okay, guys, we're gonna have
to hit this hard and fast.
We got four K left
before the downgrade.
Locked and loaded!
This is all you, Han.
Liquid gold.
We're clear.
Okay, T, you're up.
Let's see if you can get it
under six tries this time, huh, T?
It's more like three. Come
on, Tego, keep it real.
Just one K left. We're running
out of road. Get in there, brother.
I got it, I got it.
Shit!
T, cut loose!
Unhitch, unhitch!
Spray that hitch!
I don't have a hammer!
Just do it!
Hold on! Hold on!
No shit!
Hold onto
something tight!
Letty!
Give me your hand!
I can't reach!
You got to jump!
Jump!
Letty, jump!
I've got you!
Dom...
Dom?
Dom!
How you doing?
Money, money!
Good.
Yo, why your stack
is bigger than mine always?
I'm supersized,
baby.
Cops just raided
our garage in Baracoa.
They were real
interested in you.
Heat's on and we just sent up a flare
that's gonna lead them right to us.
I say we move out first
thing in the morning.
Nah, it's me they want.
And if they catch me,
they're throwing big
numbers at anybody with me.
Han, we had a good run.
Time for you to go
do your own thing.
Heard they're doing
some crazy shit in Tokyo.
Have you seen Letty?
There she is.
I hear Rio is nice
this time of year.
The cops are
getting hungrier.
Then I guess we're doing our job.
I'm a walking target.
I don't want you around
when they catch up to me.
"Ride or die,"
remember?
Dom, how long have we been doing this?
And now all of a sudden, out
of nowhere, it's too dangerous?
Come on.
We'll figure it out.
We always do.
I don't know shit!
Give me a name!
I don't know shit, man!
David Park! David
Park's the guy you want!
Please!
Thank God. Listen, he's in a mood
because yesterday was his cheat day,
and then today, some
genius brought in donuts.
Great.
Sorry I'm late.
Complaints keep rolling in after your
little downtown Olympics, O'Conner.
Tell me that reinstating
you wasn't a mistake.
I got a name. David Park. That's it?
That's all you got?
David Park?
I could throw a fortune cookie out this
window and hit 50 David Parks right now.
It's Korean, not Chinese. Whatever.
Park is a scout that recruits street
racers to be mules for the Braga cartel.
We find Park, and we bust the bad guys.
Yo.
Where's my money?
Dom.
Mia, I told you
not to call me here.
Dom, it's Letty.
She's been murdered.
We have gathered here
to pay our final respects to...
Let us reflect
on her journey...
"The Lord is my shepherd, I shall
not want. He makes me lie down... "
Facial recognition software
matched Toretto
about 10 minutes after
he crossed the border.
I don't get it.
I thought he'd show.
I told you not to come.
They're staking the place out.
If they find you...
They won't.
Come on.
Look at you.
Letty wouldn't
let them junk it.
Even though it is
a goddamn curse.
When she came back,
she was always in here,
working on it
day and night.
It was weird.
It was like she knew
you were coming back.
I want to see
the crash site.
I just got off the
phone with Deputy Director Lawson.
If we don't make serious inroads into
the Braga case in the next 72 hours,
they're gonna
shut us down.
I know I'm a newbie here,
but why the clock now?
Because it's been
two years,
and the last three agents we sent
to infiltrate his organization
came back in body bags.
He's moved more heroin across the
border than Escobar did in 10 years.
This guy is becoming one of
our biggest national threats,
and we don't even
have a picture of him.
We don't have prints!
Not even a goddamn DOB!
What's the status
on David Park?
Isn't he our ticket into
the Braga organization?
We're running the name through city and
county databases, sorting the possibilities.
We've got
over 500 already.
Park's insignificant. Sounds
like another jerk-off to me.
It's not. Without Park, Braga
wouldn't have drivers to move his shipments.
Cross-check traffic.
Illegal modifications.
Street racing. This guy will definitely
have a record. We'll find him.
We better.
What do you know?
Your boy Toretto's red Chevelle has
been spotted in his old neighborhood.
I'm going to
bring his ass in.
Not in your car
you're not.
It's straight ahead.
You found something
back there.
There were burn marks
on the ground.
The kind that could only
be caused by nitrometh.
There's only one guy in
all of L.A. that sells that.
Nothing you can do is
gonna bring her back, Dom.
If I were Letty,
I would ask you...
No, I would beg you,
please, let this go.
Before it's too late.
It's already too late.
I love you.
Miss Toretto.
I'm Michael Stasiak, FBl.
Let's you and I
have a little chat.
Hi. This is Forsythe
in Evidence.
I need Stasiak down here right
away to sign some greenies.
Thanks.
Hi.
Hey.
Okay, I narrowed it down
to 50 or so David Parks.
What I'd like you to do is run the
make and model on each one of them.
All right?
Okay. All right.
Thank you.
Hey, Tyler,
we got a transfer.
You want to
come with me?
Toretto.
When'd you get
back in town?
I'm looking for a car
you did an engine mod on.
Nitromethane tank. Ford
full-size. Continental tires.
Look, what are you doing,
coming in here like this, huh?
This ain't your scene
anymore, boss.
Don't ever put your hands
on me again, okay?
Say hi to your
sister for me.
A Korean kid brought it in. David Park.
It's a green Ford Torino.
Please don't
drop this on me!
I'm almost done.
Why don't you tell me why
you dragged me here, Brian?
You know they're going to
capture Dom. Maybe worse.
I don't want you getting tangled
up in this. So stay away from him.
That's what you have to
say to me after five years?
All of a sudden, you
care what happens to me.
What I did to you
was wrong.
I'm sorry. It was... It was the
hardest thing I've ever had to do.
I'm sorry, too, Brian.
I'm so sorry that you had to come
into my home and pretend to love me.
I'm so sorry that you
ripped my family apart.
I'm very sorry that
that was hard for you.
I lied to you.
I lied to Dom.
I lied to everybody.
That's what I do best. It's
why the Feds recruited me.
Maybe you're lying
to yourself.
Maybe you're not the good guy
pretending to be a bad guy.
Maybe you're the bad guy
pretending to be the good guy.
You ever think about that?
Every day.
I always wondered,
why did you let
my brother go that day?
I don't know.
Shit.
Brian!
I got the cross-checks on David Park
back and have a list of possibles.
What do you got? All right. A
45-year-old male in a '06 Scion
with three reckless driving tickets. No.
An '01 Chevy Tahoe.
No.
Two Mini Coopers, a '06
and a '07, a Toyota hybrid.
Hell no. A '98 Saturn, a '95 Sebring.
A '98 Nissan 240
with an illegal mod.
Wait. That's it.
What? The 240 with the illegal mod.
How do you know? 'Cause
that's something I'd drive.
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Green Torino,
running nitro.
Whose car?
I don't know, man.
I'm just the middleman. I
swear! I'm just the middleman!
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't know shit, man. I swear. I
just run cars for Braga, all right?
All I can do is get you in
the race! That's all I can do!
What race?
Help! Come on,
hold on!
Let me up, man!
Come on!
Come on, man, I don't
know shit! Just let me up!
I told you, you got to talk to Braga!
Bring him up, Dom.
God! Don't drop me!
That's all I know!
Bring him up.
You here to take
me in, O'Conner?
Shit! Shit!
Shut up!
Letty was my friend, too.
You weren't
anyone's friend.
Yo, can you guys talk about
this later? Now pull my ass up!
She was running for this guy,
Braga, and things went bad.
Please!
I'm going to
get these guys, Dom.
Now let me do my job
and bring him up.
I'm going to
kill this Braga.
God!
And anyone else
who gets in my way.
Hey!
Don't let go.
O'Conner!
O'Conner! If you ever release
a witness of mine again...
That's enough! STASIAK: Don't touch me.
I'm fine! PENNING: That's enough.
You're through, O'Conner!
I said that's enough!
Stasiak, go get
yourself cleaned up.
What?
He hit me first! You...
This isn't
the Cub Scouts!
Now, go on! You're bleeding on my floor.
O'Conner, do you know the difference
between a cop and a criminal?
What?
One bad judgment call.
Keep your shit in line,
son.
Have a good time.
Take a seat.
Good news. We have intel that
Braga's number two, Ramon Campos,
will hold a street race
in Koreatown tomorrow night
to fill a slot
on his team.
They've already chosen three
drivers from previous races.
Our newest informant,
Mr. David Park,
has been kind enough
to get us into the race.
O'Conner, you're up.
Let me guess,
winner gets the slot.
All right, so these are all the
imports the city has in impound.
Okay, nice.
Pick your poison.
All right, 2206.
I crashed one of those.
3418 and 2765.
Okay, so which one
do you want?
I want them all.
Standard issue
tracking device.
Boss wants to know where
you are at all times.
You want to
play with it?
Hey!
What are you
looking at, nutsack?
I don't know.
You tell me.
The racer wants
what Dwight's got.
See, but, ladies, Dwight's
already on the team.
You got to be fast if you
want to drive for Braga.
Is there a problem here? No.
You one of
Park's guys, blondie?
Yeah. Yeah, I am.
Follow me.
See you later, punk.
You, too, punk.
Bull's-eye, coño,
come on!
We can do this all day.
You all know
why you're here.
Good drivers
are a dime a dozen.
Man, every corner's got a
chingadera tuner racing for pinks.
That's not what Braga
has got me looking for.
Braga wants someone that would sell
their abuelita to be behind the wheel.
Someone that drives their 10-second
cars not in a straight line,
but to push it and make it through
places no one else would take it.
Real drivers.
So, what are we hauling?
For the money Braga's paying,
you don't need to know.
You just said you wanted real drivers.
A real driver knows
exactly what's in his car.
Mira, real driver,
nobody's forcing you
to race.
You the boss?
Or am I talking
to the boss?
Do I look like a boss?
My job is to find the
best drivers, period.
Whoever wins the race
gets the info. We cool?
Are we cool?
Yeah, we're cool.
No,
we ain't cool, man.
Who's closing these streets?
No one.
That's the point.
Please wait while
directions are downloaded.
Proceed to
the highlighted route.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six...
You sure you want to do
this? A lot has changed.
...four...
You're right.
...three,
two,
one,
go!
Right turn ahead.
You are now five miles
from your destination.
How's my ass look,
Chia Pet?
Ghetto Smurf.
Dead man driving.
Come on!
Right turn ahead.
Shit!
Damn.
Rerouting.
Proceed straight ahead.
Shit.
Rerouting.
Just shut up!
You are 2.6 miles
from destination.
Oops, I didn't see you.
You are now four and one-half
miles from your destination.
U- turn, if possible.
Are you kidding me?
You are now 4.2 miles
from your destination.
Sorry, car.
You are now one mile
from your destination.
Yeah,
guess who's back, Dom?
Let's go!
Nice car, baby!
Bitch!
You are now one-quarter
mile from your destination.
Too early, Dom.
No!
Still a buster.
You have reached your
destination. Goodbye.
At least we know you
can't beat me straight up.
I didn't know
there were any rules.
Now that's what I call
real driving.
No, that's bullshit, man!
Go cry to your mama, eh?
You work for Braga now.
When the GPS calls,
you follow.
Driver's license.
What driver's license?
Thumb.
Cell phone number.
The print is for Campos.
The number is for me.
Yo, nutsack!
Let me tell you something, man,
muscle beats import every time.
You know what I'm saying? Every time!
Ladies, let's get on
back to Papa Dwight's.
Papa Dwight wants you
to take off your shoes.
Dwight likes feet.
Take off your shoes.
So beautiful.
Dwight likes this foot a lot.
Yes, baby!
Daddy Dwight loves...
FBl!
I didn't do nothing, man!
Dwight didn't do nothing!
Hey, no! Stay, stay! Where
you going? Bye, Dwight!
No, what did I do?
You're under arrest
for distribution of meth.
Meth? Dwight's never
touched that shit, bro!
Dwight has now.
Yo, that ain't mine! No!
You know that's never
gonna stick, right?
Yeah, it's not
supposed to.
Live it up!
Yeah, Corona.
That's too bad
about Dwight.
Having the Feds raid your house
the same night you make the team.
So unfortunate.
I wish I could say I was
surprised to see you here.
What's to stop someone from
telling them you're a cop?
Probably the same thing that's keeping me
from telling them why you're really here.
What up, fellows?
Hey, how you doing?
Great. You having a good
time? Yeah, a great time.
Come on, let's have a better time.
How's your car?
It took a nasty bump.
It'll be ready.
I also heard you just
got out of County.
Yeah.
Mmm-hmm.
You know a guy
named Jim Garcia?
Nah. Big place. Lots
of names, lots of faces.
And you, you're wanted by
a lot of people, homes.
Yeah, that kind of heat
can't be good for business.
Yeah, well, that depends
on how you look at things.
I go down, I do time.
I do real time.
I don't know about your other drivers, but
when I see flashing lights in my mirror,
I don't stop.
Do you know each other?
He used to date
my sister.
I see.
You're a lucky man.
How's that?
You're still breathing.
To the ladies we've loved
and the ladies we've lost.
So, what's Braga about?
You know,
he's just one of us.
Came up from the streets.
Down for el barrio.
Now he's a shot caller.
The boss of bosses.
See all these
cats in here?
Any one of them
would die for Braga.
Including you?
Especially me.
Enjoy the party, fellows.
Club's yours.
Whatever you want, booze,
broads, it's all good.
Braga's mine.
I'm taking the
whole house down.
Good luck.
Something interests you
about this car?
Just admiring
the body work.
Are you one of those boys
who prefers cars to women?
I'm one of those boys that appreciates
a fine body, regardless of the make.
Your car?
It's Fenix's car.
You'll meet him at the
rendezvous. He'll be leading you.
So now
that I know
your taste in cars,
tell me, what about your women?
It all starts
with the eyes.
She's got to have those kind of eyes
that can look right through the bullshit
to the good in someone.
20% angel,
80% devil.
Down to earth.
Ain't afraid to get a little
engine grease under her fingernails.
That doesn't sound
anything like me.
It ain't.
Hi.
I got a gift for you.
All right.
A dirty shot glass,
just what I always wanted.
I got these from the club last night.
There's two sets of
prints here. Run them both.
I know one of these is Campos'. I
think the other might be Braga's.
And you're gonna have
to go beyond Interpol.
So, that means I have to
contact individual agencies,
and that could
take weeks. Okay.
Yeah.
That's your third traffic
violation in less than three blocks.
Slow it down,
O'Conner.
Sure thing, Dad.
He stopped.
We lost him.
He killed the tracker.
We don't know that.
I'm telling you, he killed the
tracker. We don't know that yet!
Get the bird overhead.
Right now, I'm moving north, 33', 56'...
All clear.
Base, flag nine,
I'm at Angels 5.
I don't have a tally on the target.
Repeat, I don't have a tally on the target.
They're gone, there's no one down there.
Damn it!
This ain't right, bro. Nobody said
nothing about being locked in no truck.
Tell me about it.
Hey. Hey!
Yo! Where do you think
they're taking us?
Don't matter.
We're all just along
for the ride now.
Welcome to Mexico, boys.
There are helicopters
and surveillance cameras
that scan for heat
signatures at the border.
But there are blind spots that I
can guide you through via satellite.
There can be no margin of error, so
you must follow my every direction.
Any questions?
I thought Fenix
was gonna be here.
He'll meet you
out there.
All right, everybody, sync up.
Good luck, gentlemen.
Satellite linkup engaged.
Keep proceeding northbound
at current speed.
Stay close to Fenix.
He'll lead you across.
I got a heat signature
northbound along Lagardo Ravine.
Thermal imaging window on the Mexico
side's gonna be down for about 45 seconds.
Get the camera on it.
Manual override. Rerouting
camera to designated coordinates.
Hurry it up.
You guys have been tagged.
Shit.
Toretto,
get back in formation.
Reimaging commencing.
I don't see anything.
They're gone.
Get the helicopters
to cover it.
Base, we're 40 seconds
out from Lagardo Ravine.
They're sending
a helicopter.
You have 30 seconds.
North 32' 33',
west 116' 49'.
The window
is closing fast.
You need to get out of there
before they send ground support.
Fifteen seconds.
Base,
target is at two miles.
You're running
out of time.
You need to get out now!
Base, we're at north
32' 33', west 116' 49'.
We have no visual contact. Roll
ground units for confirmation.
Sloppy!
Very sloppy!
What are you doing, man?
Come on.
Get out.
Come on, man.
Come on, today, man.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, don't touch me.
Hey, don't touch me, man!
Hey, I said don't touch me, man!
Hey, look, dawg, don't
put your hands on me.
Hey,
Malik, chill, bro.
Yo, man, what's up
with your boy?
Hey, boss man!
What did you say?
I said only pussies
run nitrometh.
You looked under my hood?
I'm talking to you.
Got something on your mind?
'70 Plymouth.
Her name was Letty.
And somebody
wrecked her car.
I wrecked her car.
You remember her face?
Huh?
'Cause I don't.
Last time I saw it,
it was burning.
Now what?
I'm going to enjoy
what happens next.
Dom, get in!
Get in! Come on!
Come on! Get in the fucking
car! Let's go! Hurry up!
What
have you got, Trinh?
We're contacting agencies
in multiple countries.
Unfortunately, most of them have to
manually scan their prints for us to upload.
O'Conner's on line five.
And, sir,
you should see this.
Thank you.
Talk to me, O'Conner.
Where the hell have you
been? I got the shipment.
"I got the shipment,"
or "we got the shipment?"
What are you
talking about?
Traffic cams in the area picked up
pictures of you and Toretto together.
Listen to me, O'Conner. Bring in
the shipment and bring in Toretto.
But I thought the point was to get
Braga. We got an opportunity here.
Brian, the clock
stopped ticking.
Bring them in.
Are we clear?
O'Conner?
So this is what
$60 million looks like.
Yeah, we got to
get you to a doctor.
We got to find
a place to hide this.
I got a spot.
502, wet reckless.
I need a 48-hour hold.
Out back.
Any spot you can find.
You sure about this?
Yeah. The last place they'll check,
their own impound yard. Trust me.
You know,
I've been thinking,
when you blew up your car back
there, you blew up mine, too.
Yeah?
Yeah.
So now you owe me
a 10-second car.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Now we're even.
Is this your way of
keeping me away from him?
You're the only one I could
call. He's my brother, of course.
The bullet's not in there.
I'm gonna clean it and stitch
it up. It's going to hurt.
I bet you're going
to enjoy this.
A little.
Want some of this?
Yeah.
It's spicy.
I like it hot.
Dom, what are you doing?
You reached first,
you have to say grace.
Thank you, Lord,
for blessing this table.
With food, family
and friendship.
You asked me
why I let Dom go.
I think it's because
at that moment,
I respected him
more than I did myself.
Yeah.
One thing I learned from Dom is that nothing
really matters unless you have a code.
And what's your code,
Brian?
I'm working on it.
Shit. Hey, Dom.
When were you gonna tell
me? Dom, what are you doing?
When were you gonna tell me
you were running Letty?
Let me explain...
When were you gonna...
Dom, stop!
You don't understand.
I don't understand?
Stop!
She did it for...
Dom, stop!
Dom, stop it!
Please stop!
She did it for you, Dom!
She did it for you!
Letty came to me to clear your name
in exchange for bringing down Braga.
She just wanted you
to come home!
I'm sorry, Dom!
I'm sorry!
You better have one hell of an
explanation. You disobeyed a direct order.
Where's the shipment?
It's safe.
Look, we could use the shipment
to parade in front of the media,
get a few hundred pounds
of heroin off the street,
but Braga's just gonna send another
shipment next week and the week after that.
Let's use the shipment
to lure Braga out
and lop the head off
a multi-billion dollar cartel.
And how do you
suggest we do that?
A hand-to-hand
exchange with Braga.
He'll never show.
He can't afford not to.
You got a plan?
There's a price.
We bag Braga,
you let Toretto walk.
Yes?
It's Dom.
I was just
thinking about you.
You know, when I gave you my
number, I was hoping you'd call.
But not under
these circumstances.
What circumstances?
Me being alive?
Don't take it personally.
It's just business.
I got some business
of my own.
Get Campos.
It's them.
Uh-huh.
Was that how Braga inspires
loyalty? Killing his drivers?
One can always
find more drivers.
It's just good business.
I want to trade.
Braga doesn't negotiate.
Fine.
You explain to him how all of a sudden
$60 million worth of product disappears.
I know that can't
be good for business.
What do you want?
Six million cash,
delivered by Braga himself.
I don't like being shot at.
I ain't gonna put my neck out again
unless he's got something to lose, too.
He'll never go for it.
Either I deal with Braga,
or you do.
When and where?
Sir, players are onsite. Holding
positions at the perimeter.
All right. Listen up.
Everybody stay frosty.
We don't move a muscle until
O'Conner gives the signal.
When he gets the money,
you know what to do.
Well, the good news is,
when we get this guy,
you walk out of here
a free man.
Is that what
they told you?
Yeah, that's the deal.
You still put milk and
cookies out for Santa Claus?
Yeah.
Here.
In case things go shitty.
Just like old times?
Yeah.
You dropped something.
That's what you wanted, right? Dom...
He's harmless.
Don't worry about him.
And he's really
sorry about Letty.
Where's our stuff?
You mean the stuff that
used to be in here, right?
Well, you'll see it when we
see Braga. That was the deal.
No worries.
Braga keeps his word.
$2 million.
You get the rest
when I get my property.
Stasiak.
We got a match.
The fingerprint's
Braga's 100%.
Just waiting on facial
confirmation via fax.
I got
a question for you.
You wearing pink when you were
clawing your way out of el barrio?
Order all agents
to move in.
We got confirmation. Primary
suspect wearing gray suit.
Let's move.
Sir, O'Conner hasn't
given us the signal yet.
What part of that didn't you understand?
We just got confirmation. Do it!
FBl AGENT: Secure primary
suspect in gray suit. Repeat!
Secure primary suspect
in gray suit.
You're thinking what
I'm thinking, right?
He ain't Braga.
Oh, shit.
Drop your weapons!
FBl!
Get down!
Get out of here!
Get out of here, Dom!
Run him down.
Go!
Campos is Braga!
Come on.
Approaching primary target.
Primary suspect is secure.
He was under your nose
the whole time.
Now Braga's escaped.
Toretto's heading south, probably
long across the border by now.
Do you have any idea the kind
of trouble you're in, O'Conner?
I was doing my job.
He ain't the first bad guy you
helped escape the law's grasp.
As of now, you're being
taken off active duty,
until this house can
mount a formal inquiry.
What about Braga?
That's no longer
your concern.
We now know where Braga is, right?
Customs tracked him via satellite
to his home base in Tecali, Mexico.
Mexico is out
of our jurisdiction.
The fact is
the brass will be so busy holding
press conferences over the seizure,
we'll skate
under the radar.
I thought we signed on
to do the right thing.
Everyone's looking for you.
I'm right here.
It's nice to see you've
gone with the times
and switched to electronic
fuel injection. Looks good.
Buster became a gearhead.
I'm going with you.
I don't plan on
bringing anyone back.
I know.
Hit that throttle.
Hey.
How do you say goodbye
to your only brother?
You don't.
I thought you weren't
gonna show up.
You saved my life.
I'm willing to
return the favor.
This will help
get you to Braga.
Dom.
Going in there
is suicide.
I have no choice.
You must have
loved her very much.
So this is where
my jurisdiction ends.
And this is where
mine begins.
You ain't forgiven.
You boys want
to arrest me?
No, we're beyond that.
You can't buy your way out of this one.
You and me...
You and me,
we're not so different.
You're no hero.
You're right.
And that's why you're going
back across the border.
But Fenix is mine.
You got it.
Shit!
You'll make it a couple of
miles out, if you're lucky.
You know where
you're going?
You want to borrow my GPS?
Where are your boys at?
Are they going
to show up or what?
Careful what you ask for.
Just stop.
Just stop the car.
Right behind you.
Dom, head to the tunnel.
Let's use the tunnel.
Get out of here, Brian.
You sure you know where
the tunnels are? You sure?
Yeah. I'd hold on.
This might hurt.
You're in
my world now, baby!
That's it, baby!
End of the road.
Now what?
Game over.
No, no, no.
Come on!
Hey!
Get me out of here!
Pussy.
Let me see that.
Yeah.
Just keep pressure there.
You'll be all right.
You gotta get
out of here.
I ain't running anymore.
I gotta ask you
something.
Yeah?
You know I would have won that
race if you didn't cheat, right?
You hit your head hard.
Don't make me laugh.
All rise.
Please be seated.
Please rise,
Mr. Toretto.
I've listened
to the testimony
and taken into
special consideration
Agent O'Conner's appeal of
clemency on behalf of Mr. Toretto.
That his actions directly
resulted in the apprehension
of known drug
trafficker Arturo Braga.
However,
this judiciary
finds that
one right does not make up
for a lifetime worth of wrongs.
And as such,
I find that I am forced to level the
maximum sentence under California law.
Dominic Toretto,
you are hereby sentenced
to serve 25 years to life
at the Lompoc maximum
security prison system
without the possibility
of early parole.
This court is adjourned.
Here's what we know so far.
This is all the aftermath of a daring,
daylight breakout.
There were 26 high-risk inmates
being transferred...
A daring midday breakout where everyone
onboard has been accounted for,
except for one, Dominic Toretto.
Police have just released the identity
of the man they believe to have orchestrated
the shocking escape
that amazingly resulted in no
fatalities this afternoon.
He is former federal agent, Brian O'Conner.
A fierce manhunt is underway
for three fugitives tonight.
Multiple federal and local agencies
have joined forces
in the search for Dominic Toretto
and his accomplices Brian O'Conner
and Mia Toretto.
But despite every eye in the country
looking for them
where Toretto and O'Conner
are now is anyone's guess.
It's got to be it, right?
Let's get out of here.
Whoa, whoa.
Easy, friends.
She's with me.
Mia.
Vince.
Buster.
Come on.
Dom here yet?
No.
When was the last time you heard from him?
A couple of weeks ago.
Up in Ecuador somewhere.
How does it feel? What's that?
To be on the other side of a wanted poster?
He will show up.
Yeah.
Dom's?
Time for bed little one.
Can I bring him?
Of course.
Aw.
Good night.
Excuse me, sorry.
Why Rio, Vince?
You mean after
you screwed everything up in LA?
Ended up free-falling through
South America, you know,
hitting every hellhole on the way down.
Would have kept on going if not for Rosa.
Does he know?
So, listen.
There is a job coming up.
I was hoping Dom was going to be here by now
but this one is clean enough
we can do it without him.
It's a good gig.
Couple of high-end cars, easy targets.
Guy I know is putting together
a team to swipe them.
Just need a few more willing bodies.
I don't know.
Look, the way the car scene is down here
we can unload them quick and get top dollar.
It's easy money.
And from where I am sitting,
it looks like you both could use the payday.
What are you reading?
Travel guide.
Yeah?
Tokyo.
Moscow.
Goa.
You want to know what all of these
places have in common?
Huh?
No extradition.
Here we go.
Excuse me, buddy.
Okay.
Hey, we have found them.
Yeah, second-to-the-last freighter.
What is it?
DEA tags. These cars have been seized.
Look who showed up.
God, I am so happy you're okay.
I thought I told you to lay low.
Been running on fumes. Had to make a call.
Hey. Quit talking.
We only got the two-minute window.
Let's go, Vince.
I am taking the GT40.
Ladies first.
Hey.
This car suits me better.
See you, baby.
It's okay...
we're all going to the same place.
We will get the car there.
Change of plans. Wait for my call.
Let's go.
Where is she going?
Where is she going? Hey.
Hey.
We're being robbed. Whatever
happens, don't stop the train.
Go after the girl.
Hurry up.
Access card. Get the access card.
Shit.
Bridge. There is a bridge.
Luggage car is clear.
Freeze.
Oh, shit.
You had to make a call, huh?
Shitty call, O'Conner.
Shitty call.
You two stirred up quite a
bit of trouble today.
Three of my men dead.
Three DEA agents along with them.
Of course, this is business
and sometimes things go astray.
All I care about is the car.
Tell me where it is,
and I will let you go.
This roofing plastic says you're
full of shit.
I don't know how you guys do business
in your part of the world,
but here in Rio,
I like it when all parties
know what they're up against.
That's funny.
Because it goes both ways.
You know,
I hear your sister is very beautiful.
Wherever she hides
I will find her.
The American fugitives killed three DEA
agents during a train robbery...
...police warn they are armed
and extremely dangerous.
Anyone with information should contact
law enforcement immediately...
Mia?
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah, you all right?
Hey.
Hey, yeah.
Just like a Toretto.
Where's Vince?
That's a good question.
He will be here.
Guys, we're all over the news.
They're blaming us for the killing
of those DEA agents on the train.
Which means we just jumped
to the top of the wanted list.
The feds have got to show everyone
their agents are off limits
and they're going to send their best
guys. We got to get out of here.
One thing we know for sure
is that they wanted this car.
Because something is in it.
If we find out what it is, we will
know what we're up against.
All right, listen up. The men
we're after are professional runners.
They like speed and are guaranteed to
go down the hardest possible way
so make sure you got your funderwear on.
We find them, we take them as a
team, and we bring them back.
And above all else, we don't ever,
ever let them get into cars.
Crime scene is 10 hours old and
counting, men. Let's go hunting.
Agente Hobbs.
Chief of Police, João Almeida.
Luke.
Sorry to hear about the loss of your men.
Is all this really necessary
to apprehend two men?
Let me tell you something about these two men.
One is a former federal officer, been
in deep cover for five years.
He knows every way
you're going to come for him.
The other one is a professional
criminal, escaped prison twice,
spent half his life on the
run avoiding folks like you.
Well, if there's anything
we can do to help the DSS...
Two things. One, I need a translator.
We have plenty in the
public relations department.
Elena Neves.
A patrol officer? You heard me.
But why? We have many more experienced people.
I like her smile.
What's the second thing?
Stay the fuck out of my way.
Brian. Hm?
I have something I have to tell you.
God damn.
What a mess.
Where you been, man?
You better check that tone.
And you just better answer the goddamn question.
Stop it. Both of you.
Where were you, Vince?
Guys all over the favelas asking about you.
Couldn't get out of there without
leading them straight to you.
Had to wait them out.
That is such horseshit.
That was your job,
and those were your guys. Hey.
Hey. Enough, O'Conner.
If he said he didn't do it, he didn't do it.
Go walk it off.
Look, I would love to expand
my operations into your countries
but, quite frankly, your business
methods are too violent.
Let me tell you a true story.
Five hundred years ago, the Portuguese
and the Spanish came here,
each trying to get the country
from their natives.
The Spaniards arrived, guns blazing,
determined to prove who was boss.
The natives killed every single Spaniard.
Personally,
I prefer the methods of the Portuguese.
They came bearing gifts.
Mirrors, scissors, trinkets.
Things that the natives
couldn't get on their own,
but to continue receiving them, they
had to work for the Portuguese.
And that's why all Brazilians
speak Portuguese today.
Now, if you dominate the people with violence,
they will eventually fight back because
they have nothing to lose.
And that's the key.
I go into the favelas and give them
something to lose.
Electricity, running water,
school rooms for their kids.
And for that taste of a better life,
I own them.
Gentlemen.
I apologize for the interruption.
Senor Reyes, may I speak with you?
We have found them.
Pardon me, gentlemen.
Almost wish I didn't see that.
Almost.
Wait, Dom.
Mia was on that train.
My sister.
I didn't know.
I wouldn't do anything to hurt her.
You set up the deal.
I thought the job was for the cars.
I didn't know.
All they want is the chip.
Damn.
You should have come clean.
What's going on out here?
Nothing.
Please, Dom, just let me have the
chip. I can take this to them.
They will give it to
Reyes and set things right.
Get out.
What?
You never listen to me.
Not when I told you he was a cop,
and not now.
You never trust me and
look where it's gotten us.
Look at our family now.
I can't go home.
Your sister is stuck in this life.
Where's Letty, Dom?
Where's Letty?
Plasma cutter.
Wilkes, I want a list of every
place within 50 miles
that distributes compressed gas tanks.
Pass me that manifest.
Officer Neves. Been waiting for you.
You asked for me? I did.
May I ask why?
My smile is not that great.
Your husband was an officer who
was gunned down in the favela.
Six months later,
you upped and joined the force.
You're motivated.
Plus, I figure you're the only one
in Rio who can't be bought.
Am I right?
Yes. Of course I am.
Good news, bad news.
You know I like my dessert first.
Back-checked the rail line like you asked.
Found a couple of spots
where they unloaded the cars.
One set of tracks headed west
until it hit the main highway,
then disappeared.
But another set of tracks headed east.
A 107-inch wheelbase,
eight-and-a-half-inch tread.
The GT40 that was missing from the manifest.
Followed the trail a couple of miles.
Pretty easy in this scrub.
Can't move without leaving a sign.
Give me the damn veggies.
The ground rolls into a hardpack
and we lost that track, too.
Not necessarily.
That road heads up through the
hills into the favelas.
Couple of years ago,
it was washed out by a storm.
It's all dirt a mile from where you were.
If they headed that way, we will
pick up their tracks there.
You come prepared.
I am motivated.
All right, then.
Let's find ourselves a car.
What do you think?
Well, it's definitely a custom chip.
Look at all these side menus
here for data entry.
Let's check this one.
Look at that.
Same building, same order every week.
It's a delivery schedule.
What's this?
Drugs?
No. That's a dealer pack.
See, most major players,
they weigh their money
so they don't have to constantly count it.
Right there, that's 49 kilos.
49 kilos is a million in twenties.
You're saying each one of these shipments
is worth 10 million dollars?
Yeah.
I thought so.
So what is that?
A 100-million plus in cash houses?
That's how he keeps it off the grid.
I think it's safe to say that Reyes
is smart to want this back.
It's his whole network right there,
just laid out on a chip.
Wilkes, Fusco, up the middle.
Mac, Chato, flank north.
What about me?
Stay here.
Go that way.
The other two went over the wall.
Come on, go. Go.
Get on the ground.
I got Toretto. Four blocks north of your...
They already know who you are.
Let's go.
You okay here?
Yeah. I am good. Thank you.
They're going to be looking for
the three of us together now.
We need to split up.
You and Mia head south,
I will lead them away.
No.
Dom is right.
Look how lucky we just got.
What happens next time?
We have no choice but to split up.
I am pregnant.
I already lost my family once.
I am not going through that again.
Are you kidding me? No.
I am not going anywhere. Okay?
Dom?
Promise me we stick together.
I promise.
Our family just got bigger.
Something doesn't add up.
Toretto and O'Conner.
They stay when they're supposed to run,
they steal gas then give it away?
Now they're killing federal agents?
It doesn't make any sense.
Here's what makes sense.
All these guys are is names on a list.
They come up, we take them down.
Not a phone call more, not a bullet less.
Wilkes, we get anything?
Standard forensics.
Shoe prints. Hair and fiber.
Prints are all over the car.
Anything else?
Yeah,
we tracked the owner off the vehicle ID.
There are a couple of shell
companies in between,
but we finally traced it back
to a corporation
owned by an investor
down here named Hernan Reyes.
Investor?
If there's anything illegal happening
in Rio, Reyes is involved.
Okay, then so are we.
If he could get us any closer to our
guys, I want everything on him.
Chato, you're on the roof.
I want you on overwatch in case somebody
comes back for something.
Mac, give me a cross-check on Reyes,
full specs.
If he goes to the john, I want to know
how many times he shakes it.
You got it, boss. Wilkes, Fusco.
Let's put all this mess back together.
That's going to take a while.
Then you better get started.
They were taking this car apart for a reason.
Let's put it back together
and find out what's missing.
Hey, Dom,
what do you remember about your father?
My father.
He used to...
He used to have a barbecue
every Sunday after church.
For anybody in the neighborhood.
If you didn't go to church,
you didn't get any barbecue.
Every single day he was in the
shop, and every single night,
he was at the kitchen table with Mia,
helping her with her homework.
Even after she went to sleep,
he'd stay up for a few more hours
so he could learn the next chapter
and help her the next day.
I remember everything about my father.
Everything.
That's just it.
I don't remember shit about my dad.
I don't remember him yelling.
I don't remember him smiling.
To be honest with you, I don't even
remember what the hell he looked like.
I don't remember. He just...
He was just never there.
You ain't going to be like that, Brian.
We can't keep running, Dom.
We got to get out.
We got to get out now.
You're right.
Here's how we're going to do it.
We're going to use this.
We're going do one last job.
We're going to take all of Reyes' money.
Every dime of it,
and disappear.
Forever.
New passports.
New lives with no more
looking over our shoulder.
And we're just going to buy our freedom.
That's right.
You realize we're talking
about going up against
the most powerful guy in all of Rio?
Yes, we are.
Then we're going to need a team.
Let's run through the bases real quick.
Who do we got?
First we're going to need a chameleon.
Someone who can blend in anywhere.
What else?
A fast talker.
Someone who can bullshit their
way out of anything.
I got that.
This guy is going to have
a lot of surveillance.
We're going to need someone
who's good with circuits.
And with those circuits,
Reyes is going to have walls.
We're going to need guys to
punch through those walls.
What else?
Utilities and weapons.
Someone who ain't afraid to throw down.
Someone to back up every position.
Yeah, what else do we need?
Most importantly,
we're going to need two precision drivers.
Guys that don't crack under pressure.
Guys that never lose.
You know we got that.
Aw, hell, no.
I see they really scraped the bottom
of the barrel, huh?
I guess they did, since your ass is here.
When are you going to give Martin
Luther King his car back?
As soon as you give Rick
James his jacket back.
What's up, man? What's up?
Hmm.
Sexy legs, baby girl.
What time do they open?
They open the same time
as I pull this trigger.
Want me to open them?
I told you the skinny chick had balls.
Looks like she started the party without us.
Hey, anybody can talk shit in Spanish, homie.
What's this guy saying?
Ugly is still ugly in Spanish or in English.
Who are these clowns, man? Circus clowns.
I thought cockfights were illegal in Brazil.
I see you all have met.
You know when you called me to come to Rio
I assumed it would be for something
more exciting than this.
Look at this guy.
Long time. I missed you, man.
Good to see you.
Brother. What's up?
Yo, check this out. This is Tej.
Best circuit man on the East Coast.
And this is my boy, Roman Pearce.
We go way back, I met this guy in juvie.
I pulled that job with him in Miami.
I have heard about you.
Nice digs.
Yeah, well, the Ritz was sold out.
So what's this all about, Dom?
Yeah, man, why did you drag
us halfway around the world?
Because we got a job.
All right,
so our target's name is Hernan Reyes.
And he runs the drug scene down here.
He's never been busted because
he doesn't leave a paper trail.
No paper trail means no banks.
And no banks means cash houses.
That's right. Ten of them, to be exact.
Spread throughout the city.
And we're going to hit them all.
All of them?
All of them.
That sounds crazy.
You bring us to a whole other country
so we can rob the dude who runs it?
I thought this was business.
Sounds personal to me.
Is that what this is?
I got love for you all,
but personal ain't good business.
I can't do this, homie.
So what we're talking about is $100 million.
You say what?
Hundred...
See, sometimes I be over thinking, man,
and I know we just met, but
you just, kind of, got to...
That's right, $100 million,
and everything we take,
we split even.
That's a little over $11 million apiece.
I am down.
I am in.
Eleven million.
Sounds like a whole lot of
vaginal activity to me.
You can't pull off 10 heists
on the same mark.
You just can't.
As soon as we hit the first one,
they're going to do everything
they can to protect the rest.
Exactly.
Nobody move.
That's all of it.
You a dead man.
You're all dead men.
You don't have a place to hide.
Who's hiding?
Are you crazy?
Do you know whose house this is?
Whose money are you stealing?
We ain't stealing it.
You tell your boss exactly who did this.
Tell him there's more coming.
Voila.
Turn it over.
She's running on all eight.
Checks out fine.
Keep looking.
Boss, if something was missing, we'd know.
It's a goddamn shame putting
bullshit like that on a classic.
You may as well slap neon lights on it.
They took the chip.
We got a hit on the police scanner.
Armed robbery at a house in Leblon.
Address cross-checks against property
owned by one of Hernan Reyes' corporations.
All right, if that's our guys
then whatever was on that chip
led them directly to that house.
It's them, for sure.
How do you know that?
Because no one else in Rio is
stupid enough to rob Reyes.
Explain.
They invaded the Leblon house.
Who invaded?
The men from the train.
How much did they take?
They didn't take anything.
They burned it.
They burned my money?
Yes. And said there's more coming.
Okay...
Then this...
...is what we're going to do.
Clean the houses.
I want that money under lock and key...
...within an hour.
Understand?
Understood.
Number one is on the move, man.
Two is on the move.
I got mine.
I got eyes on Five.
I know you all said they were consolidating
the money somewhere, but,
you all ain't going to believe this.
Well, this job just got a lot harder.
If he's moving it into a police station
he's got some serious brass in his pocket.
Looks like this is going to be a
shorter trip than I thought...
Hell, yeah, we can't do this.
"Can't?" You mean, "shouldn't. "
I think this doesn't change a thing.
I say we stick to the plan.
You say what?
This just went from Mission: Impossible
to Mission: In-freaking-sanity.
Whatever, man.
I ain't scared, I am just letting you
all know, going in that building is crazy.
I got this.
What time was the robbery?
Around 11:00.
Here we go.
Enhance it.
Their faces are covered.
Run it through FRS.
Well, hello, you son of a bitch.
Wilkes. Run the photos of known associates
of Toretto and O'Conner
against customs entries into
Brazil in the last two weeks.
Check planes, trains, boats, everything
short of the goddamn space shuttle.
They can change their names but
they can't change their faces.
Something big is going down.
That's a 1970 Charger.
Fusco. Upload these specs into the database.
Have the computer cross-check
it with overhead satellites
every 15 minutes, the van behind it, too.
If these vehicles move in the streets
of Rio, I want to know about it.
Everything okay?
Everything is okay.
Who is this Hobbs? This Federal
Agent running around town?
Some American cowboy.
He's handled.
He killed sixteen of our men.
Handle him better.
Look... He requested a rookie
patrol officer as his assistant.
They won't be a problem.
It's all here? Yes.
What about Toretto and O'Conner?
Where are they?
Nothing yet.
But I have all our officers searching.
Not good enough.
Put a price on their heads.
High enough...
...to get every pair of eyes in
the city searching for them.
The beauty of public offices?
Public records.
This is where he's keeping the money.
The vault in the evidence room.
Um. Uh, yeah. Can I get everyone's
attention, right here, for a second?
We're talking about breaking
into a police station.
Is anyone listening to those words?
Anybody? Popo?
Five-O. One-time. Pigs.
People we don't like.
You know, police stations are designed
to keep people in, not out.
That's why it's a stealth mission.
We will be in and out before they
even know we were there.
Well, we will need to get eyes in there.
At least to find out the make
and model of that vault.
So the vault and then, so...
It's crazy.
Who's supposed to do all this?
What do you mean?
Why me?
Because you got the biggest mouth.
That's for damn sure.
Ooh.
Hello, beautiful.
Look at those dimples. Sexy, sexy.
Love those glasses.
Where did you get them from?
Are those like Gucci frames or something?
No English?
No, no, no. Damn.
How are you, sir?
Special Agent O'Conner. US Federal
Bureau of Investigation.
It says Caucasian.
That's a tan. You know, a tan?
Look, I am working this case and I got
some evidence here to be held.
But I need to get in and check
your storage facility first.
Nope.
Look, I know you're a true professional,
and I respect you, I promise.
You know, it looks like you
work out a little bit, too.
What do you bench, about 350?
Ah, shit.
Look, I am just trying to do my job, man.
My boss sent me here to just make
sure that everything was safe.
It will be safe.
Let me just come in and take a quick peek.
Nope.
Come on, man. Hook a brother up, please?
Nope. And you're not my brother.
Brother from another mother?
Look. No one enters the facility but
authorized evidence personnel.
Now stop wasting my time.
I am going to call the embassy.
No, no, no. No, we're good.
We don't need to call them.
For what? We're good.
Here, I got the box. We're all good.
I promise you.
Thank you so much for your time.
Swear to God, if you were on
the other side of that glass
I'd bust your damn face in.
Now translate that.
It's done. See, I think I make a better
special agent than you ever did.
Well, that depends on how you define "special. "
Come on, now. Let's see what we got.
Not funny.
All right, come on.
Dawg, you still can't drive.
Now, I see why you're always
getting into accidents.
You can't even drive a
damn remote control car.
I am going to need you to shut up right now.
I am not going to shut up. Shut up.
Strap him in his safety belt, man.
Give me the remote, dawg. Go left.
It looks like something right over
there to the left. What is that?
What is that?
Bingo.
What is that, six-by-six?
Eight-by-twelve.
Seven-by-twelve.
Fitted with 18-inch-thick steel
reinforced walls...
...with a insulated copper core to
protect against thermal lance.
A Class-3 electronic lock with
a surefire Griffin retumbler
and a biometric palm scanner.
Ten tons of top-of-the-line security.
Do I want to know how you know all that?
I had a life before you knew me, O'Conner.
Let's just leave it at that, all right?
She is a beauty, though, man.
A "beauty" as in "good?"
"Beauty" as in, she's going to
start off playing hard to get.
Then, no matter how much I caress her,
no matter how much I love her,
in the end, she still
ain't going to give up that ass.
Two to one says you blow the wrong pipe.
Yo, why you got to be so negative
all the time, man?
I ain't negative.
I am just positive you're going to mess it up.
I am telling you, man, you got issues.
Next time if there's no elevator,
I am not coming.
You need to learn to relax, loco.
You better hurry up,
we got less than a minute.
Why do you always set the timer so short?
I hope you know where you're going.
I got this. Relax, man.
Relax.
...a police station.
You used too much explosive. Again.
Too much, too little...
It's all the same.
That's some Buddha shit you learned from
a book in the prison library, isn't it?
And what you're doing there on the wall...
You got that from the same book, huh?
You're so negative, bro.
Can I have some light?
Got it. We got it.
Yeah, we're looking at four cameras.
Yo, that's some high-end shit, too.
Marker optics.
Hundred-degree field-of-view.
Ten seconds oscillation.
Yeah, that's a narrow window, man.
Can't we just tap in and replace the image?
No, it's hooked into a digital sync.
They would know we were in the system.
The best we can do is peek.
We're going to need some real
fast cars to get through this.
Not just fast.
You got a hard right and a hairpin.
We're going to need something agile.
You guys mock up a track.
O'Conner.
Let's go get some cars.
Nice.
Home sweet home.
Or that.
How about that?
All motor, no tuning issues.
I always wanted one of those.
Held the record on the
Avenida three years running.
Damn, bro...
You got a lot of balls to bring
your problems here, Toretto.
Not to mention a cop.
Yeah, we can keep that on the low.
Word on the street is a lot of people
are looking for you two.
What?
You didn't think we'd recognize you?
No, we're kind of counting on it.
That little coupe may
run the streets around here,
but that monster has never
seen a set of tail lights.
Ever. Well, she's about to.
Dominic Toretto's ride in my garage.
Now that... will be a nice trophy.
Let's go, legend.
Car for car.
Car for car?
You want it, come and get it.
Let's see what they got.
Really?
Where did you get that from? Papa Smurf?
Okay, O'Conner, give it your best shot.
How was that one?
Camera caught you.
What? Yeah, it still caught you.
Man, I was milking the hell
out of that thing, too.
We're going to need a faster car.
I want my money. Come on, man.
Yeah.
Let's get it. Watch this.
That's exactly why your
ass ain't been driving.
I think I am in love.
That was real solid work.
I think Camera 3 still caught you, though.
Let's do it again.
That's the piggy bank you ordered.
You're kidding me. Yep.
Where in the hell
did you all get one of these?
Well, we had a life before you met us.
All right, I will get to work
on the electronic tumbler
but there's still another problem.
Palm scanner.
And without Reyes' handprint,
Houdini himself couldn't open this bitch.
How do you know it's Reyes' handprint?
You got $100 million in a safe.
You going to put somebody
else's handprint on it?
Now there you
go with that negativity, man.
That shit is eating you alive.
You check that.
Yo, check that. Shut up.
How are we supposed to get Reyes' handprint?
Han.
You're up.
Sure. Nothing like the easy stuff.
Let's go. I will drive.
I make six bodyguards. Seven.
You think that guy with a
fanny pack is a tourist?
So, how long were you in the army?
That gun you pulled the other
day was a Jericho 941.
Thumb-racking the slide?
That was straight-up Mossad.
I got out of the military
probably the same time you quit smoking.
The amount of chips you eat,
the way you always have to keep
your hands and mouth busy,
you were a two-pack-a-day man for sure.
Unfiltered.
Well, this is a bust.
We're not going to be able to
get his fingerprints out here.
We need to do some more recon,
call in a couple of extra guys.
Or
you don't send a man to do a woman's job.
We're going to figure this out,
I promise you.
What's up?
I thought you were more of a thong man.
We got the print.
Where?
Okay, that's crazy.
So, did he just slap that ass or
did he grab and hold on to it?
Hey, this will work.
I am impressed.
Got it?
Got it.
But you still didn't answer the question.
Oh, no. Guys, guys.
Guys, we have a problem.
The whole team just got burnt.
Now we're all wanted.
How did this happen?
US Diplomatic Security Service
issued the warrants.
Agent L. Hobbs.
Hold on one second.
Hey, Dom.
Is that the guy you saw in the favela?
Yeah.
Hobbs is the leader of the elite
task force for the DSS.
So he's good.
When the FBI wants to find somebody,
that's who they call.
Because he never misses his mark.
This guy is Old Testament.
Blood, bullets, wrath of God.
That's his style.
And right now he's hunting us?
Dom, we got to move up our timeline.
Yeah, but how?
This thing's already been difficult
without Wyatt Earp on our asses.
If anything, we need more room to breathe.
Roman's right.
Think we need to get some fresh air.
We have got a hit. '70s Charger.
Let's get a move on.
Eastbound on Avenida Atlantica.
Move, move, move, move.
It stopped about a block ahead.
Park it. We're going on foot.
Hey, Toretto.
You're under arrest.
Arrest?
I don't feel like I am under arrest.
How about you, Brian?
No, not a bit.
Not even a little bit.
Just give it a minute. It will sink in.
We didn't kill those feds. That was Reyes.
I don't give a shit.
I am just here to bring in two assholes
whose names hit my desk.
Yeah, that sounds like a real hero.
That's funny.
From a guy who took the oath of a cop,
then went against everything it stood for.
Or some wannabe tough guy prick
who beat a man half to death with
a socket wrench.
Yeah, real tough.
You turn around and put your
hands behind your back.
I don't think so.
Your mistake is thinking you
got a goddamn choice, boy.
And your mistake?
Thinking you're in America.
You're a long way from home.
This is Brazil.
Come on, boss. Another day.
Come on, H, it's a lot of heat.
I will see you soon, Toretto.
I look forward to it, cop.
Yep.
Tracker's on.
Got them.
I don't understand. Why come here?
Why risk it all for $20 worth of silver?
Because it's worth it.
You should run, you know.
Hobbs will find you.
You have every reason to leave.
Why stay?
Why do you?
My husband was a good police officer.
An honest man.
We both grew up here.
Two years ago he was murdered
in the street...
...right outside our door.
Reyes owns this favela now.
He gives things to people.
But everything has a price.
The people here need a new start.
They need to be free.
You didn't kill those men in the train,
did you?
Now, why would you believe anything
I would tell you?
Hey.
Was she so special to you?
I never thought
anyone could understand how much.
But you do.
Yeah.
Close, but not enough.
Dom, the window is too small, man.
Only way we're going to beat the
cameras is with invisible cars.
And I know just where to get them.
Let's take a ride, boys.
Don't hurt yourself.
It's been a while since I have been
behind the wheel of one of these.
First time I have ever been in the front seat.
Rome, what took you so long?
I thought for sure you'd be showing up with
some chrome spinners or something.
Real funny.
I got $100,000 that says I can take
you all in the next quarter-mile.
Yeah, your broke ass has got a hundred grand.
If we pull off this job, I will.
The next two lights.
Hundred thousand.
We don't pull this job off,
we're probably dead anyway.
Let's make it a million.
I like that. All right,
a million-dollar quarter-mile.
All right, then.
You only live once. Let's do it.
What do you say, Dom?
We talking or we racing?
Just don't cheat this time.
Got to let that go.
Yeah.
Typical, Roman.
I am going to get this money.
I am hungry.
Don't make it too easy for me, boys.
No.
Not this time, Dom.
You got to want it, Brian.
Yeah. Owned you. Owned you.
Good race, O'Conner. Thanks, Dom.
Do you know how long
I have been waiting for that shit?
I told you he didn't see it.
Your man right there?
He let off the throttle at the line.
You didn't do nothing. He let you win.
Bullshit.
Vince, what are you doing? Quiet.
They have been tracking you.
I know she's here.
Find her.
Go. Go. Go.
It's okay. Wait.
Reyes' guys were waiting for me at the market.
Vince saved my life.
You hungry?
Yeah, sure. Good.
Because you're saying grace.
Thanks, Vince.
Yo, you burned it.
Yo, this is how my momma does it.
Relax.
Yeah, but your mom is
the worst cook in the world.
Yo, don't you be talking about my momma.
Yeah, come on, baby. Who's good living?
To you, bro. Cheers, cheers, cheers.
So, we in Brazil. It's the good life.
Yeah.
So, you got a little more than
$10 or $11 million coming.
What you going to do with your money?
Me? Yeah.
Actually, man, I been thinking about
opening up a garage back home.
Place where people can bring their cars
and not get completely ripped off.
You know what I mean?
Really? Yeah.
So, your dream is to start a day job?
That's stupid. Like, why would...
No, it's not stupid at all.
I love what I do.
That don't make no sense to me.
I know what I am going to do with my money.
Buying some cooking lessons for my man.
See? See?
There you go with that negativity, man.
You know me. Money ain't a goddamn thing.
It's going to take a little more than
money to learn how to cook.
That's horrible.
But I heard they was looking for a
chef down at this animal shelter.
You might want to...
I know the manager.
Hey, Dom.
Listen.
I know that you're all
set for this job tomorrow,
but if you need an extra man, I could...
You're in.
There's always room for family.
Thank you.
Get something to eat.
Yeah.
Can you believe Mia calls this a curse?
She might be right.
You really like doing that stuff, huh?
When your life is on the line that's
when you learn about yourself.
That's a fair deal.
We're less than 24 hours from the
biggest celebration of our life.
You all need a refill.
This is serious stuff.
No, I am good. Cheers, baby.
I am good. No, thank you.
No, she can't.
What do you mean? She can't.
What do you mean she can't?
What is...
Are you serious right now?
Is that the reason you let him
beat you in the quarter-mile?
That was a baby gift.
No, that's messed up.
No, you're not taking that from me.
Wait, wait, hold on a second.
So, did he just smack the ass or
did he grab and hold on to it?
Which one was it?
Congratulations. Thank you.
How can you keep this a secret?
Crazy, huh?
It's your boy.
Why would you keep something
like that away from me?
Baby gift, huh?
I have no idea what they're talking about.
Oh?
What happened to the pull-out method, man?
Toast. Toast.
Money will come and go. We know that.
But the most important thing in life will
always be the people in this room.
Right here.
Right now.
I am all set.
Yo, Santos. Van good?
You know we're always good, bro.
Hobbs is on the other side of the city.
We're not going to get a better window.
Okay, guys, it's show time.
First team in position, let's go.
Come on, let's do this.
Hey, Dom.
I got eyes on Mia.
Moscow, Bali, Goa, Hong Kong.
And what do they all have in common?
No extradition.
We're one hour away from the rest of our lives.
Yeah.
Cops.
Come on. Go.
You just made a big mistake.
Took me a while to find that tracking chip.
But not as long to flip the receiver.
You're going down, Toretto.
I am right here.
Dom. Stand back. I got this.
Pull off. Dom. Please, stop.
Dom.
Yeah.
We're coming in now.
Have the marshals meet us at
the airport when we land.
Ambush.
Wilkes, suppression fire. Shut them down.
Stagger-step. Cover me.
Watch them.
Cut us loose.
Come on. Cut us loose.
We're good? Yeah, let's go, let's go.
Hey, Dom.
You have got to meet my son.
Nico.
I will.
He's a good kid.
You know, we named him after you.
"Dominic. "
You have got my word, Vince.
You were always my brother.
I got eyes on Nico now.
We need to move.
We don't have that much time.
I got us a flight out.
We can leave Rio in the
rearview in the next five hours.
Not to run away.
To finish the job.
Are you crazy, Dom? We can't.
It's a suicide mission.
That's your man over there on the table.
The plan is busted.
This is bullshit, man.
Reyes knows we're coming.
He's right.
They tripled the detail at the police station.
It's going to be a wall of gunfire.
Reyes doesn't get away with this.
It's a trap, man.
You know that.
Dom, listen to them.
Run, before it's too late. Leave Rio.
You can be free.
Running ain't freedom.
You should know that.
You know you're all free to
make your own choices.
I am in.
I will ride with you, Toretto.
At least until we kill that son of a bitch.
So what's the plan, Dom?
We can't just go sneaking around anymore.
We don't sneak.
The only thing he cares about is his money.
We pull that,
we pull him.
See?
I called in every cop on our payroll.
We're covered.
We have got every entrance covered
with weapons teams.
God Himself couldn't get at your
money if He wanted to.
God isn't my worry.
You ready?
I am ready.
What's happening?
They're taking the vault.
What? The vault.
Follow me. Quickly.
Let me through.
Don't move.
Stay down.
Call it out, Mia.
You have got a straight shot for two blocks.
Go right. Got it.
Well, the plan is working.
You guys have every corrupt cop in Rio
on your tail. You have to move fast.
What's the best route?
Okay, keep going straight another
half-mile onto Rua Fonseca,
and then go left.
That ain't going to work.
Spikes ahead, Dom. We got spikes.
We're going right.
No, it's too tight, we're not going to fit.
We have got no choice. Now.
Shit.
Holy shit.
Guys, I am hearing all this chatter.
Did you just take out a bank?
Two inbound.
All right, there's an alley
coming up on your left.
Yeah, I got it.
You little bastard.
All right, good job, Dom. Right-hander,
right here, right-hander.
Guys, there's a big group coming
at you from the south.
You have to do something now.
Hey, go wide.
Yeah.
You're all clear on the left.
Good afternoon, officer.
License and registration, please.
Yes. This is big-boy stuff.
We're clear on the right.
Oh, man.
Thanks, guys.
Any time.
I will see you on the other side.
You guys just carved out a 10-second window.
Make it count.
Zizi, stay on them.
They can't outrun us on the bridge.
Shit.
They have no way out.
No.
There's too many of them.
Hey, there's too many of them.
We're not going to make it.
You're right, we aren't.
You are.
What are you talking about?
Just let the vault go.
Get out of there.
You're a father now, Brian.
No, I am not leaving you.
Now you stick with the plan.
It was always the plan.
Take care of Mia.
Dom, you listen to me now. Okay?
You cut loose right now.
Hey, what is he doing?
We have got him.
Close down the bridge.
Do something, asshole.
Kill him, damn it.
Kill him now.
I thought I told you to go on.
Yeah, I had to make a call.
Help me.
That's for my team, you son of a bitch.
It's a hell of a mess.
Yeah, it is.
You know I can't let you two go.
I ain't made that way.
The way I see it,
you have earned yourselves 24 hours.
The money stays, though.
If I were you, I'd use the time.
Make peace with whatever demons you got left.
Because come tomorrow,
I will find you.
Toretto.
I will see you soon.
No, you won't.
Come on, baby.
Don't be mean.
Come on.
"For Rosa and Nico. See you soon, Uncle Dom"
You sure about this?
You know I am.
You don't need to do this.
Just leave me alone.
Bro, I am not trying to be negative,
but casinos...
...are the kinds of places designed to
take money from guys like you and me.
When I win here I am buying you a lifetime
supply of antidepressants.
You don't put ten million on red.
Enough already.
You put it on black.
No more bets.
Right this way, my dear.
You stay right here,
I will be right back.
So, this is your dream, huh?
It's enough for me, man.
I take it that's your dream.
Absolutely. What up, boy?
What's going on?
You good? Yes, yes.
You know what's crazy?
There's only four of those cars
in the whole world.
Yeah, I got the only one in the
Western Hemisphere.
I made a sheikh in Abu Dhabi
an offer he could not refuse.
Huh.
That's a nice lady you got there, too.
Absolutely. What's happening?
We got to go, man. Let's do this.
Okay, I will drive.
In that? Come on, man, no way.
No, no. Not in this.
In that.
Are you serious right now?
Man, this is crazy.
Yes, I guess that means there are two
in the Western Hemisphere, huh?
What's your smart ass got to say now?
You know what?
We can always shine together, baby.
Get dressed, man, we got things to do.
So, where to now?
I don't know.
Never been to Madrid.
I thought you wanted to go to Tokyo.
We will get there.
Eventually.
Nice surprise.
Crazy, right?
This is the happiest
I have ever seen my sister.
It's because we're free.
You know, I want another shot.
Yeah?
Yeah.
No wagers, nobody else.
Just you and me, once and for all.
You sure you can handle the disappointment?
Are you?
All right, O'Conner.
Let's see what you got.
Señor O'Conner, señor O'Conner!
It's okay, you're just in time.
You're going to be a great father, Brian.
What makes you so sure?
Because I'll be there to kick your ass if you ain't.
Get in there.
Go.
Brian.
Remember, the second you go through those doors,
everything changes.
Our old life is done.
You need to look at that.
Berlin, 3:00 a. m. this morning.
A team of drivers hijacked a military convoy.
Toretto? Nope.
I ain't interested.
Yes, you are. Keep looking.
Do you believe in ghosts?
Special Agent Hobbs?
Riley Hicks.
I read your file. Top
of your class at FLETC.
Cairo, Tunis.
Youngest RSO ever in Afghanistan.
Hell, if you're half as good as you are on paper,
we're going to get along just fine.
A Russian military caravan attacked,
satellite component stolen.
Cars just came out of nowhere.
Six hospitalized, a dozen vehicles destroyed.
All that in under 90 seconds, in and out.
This is world-class.
Job this good, there's only one crew in the world
who could get this done.
How the hell did that get up there?
They caught one.
Where?
I got you five minutes with this guy.
I only need two.
I want your boss.
Where's Shaw?
I ain't telling you shit.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Is that legal?
No.
But are you going to go in there and tell him?
I've got rights, you asshole!
Not today.
No, no!
Well, is he talking?
Not anymore.
That room is bugged, Hobbs.
So, any information you just beat
out of him, Interpol has now.
Great. Now they can take the morning off.
Shaw's in London.
Let's go pick him up.
Woman, you just don't pick up
Owen Shaw like he's groceries.
If you want to catch wolves, you need wolves.
Let's go hunting.
This is what 100 million buys?
It wasn't that hard to find you, Toretto.
I wasn't hiding.
How's the life of the retired international criminal?
I like it here.
It's quiet.
Nice weather,
and no extradition.
So what are you doing here, cop?
Last Tuesday, a team of highly coordinated drivers
took down an entire military convoy in Russia.
I don't do cold weather.
I know it wasn't you.
But you're going to help me catch the team responsible.
And you ain't gonna need that.
You can't touch him, Hobbs.
You've got no powers...
I'm not here to extradite anyone.
See, he's going to come voluntarily.
As a matter of fact,
he's going to beg me.
This was taken a week ago.
I'll see you out front.
It's Letty, isn't it?
It's impossible.
If that was my husband, if there
was a chance, no matter how small,
I would go.
I'm going to need everything, all the info you got.
You'll get it when the team gets it.
No team.
This is going to have to be me alone.
It's not that simple.
The crew we're after, they hit like
thunder and disappear like smoke.
You go in alone, you won't ever touch them.
I've been chasing this guy across
four continents and 12 countries,
and believe me, the last damn place I want to be right now
is on your front doorstep, selling Girl Scout cookies.
I need your help, Dom.
I need your team.
Okay, ladies, bring it in.
Listen, I want to make a toast.
Come on.
Listen, I know a few of y'all have already been to Macau,
but you have never seen the town
till you've seen it through my eyes.
We got a penthouse suite
with an ocean view that's going to change your life.
150-foot yacht with
a helicopter pad...
Mmm-hmm. Safe to say, you're about
to have the time of your lives.
No, you are.
Cheers.
Nice!
I'm a citizen of the world.
Ever thought about settling down?
Starting a life together?
Aren't we doing that?
Are we?
Hello?
Dom?
I'll be there.
Hey, my man, I need you to turn this plane around.
All right, listen, ladies. There's
been a little change of plans.
Something came up.
You know that casino I was telling you all about?
I got some vouchers
to the buffet.
What do you think of this?
He likes it.
All right.
Yes.
Or this?
That's my boy. All right, let's
see how this thing flies.
Are you watching?
It's Uncle Dom.
What do you know?
Are you waving?
What up?
Hey, Jack.
What's up, Uncle Dom?
You excited to see him?
Are you already pushing imports on him?
You say, "Dad's not
pushing anything."
He chose that car.
We know he's an O'Conner, but,
I brought you something, Jack.
Yeah! He's also a Toretto.
I don't know.
Luckily, he has a couple more years to decide, right?
I think he decided, Mia.
I think it's time for his nap.
Come on, baby. Okay.
Say bye.
It's weird, huh?
What's weird?
We got everything.
You know, down to the beer and the barbeque.
But it just...
I don't know, it just doesn't feel like home.
Maybe it's because, uh,
you don't realize how much you appreciate something
until somebody takes it away.
I don't know.
The place has probably changed so much,
you wouldn't even recognize it anymore.
Yeah.
Everything's changed.
So what's up with you?
What's going on?
Taken a week ago.
Diplomatic Security Service.
Hobbs.
You know, I used to do this shit all the time as a cop.
This is exactly what cops do.
He's messing with your head.
Letty's dead, Dom.
I need to know for sure.
Then I'm going with you.
You said you were going to leave this life behind.
We both said that we were leaving the life behind.
He's right.
We're family.
If we got a problem, we deal with it together.
And I'll feel safer knowing you're both out there,
watching each other's backs.
You're stronger together.
You always were.
Now go get Letty.
Bring her home.
Thank God!
Finally, some equipment I can work with.
What up, boy?
This is way better than that trash in Rio.
Way better.
You sure about these guys?
Nope.
Has anybody heard from Leo or Santos?
Last time anyone saw them, they were
hitting up the casinos in Monte Carlo.
I thought that was our last job, Brian.
And who's paying for all this equipment?
The taxpayers?
So now we work for The Hulk?
That's what we're doing?
Why do I smell baby oil?
If you keep running your piehole,
you're going to
smell an ass-kicking.
All right, Hobbs,
you got the best crew in the world
standing right in front of you.
Give them a reason to stay.
Our target is Owen Shaw.
Former major in the S.A.S.,
Spec-ops soldier.
He ran the UK's Mobility Division in Kabul and Basra.
Ah, damn. That Mobility
unit's the truth.
We're talking vehicular warfare.
Best in the world.
- You got some chips?
- Those guys don't mess around.
For years, they've been running jobs in Europe,
but it's their most recent jobs
that graduated them to a whole new level.
Three targets, highly specific.
The program terminal from an ICBM missile...
Got a little change?
Seriously?
You're a millionaire,
and you're still trying to ask for money?
That's how you stay a millionaire.
So what does this all mean?
Well, our best guess is that Shaw's crew
is building a Nightshade device.
Which is?
A tech bomb.
Designed to block an entire military communication grid
for 24 hours.
If you blind a soldier for a single second
in the middle of a fight, he dies.
If you blind a country for 24 hours,
the loss of life is unthinkable.
This could be worth billions to the right buyer.
Billions?
Why don't we just steal that shit?
Hey, man.
Which one of these things is a dollar?
It says something about...
It's on the house.
I want you to help me catch Shaw.
He's only got one piece left that he needs,
and I intend to stop him before he gets it.
Now, I know you guys are a family.
So I'm offering you a chance right now
to make that family whole again.
You want to make this family whole again?
Get us to Letty, we'll get you Shaw,
full pardons all the way around.
I can't promise you that.
Yes, you can.
That's the deal.
Take it or leave it.
You get me Shaw,
and I'll get your pardons.
You heard him.
But this is different.
We're not dealing with cops,
we're not dealing with drug dealers.
This is a whole different level.
We're getting paid, right?
Interpol picked up one of Shaw's guys in Moscow.
I went in, had a little therapy session with him.
He gave up Shaw's hideout.
Then why aren't we down there now?
Well, we weren't invited.
Hobbs, they're sending in your punching bag.
He's wired. He's going to give a
positive ID on Shaw before they move in.
So, the cops just let you go, huh?
Don't worry, I didn't give them shit.
Oh, I'm not worried.
Okay.
Turn it over for me.
God, it's amazing.
The simplest things can cause the biggest problems.
Good news is, if you swap out a bad part,
everything runs smooth as silk again.
Look, Shaw...
Wait, Shaw! Shaw!
Shaw!
I just got confirmation on Shaw.
They're going in.
Wait, wait, hold up...
Police scanners are saying alarms are
going off at Interpol headquarters.
Shit.
He brought us here so he could take down Interpol.
This whole thing's a set-up.
Brian, take the team.
What about you?
Hobbs and I will wait for Shaw.
Shaw leads to Letty.
Come on, you son of a bitch.
What's this?
It's your share from the last job.
You're part of the team, Oakes.
You do your job, you get paid.
There's a little extra in there for you.
Consider it an advance.
For what?
The next job, of course.
Which job?
The one we're working right now.
Han, how far are we from Interpol?
Twelve blocks away.
You guys, it's a ghost town over here.
Shaw must have pulled all the cops to him.
All right, y'all, we're in this shit, so let's go get it.
It's been fun running with you, mate.
Stop! Drop the bag!
There he is.
On it.
Toretto, it's on you. Straight
ahead, don't lose him.
Ain't gonna happen.
Sorry about that, boys.
Interpol, straight ahead.
Let's go, guys.
We've got company.
Let's go, boys.
Get in! Let's go!
Hey! We got to move. Now!
Shaw, we have three cars tailing us.
You know what to do.
Guys, I got the Rover.
Okay, I got...
Whatever the hell that thing is.
What is that, a hockey puck?
Oh, shit!
Approaching rendezvous point.
Dom! Tej and Roman
are out! Where you at?
I'm right behind you!
Stay on track. I'm
taking the contingency.
Boys, I got eyes on Shaw.
He just made a left.
- I got right.
- Toretto, make that left!
No problem.
Letty.
Take the wheel.
This is crazy.
We are not in Brazil.
So, now we got cars flying in the air?
On some 007-type shit?
This is not what we do!
Man, you really got to check that emotion.
Your voice just went from
Shaggy to Scooby-Doo.
"This is not what we..."
See, man, when a woman starts shooting at you,
that's a clear sign to back the fuck off!
We need to get the hell out of Dodge!
That could have been my forehead, man.
No.
That's not as big as your forehead.
Mia...
Uh, It's definitely Letty.
But it's, uh..
It's complicated.
Letty's alive.
That's all that matters.
We have her back, Brian.
Well, do me a favor and give Jack a kiss goodnight for me.
Be safe.
I love you, Mia.
She definitely saw it was you?
She looked dead at me, Brian.
Maybe the Letty we once knew is gone, Dom.
Even though she's alive, maybe she's gone.
You don't turn your back on family.
Even when they do.
Ivory.
Yo.
It's going to need some repairs.
No problem, treacle.
Are you good?
Yeah.
Okay, listen up.
That was a very different breed
from Hobbs' usual wannabe warriors.
We need to learn who these people
are, what they're made of.
Vegh?
O'Conner, Parker,
Pearce, Toretto
and the rest of the team.
These guys are common criminals.
Tonight these common criminals were seconds away
from taking us down.
Show them the respect they deserve, or it weakens us.
You might want to see this.
Ring any bells?
Yeah.
That's the guy I shot.
You look happy.
I don't remember him.
That's bullshit.
We got a problem, guys.
We got a picture of her with the
guy who almost took you out.
Klaus, aren't you team muscle?
Don't make me go over there and make you team pussy.
She doesn't remember him.
Names and records aren't enough.
I want personal information. Get
into their lives, into their minds.
Find their weaknesses, and we will exploit them.
Mmm-hmm. Yeah, right.
This is crazy, man.
What are you talking about now?
I'm sitting here looking at these images...
It's like we're hunting our evil twins.
Look at this black dude right here, he's handsome.
Clearly, that's me.
We got a white Hobbs.
This is Han.
Tej, it's an African in a beanie.
That's like
your Mini-Me, man.
And Brian!
When did you do this photo shoot?
I'm just playing, man.
You know you're the prettiest blonde around here.
All right, lock it up.
We got two things.
First off, this is the worst damn
city in the world to commit a crime.
They got cameras on every street corner.
I got video footage from CCTV of the raid.
Let's track that, see where it leads us.
And secondly, we just got confirmation
on what Shaw's crew grabbed from Interpol.
They ripped off the database
of every location that houses the
final component that they need.
So where are they at?
There are over two dozen of them around Europe.
But the list is only good for 96 hours.
Which means, wherever Shaw's crew is going to hit next,
it's going to happen within the next four days.
They got a window, and so do we.
- We gotta move.
- Hobbs is right.
So let's break this down.
You met them.
What do we know?
We know they have to be running custom engines.
You heard that flip car going through those gears.
Sequential transmission.
That didn't sound like a normal engine.
That was a turbo diesel.
It sounded like something you hear at Le Mans.
Did you see it take all those hits
and still stay flat in the corners?
Yeah, hydraulics.
Or magnetic suspension.
Who not only has access to the components,
but can fabricate something like that?
Maybe a handful of shops in London.
Regular tuner shops aren't going to cut it on this one.
We're going to have to dig deeper than that.
Han, Gisele, Roman, you're up.
We find the guy who made that car,
we find Shaw.
Let's go.
I'll help.
Roger that.
Tej, we're gonna need cars without
computer chips that can be overridden.
Make sure they're fast.
I got this.
I'm already on it, Dom.
I've contacted R&D at DSS.
Hobbs...
I said I got this.
This should be interesting.
Man, you really got to loosen up.
You can't just throw a bunch of factory-line
Beemers at people and expect...
Hey. That car is
a hell of a car.
You're talking about
twin-turbo V8,
spitting out 560 ponies, son.
He reads the brochure.
I'm proud.
But with cars, you have to customize.
It's all between you and the car you build.
It's a bond, it's a commitment.
It sounds like a marriage.
Yeah, but with cars, when you trade up,
they don't take half your shit.
Jesus.
With price tags like this, these
cars better be made out of gold.
You ain't thinking about stealing
these cars, are you, Parker?
Kitchen help entrance is towards the back.
Come again?
I don't mean any offense, gentlemen,
but you couldn't possibly afford the cars in this auction.
Substantial lack of gaudy
jewelry, no entourage, no honeys.
Clearly you're
not a "baller."
And you.
Hmm. Shoes, shirt, trousers.
Functional.
And your posture, too rigid, no swagger.
My guess is military.
Take home of 50,000 a year.
That's U.S.
Which is not enough to be playing here.
So, if you're not kitchen help,
then you must be in the wrong place.
But please, do finish your champagne.
Oh, he needs to be taught a lesson.
Like I said, you ain't stealing these cars.
I got this.
All right, this is number five on our list.
Holy shit.
What's the dude plan on hunting?
Moby Dick?
That must be our guy.
So, how do you all want to play this?
Han and I got this.
We go in tight, you let me do all the talking,
and you all have my back on it.
There's one thing you boys are forgetting.
He's a man.
Let's go.
"He's a man?"
You know, she always says that.
What you're looking at is a
5.45 by 18 FMJ spitzer bullet.
It's specific to one handgun, the PSM.
Given that handguns are illegal in the United Kingdom,
there's very few people that have access to that firearm.
So if somebody wanted to, say,
track down where it came from,
it wouldn't be too hard.
I was a cop for a lot of years.
Some habits die hard.
A pawn shop.
Who sent you?
Come on, ladies!
Two hot girls like you don't wander into this neighborhood
unless I've called the escort service.
And I haven't, yet, today.
I don't know, man.
That was disrespectful.
And I don't like the way she said it,
like, "He's a man."
"He's a man?"
So, what are we?
Come on, she's just doing her job.
"Doing her job."
I see what's going on.
See what?
You got the little stardust in your eyes, eh?
Little birds floating around a little bit.
Uh, you don't want to lease this model.
You want to buy.
Can you please stop talking?
No, no, you're in love!
Look at you!
Just stop.
You got special plans?
Big day?
You're going to invite us all out?
Better make sure you get her a big rock, man,
'cause she doesn't look like
she'll be that easily impressed.
And if it's not a big rock,
you better be big somewhere else.
You know what I'm talking about.
That's why all your girlfriends wear so much bling, huh?
We're looking for information.
You're looking for information?
About what?
Information about cars.
In particular, two you designed recently.
Ramp cars.
Low slung, skeletal frames.
We'd be very interested to find the man who bought those.
Why should I help you?
Because we're asking you nicely.
Because you're asking me nicely?
What can you offer that I can't
get from a thousand other girls?
Hmm?
Stop! Stop!
You look like a man who likes it rough.
My friend here can give you heights of pain
you've never experienced before.
Do we have a deal?
Deal! Deal! Deal!
I take it back.
Me likey.
Stop, stop, stop.
So this is how you "got this?"
By buying all of his cars?
What good is having millions of dollars in the bank
if you don't spend any of it?
But don't worry about that.
Watch this.
Mr. Parker, again, can I
just express our gratitude
and say how much we appreciate your business.
If there's ever anything else
you need, you just have to ask.
Anything?
Mmm-hmm.
Now that you mention it,
my swagger-less friend here,
he really likes that shirt you have on.
Uh, this shirt?
That shirt.
I'm not entirely sure that this shirt
would fit your friend.
It will fit.
He needs a shirt that's a little less...
Functional.
That's it, functional.
Okay.
I'll hold that.
Thank you.
Come on, man, time is money.
Yes, doing my best.
Damn, you need some hedge clippers for that shit.
Well, if that will be all...
And the pants, too.
Right.
While you're at it, let me get that watch.
I like that watch.
This is for you.
And this is for you.
Thank you.
Good day, gentlemen.
So I, um,
I got the information in here.
May I ask why you're looking for Shaw?
He took something of ours.
We'd like to talk to him about it.
Let's see what we've got.
All right.
What do you want?
They say if someone's looking for a Russian gun,
you're the man to see.
Oh, they do, do they?
What do you want, mate?
That might be a bad idea.
I'm looking for the owner of this.
I don't know.
Take a closer look.
About a week ago, a girl came in,
bought guns, ammo, everything I had.
A girl?
What did she look like?
Tough chick, dark hair.
Mean streak.
Word is she's a street racer.
Where can we find her?
How do I know?
Do I look like a racer?
No. You don't.
Take care, guys.
Oh, shit.
Sorry, girls.
Let's go!
Hold on.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
Tell me where to find Shaw,
and I'll make him pay for this.
Braga...
Ow!
Hey, you!
Stop right there!
You go!
No, you go!
No one needs to know about this.
No one.
We lost Ivory.
He's gone.
Thanks.
That's it?
If ivory's dead, he made a mistake.
If you make a mistake, you pay the price.
That's a great eulogy, Shaw.
Are you going to give the same speech
for the rest of us when we go out?
You're the last one I'd have pegged to be sentimental.
I like you, Letty.
I dare say I even feel a certain warmth towards you.
When I found you in the hospital,
and you couldn't remember anything,
I said to myself,
"This girl has a gift."
"She's a blank page."
And that made me feel somewhat protective toward you.
If something happened to you, for instance,
I think I might find that slightly harder to bear.
What I'm saying is,
I would hate to see you
make a mistake.
I'm going to get some air.
What the hell happened?
We met Dom's girlfriend.
She's lovely.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Tej, what have you got?
Footage, CCTV? Talk to me.
I just went through all of it.
Believe it or not, everywhere Shaw's
team is, the cameras are down.
That's a hell of a coincidence.
All right, we're going to pay
CCTV a little visit. Let's roll.
What is that?
That is a new toy for you.
So, what happened?
Shaw's goons showed up and started shooting up the place.
But we got something big.
What?
Braga.
He's working with Shaw.
What are you talking about?
It's true. That phone's filled
with coded payment transactions
that lead straight to Braga's cartel.
Who the hell is Braga?
He ran one of the biggest cartels in Mexico.
And my old boss.
We used codes just like that
to move money out of the country.
It all makes sense.
Braga was running Letty, now he's working with Shaw.
It would explain how the two of them met.
Okay, so you all know all this information
about him, where do we find him?
He's sitting in a prison in Los Angeles.
How do you know that?
Brian put him there.
All right, so this is the break we were looking for.
If the two of them were working together,
Braga will know what Shaw's up to.
I'm going to pay him a visit.
Are you serious right now?
Think about what you're saying.
You're wanted, Brian.
The moment you step foot off that plane, it's a wrap.
You're not coming back.
"Coming back?" How are you
going to get in the country?
Let me worry about that.
This is on me.
I'm the one that served her up to Braga.
I'm the one that gets to make it right.
Let me make it right.
Be careful.
He's ready to see you now.
Right this way.
Thank you for seeing us. I won't
take up much of your time.
My men were attacked earlier today.
I'm going to need to see all cameras
in and around Waterloo station.
Will somebody tell Captain America here
that requires clearance?
Terry.
Bring up cameras 58 through 62, earlier today.
They've been down for maintenance all morning.
Sorry.
Okay. Well, we appreciate
your help. Thank you.
You know what I find very interesting
is Interpol was attacked recently as well.
Those cameras were down, too.
Didn't catch a thing.
Nothing.
Now, that means either one of two things.
Either means that your maintenance schedule here
aligns perfectly with their escape route
or it means that someone here is working with them.
And that's just ridiculous.
Because there ain't no way in hell
anybody here would be working for them.
Particularly you, ain't that right?
No, no, that's ridiculous.
That is ridiculous.
I'm going to need direct access to your live feed
citywide.
And I also strongly suggest
that you put a hold on any more
"maintenance."
Yeah, of course.
We appreciate your help.
Thank you so much.
Well, well, well.
The orange in that really makes your eyes pop.
Thanks, fellas.
Tell me something, O'Conner,
how is it you keep running around the world,
breaking every law known to man,
and yet here I am, putting my job on the line for you?
You'll feel a lot better once you get
the credit for taking down Shaw.
Oh, I'm tempted to settle for you.
Well, you know what they say, Stasiak,
if you want the
career-changing big fish,
you got to be willing to put on the big boy panties
and sail out to the deep water.
You're an asshole, you know that?
I missed you, too, man.
I really missed you.
I got you admitted into
Victorville to do whatever you got to do.
It's a 24-hour hold.
You need to be out
of there by 9:00 a.m.
That's when Forensics will run your
fingerprints through the national database.
That program will match you
and when they find out who you really are,
I won't be able to get you back out.
We're taking life in prison.
Cute kid.
So, I found out Braga's being held in cell block D3.
That's solitary.
I only had enough juice to get you in Gen Pop.
So you're going to have to do
something to get his attention.
Sorry about this, man.
Sorry about what?
Again?
Big Brother's about to go live.
Damn, you can't flick a booger in
London without somebody noticing.
Hey! Don't touch that. That's
nothing to play with, man.
What's the problem?
That's high-tensile
titanium cable.
What does that mean?
That's what they use to anchor
buildings and hold up bridges,
stuff you know nothing about!
See, now, their version, it works cool,
but mine, masterpiece.
See, I reversed the gears, torqued the motor
and added this tank to the back.
That makes it even sweeter.
It does.
It's not dummy-proof.
Man, I've been known
to handle big guns. Relax.
You've been known to
handle that big-ass head.
Dom, I did some checking, asked around,
got the location of a street race tonight.
Four speed Camaro SS big block.
You like it?
Nice color.
Brian O'Conner.
That was quite an entrance.
You put a lot of these men in here.
What? You didn't think
one would recognize you?
I've kept tabs on you, you know.
You've been having a lot of fun out there.
Good cop gone bad, Rio de Janeiro.
It's exciting when you go criminal, isn't it?
Too bad you didn't do it earlier,
you could have worked for me.
Like Letty Ortiz?
So tell me something, because I buried her.
Yeah? You did?
You buried something, I couldn't
tell you who or what it was.
I know she's running with Owen Shaw.
Still playing cop, huh?
Trust me, this is way above your pay grade.
Humor me, please.
Well, you're a dead man walking, what does it matter?
I ran everything for Shaw.
Drugs, guns, money, women.
He taught me to think global when I was just local.
He made me a wealthy man.
And this guy didn't just have the cartels working for him.
He had the CIA, DEA, everyone in his pocket.
He knew what was going to happen before they did.
In fact, he even knew when some
wet-behind-the-ears FBI agent
decided to put some informant in my cartel.
The minute you put Letty undercover, she was dead, bro.
But she survived.
That girl is one tough bitch.
Shaw found her in a hospital two days later.
He went to finish the job.
And he didn't
kill her. Why?
She had no memory.
Perfect girl, huh?
You're lucky this door's between us.
What happened to Letty is on your head.
Look at me! Look at me.
You won't do it.
What is Shaw up to?
How do you think he knows your
next move before you make it?
He's got eyes on you.
Think about it.
The only way you get close to Shaw
is if he wants you there.
You've got some serious balls, man.
I've been told.
You know, you're lucky I missed my shot.
I think you hit your mark.
Really?
What is it with you?
Do you got a death wish or something?
If that's what it takes.
I just want to race.
You might lose your car.
Let's do it.
Your funeral.
Ride or die, remember?
Listen up!
Out here, we're used to getting what we want.
This is London, baby.
But remember,
don't bite the bait.
Are you ready?
Ready?
Ready.
Steady.
Go!
Just like old times.
This guy is crazy.
You got to be kidding me.
You're still upshifting early.
I do that so you brake.
You lose traction and the back end kicks out.
I noticed.
Look, just because you know how I
ride, doesn't mean you know me.
You know what they say where we're from?
Show me how you drive, I'll show you who you are.
V8.
You never could resist American muscle.
Nice scar.
You never could keep yourself out of trouble, either.
What else do you know about me?
About you?
Everything.
Like this scar.
You got that the first night we met.
You were 15.
First street race.
Some kid trying to show off lost control of his car,
wiped out right next to you.
You're lucky you didn't lose your arm.
And let me guess,
you saved me.
No.
I was the kid showing off.
And here...
Boyle Heights.
You were fleeing with my little sister
Mia and got trapped in a corner.
And you thought it was a good idea
to ride your Torino Cobra through a retaining wall.
All right, how about this one?
That's the last time we were together.
In the DR.
You wanted to go for a night swim.
You cut yourself on the reef.
I followed you.
I even got this scar to match.
Look, I don't know why you're here,
but I really think you're over your head.
I'm here for you.
That girl you remember,
it's not me.
Not from what I just saw.
Like it or not,
you're still the same girl.
I saw it out there.
I see it right now.
I got to go.
Hey.
It belongs to you.
There she goes,
leaving you again.
Bloody fickle, that one.
You want bloody?
We could do bloody.
A street kid,
starts out stealing
DVD players in East L.A.,
ends up heisting $100 million in Rio.
Not bad, huh?
It's a good story, isn't it?
Almost inspiring.
See, what I couldn't fathom is
why he's not relaxing on a beach somewhere
with that cute little Brazilian number.
Instead, he's working with a two-bit
government hack like Hobbs.
And then I realized,
he has a weak spot.
We all got a weak spot.
You know,
when I was young, my brother always used to say,
"Every man has
to have a code."
Mine?
Precision.
A team is nothing but pieces you
switch out until you get the job done.
It's efficient.
It works.
But you?
You're loyal to a fault.
Your code is about family.
And that's great in the holidays,
but it makes you predictable.
And in our line of work, predictable means vulnerable.
And that means I can reach out
and break you whenever I want.
At least when I go, I'll know what it's for.
Well,
at least you have a code.
Most men don't.
So.
I'm going to give you a chance.
Take your crew and walk away.
That's the only way you're going to keep your family safe.
Your brother never told you never
to threaten a man's family?
It's a pretty stupid thing to do.
But I'll make it simple for you.
I walk away when she walks away.
Well, then,
it appears this inspiring tale has come to an end.
If that's the way it has to go.
Let me guess...
Hobbs.
Come on, you son of a bitch.
The "two-bit
government hack."
See you around, Toretto.
You can bet on it.
Riley, Shaw's leaving Battersea, heading southeast.
Have Tej track him
on his live feed. Go.
You know what would have happened
if I didn't put that tracker in your car?
This one?
You know, this just got me one step closer to Shaw.
For what it's worth, Toretto,
I hope it gets you closer to what you want, too.
This better have been worth it.
More than you'll ever know.
Pretty.
May I?
I'm going to ask you a question, Letty,
and I want you to think very hard before you answer.
When I give you the order
to take Toretto out,
what will your first thought be?
Why don't you look me in the eye
and you tell me what you see.
Keep it.
Tej, talk to me, what have we got?
We were able to track Shaw after he left you and Dom,
but this guy's smart, so we could only track him so far.
He seems to know all the city's blind spots.
See, we lost him somewhere in here,
which means he could be anywhere
within that
half-a-mile radius.
Maybe if we cross-reference
phone records, leases...
No, this has got Shaw's name written all over it.
We've got vantage points, multiple exits,
subways, highways and storm drains.
Bad-ass and brains.
Woman, you keep that up, I'm going to be out of a job.
All right, let's go nail that son of a bitch.
They're long gone.
There's nothing here.
There's never nothing.
There's always something.
Let's go, guys.
Shaw, everyone is in place. All
things moving according to plan.
Good. Send him in.
Yo, it's Hobbs.
What have you got, Parker?
Give me something good.
Yeah, that paint you got from
Shaw's place is highly specialized.
Anti-thermal
low-IR coating.
Military.
Exactly.
We got a list of bases around
Europe that use this paint type
and those specific colors.
All right,
let's cross-reference that
with all of Shaw's military targets.
I guaran-damn-tee you
one of them is gonna match.
Bingo.
It's a NATO base in Spain.
That puts Shaw in a different country.
That means he's got
an eight-hour lead on us.
We gotta move now.
Tej, give me that info.
Riley and I will go ahead and we're
going to lock down the base.
We're going to protect that component personally.
Toretto, I'll arrange transportation
for you and your cars.
You brush up on your Spanish, boys.
I'll see you en España.
You son of a bitch!
You made it!
What up, man?
Good to see you.
So, what's going on here?
Figured out they're hitting an army base in Spain.
Border patrol ID'ed Shaw's men
crossing through last night.
Hobbs and Riley went to lock down the base.
- They're going to meet us there.
- Where's Dom?
He wasn't going without you.
I found out what happened to Letty.
It's all my fault.
Brian,
whatever you found out, that's for you.
What we're about to do now
is for her.
We've got four teams on overwatch,
sniper-spotters in roosts
north and south of the target.
Just keep all your men out of sight.
When they drive that truck in here,
I want to come crashing down on
them like the walls of Jericho.
Hobbs, I just caught this one disabling
the perimeter security system.
Your house is compromised.
What are you suggesting?
I ain't suggesting.
We follow protocol, we move the component out.
Shaw thinks it's here. We're going to
get it out of here before he arrives.
Stealth and speed are going to be our two best friends.
We're going to protect our little
egg, move it out of the henhouse,
then we're going to wait for that goddamn fox to arrive.
I just got word they caught one of Shaw's men at the base.
It's time.
Something is not right.
He wanted us to find that guy.
Think about it. At Interpol, you
were face-to-face with him.
Brian, so what are you saying?
Braga said the only way you get
near Shaw is if he wants you to.
Tej, where's that component?
They're moving it to a secure location.
Shaw ain't hitting that base.
He's hitting the convoy.
Let's go!
We've got a report, the convoy's under attack.
Get a chopper, now!
Fellas, you better hurry up.
They just took the convoy.
And Dom,
Letty's with them.
We stick to the plan.
All right, you heard the man.
Let's play this fast and clean.
That thing's heading your way.
All systems go.
Everything looks stable.
Uh, guys, we gotta come up with another plan.
They got a tank.
I'm sorry, did somebody just say "a tank?"
We got company, guys.
Toretto is coming right at you.
Okay. Get the weapons hot.
Give me satellite imaging.
Straight ahead of us.
There you are.
Who's got a plan B?
Plan B?
We need a plan C, D, E.
We need more alphabets!
Hey, we do what we do best.
We improvise, all right?
Okay, Jah.
Take it to the other side.
Let's have some fun.
What the hell is wrong with you?
This isn't part of the plan.
Take their attention away from the people!
Shaw, you don't have to do this.
We got one right in front of us.
Boom.
Oh, shit!
You lucky bastard.
Roman, you hang in there.
Hang in there, mam!
Somebody better do something!
I got a tank on my ass!
There's gotta be a break up ahead.
Oh, look,
a bridge.
Screw it.
Yeah!
We're dragging a car behind us.
Brian, that Mustang would make a nice anchor.
Yeah, I'm on it.
Damn!
Shaw, we've got to get rid of that car.
Letty, go take care of the cable.
Yeah!
What's she doing?
Shit!
Okay, Toretto.
Here's your girl...
And your happy ending.
Letty!
Jesus Christ.
I can't believe they
stole a 70-ton tank
for a three-ounce
computer chip.
That 3-ounce computer chip is more
deadly than 1,000 of those tanks.
What about her?
Not her.
She was working with Shaw.
Was,
but she's always been one of us.
Let's give them a minute.
Let's go process Shaw and his crew.
I've never looked more forward to
filling out paperwork in my life.
Hey.
Look, I don't even know how to say this to you,
but everything that's happened here is because of me.
I'm the one that put you undercover...
Stop.
I may not remember anything,
but I know one thing about myself.
Nobody makes me do anything I don't want to.
So, what's our next adventure after this?
How about we stay in one place?
Where are you thinking?
Tokyo.
We always talk about Tokyo.
Tokyo it is.
Can I ask you something?
How did you know that there would
be a car there to break our fall?
I didn't.
Some things you just have to take on faith.
Hey, Toretto!
You need to hear this.
You guys really think you've won.
This code you live by,
it's the very reason why you weren't even in the game.
I told you exactly what I was gonna
do if you didn't walk away, Toretto.
Go!
But you didn't listen.
I told you I can reach out and break you whenever I want.
And I have.
Come on.
Go.
No!
Maybe you should call Mia.
Mia?
Brian!
Let me go!
So, this is how it's gonna go down.
You're gonna cut me loose from these cuffs,
you're gonna hand me the chip,
I'm gonna walk out of here and you're not gonna follow.
You must be joking.
Look at his face.
Ask him if I'm joking.
One hostage does not outweigh the threat to millions.
I'm sorry, but this changes nothing.
It changes everything.
You tell your men to stand down.
Stand down.
Toretto,
I need you to know,
the moment we let him walk out that door with that chip,
words like "amnesty" and "pardon"
walk out with him.
Those words went out the day we were born.
Coming, babe?
Of course.
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Like I said,
you were never in the game.
If I see you on the horizon, I'll
make the call and the girl's dead.
So, what about Toretto's sister?
There's no need for her anymore.
I just jammed every signal up and down the spectrum.
Let's move.
I'm coming with you.
Where the hell does this dude think he's going?
We're on an army base, he's trapped.
Wow, you just had to open your mouth.
Now we got a big-ass
plane to deal with.
That ain't a plane.
That's a planet.
She's as good as dead if Shaw gets away on that plane.
Then we don't let him get away.
Let's end this thing.
Ride or die.
Tell them to take off!
Babe, get me under the wing.
If I can hit that flap, we can keep it from taking off.
You be careful.
This is who we are.
Shit!
Grab the wheel!
Dom!
Go!
Come on. Let's go.
Get in the car.
Whoo!
What happened?
Did you hit the flap?
Uh...
You should buckle up right now.
What?
Hey!
Wrong team, bitch.
Shit.
Yeah!
I got you.
Tej!
Keep her steady!
We gotta move, it's going down!
Go!
Go, now!
Come on, let's move, move, move!
Come on!
Dom!
Where's Gisele?
So this is worth billions, huh?
Yes, it is.
Name your price, Dom.
1327.
Don't burn it this time.
Please?
I never go and burn it, man.
Good food.
The air quality here is lousy, the traffic is bad,
but I think you'll learn to like this place.
Yeah, and here you've got your own garage
so you can build a car with Daddy.
We'll be building a car?
First car better be a Charger, Jack.
You mean Skyline.
Like I said, he's a Toretto.
You're confusing the kid.
Mia, you're gonna let him get away with this?
You're really going to do it?
Tokyo.
Yeah, it's just something I gotta do.
You know we got your back, whenever you need us.
Hey, Mia, you better hide your baby oil.
I'm just playing.
You better hide that big-ass forehead.
I was just joking, but whatever.
Definitely not that funny.
It's official.
You're all free.
Mmm.
It wasn't half bad, having you work for me.
We all know you were working for me, Hobbs.
Agree to disagree.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Elena?
Letty.
This is gonna be awkward.
But sexy as hell.
Sexy as hell.
I wanted to thank you for everything you've done for him.
For us.
It takes an amazing woman.
He's an amazing guy.
Yeah, he is.
Try to keep him out of trouble, huh?
Now, you know that's not gonna happen.
I know.
Not bad for a cop.
I never thought I'd trust a criminal.
Until next time.
Elena.
You know you don't have to go.
All this...
This is your family.
It's who you are.
This is my family.
This is who I am.
All right, everybody, let's eat.
Want some help with that?
It's all here, it's done.
Come on, man, let's get with it.
First bite, he's got grace.
House rules, man.
House rules.
Any of this feel familiar to you?
No.
But it feels like home.
That's good enough for me.
All right, y'all.
Come on, let's do this.
Okay, Roman,
bless our table.
Father, thank you for the gathering of friends.
Father, we give thanks for all the choices we've made,
because that's what makes us who we are.
Let us forever cherish the loved
ones we've lost along the way.
Thank you for the little angel,
the newest addition to our family.
Thank you for bringing Letty home.
And most of all, thank you for fast cars.
Nice ride.
It does the job.
What job, delivering pizzas?
Well, it's not the ride,
it's the rider.
What the hell was that?
What?
Hey! You talking to my girl?
Oh, shit. Here we go. Yeah.
She was just admiring my ride.
"My ride."
My grandma's Buick could smoke
that piece of shit, trailer trash.
Well, what about your daddy's Viper?
This beast's got 500 horsepower...
and a Borla exhaust system.
It does 0 to 60
in like 4.3 seconds...
That's about right.
That's about right. Yeah.
Wow. You can read the brochure.
What a pitch, baby.
What a pitch. I like that.
What's he gonna do?
- Let's make it happen.
- Bring it.
I got your...
I got your back.
Why don't you nice boys
let your cars do the talking?
I only race for pink slips.
This car goes for 80 grand.
What would I do with a broken-ass
piece of shit like that?
How about me?
Winner gets me.
Cut it, let's cut it.
Let's go, go, go, go!
Blast-off, baby!
First one out the other side...
It's time. Let's go!
Ready, boys?
Make it interesting, Clay.
Shit!
Yeah!
I thought you loved me.
Oh, well.
What the hell?
Guess I got a new date for prom.
Clay, stop the car! Shut up!
Clay, stop the car!
Shut up!
Stop it!
Clay, please stop! Please stop!
Can I get a copy of that?
You think this is a joke, huh?
You see Ken and Barbie over there?
They're gonna walk out of here
without even a slap on the wrist.
Mommy and Daddy are too hooked up.
But I like screw-ups like you.
You know why?
'Cause you're 100%
guaranteed conviction.
- Where's my car?
- I crushed it.
You did what?
- Sit down! You're done.
- Easy, easy.
You're done.
You understand me? You're done.
And all before your eighteenth
birthday. Now sit down.
Sean.
What the hell were
you thinkin', huh?
Mrs. Boswell? Please.
It's, uh, it's Miss.
Officer, is it, um,
illegal to smoke in here?
It's a tough state.
And it's a pretty clear-cut case.
He'll be lucky if they don't
try him as an adult.
This is our third town
in two years.
Your son's got two priors
for reckless driving,
willful destruction of property.
This makes it strike three.
They're definitely gonna want
to get him off the streets.
Well, there's
just got to be another way.
So, where are we moving this time?
We are not moving anywhere.
I worked with Gisele.
Back when I was a CIA operative
running the drug trade
in Central America.
The good old days.
Gisele was my best.
You can lose an asset
at any time.
Bullet, knife, wire.
But I never thought
I'd lose her...
To love.
What do you want?
I'm offering you a job, Han.
Here, in Tokyo.
Why me?
'Cause I saw your work
with Gisele.
I saw that she trusted you.
And that means I can trust you.
And that is very rare
in this line of work.
Sean.
I thought you were
gonna be here on the 7th.
Today is the 7th.
Well, look,
just hold on one second.
Come on in.
This is it.
You know, Sean, I was,
I was gonna be there.
But your mom,
she said the 7th, see,
and we're a day
ahead of you in Japan.
Well, you're here now,
and that's good.
So, how is your mom?
Where do I sleep?
Now, Sean, you know
she had no other choice.
I mean, it was
either this or juvie hall,
I mean, you just
can't keep moving away...
every time you get into trouble.
Worked for you.
Look, neither of us asked for this.
But I promised your mom
I'd take care of you.
So you just go by the
rules her and I agreed to,
and I'm sure
you'll manage just fine.
Rules?
Yeah, rules. Real simple.
You go to school,
you come back here right after.
And I don't want to see or hear
about you anywhere near a car.
Here, the bedroom is yours.
Make yourself comfortable.
Lights out in 10.
Get down!
You got to be kiddin'.
Wrong train.
I'm new here.
Boswell, yes, ma'am.
Japanese food is like the Army.
Don't ask, don't tell.
Name's Twinkie.
Hey, I noticed
you ain't have a laptop.
Yeah?
I'll hook you up. Half price.
No, I'm cool.
60% off. Hmm?
Since we're both army
brats and everything.
I ain't got no cash, man.
And I ain't an army brat.
All right, all right.
Well, what about
a cell phone, huh?
Everybody needs a cell phone.
No offense,
but I'm probably
not gonna be here...
long enough to remember your name.
Then you gonna need some new
shoes to book town with, man.
You like Michael Jordan?
I love Michael Jordan.
Check this out.
Brand new Jordans.
Not even out yet.
LeBron James couldn't even
get his hands on those.
You selling that
Sparco steering wheel?
Hell, no.
That's mine right there.
Man, I even paid
retail for it.
What you drive?
- My ride?
- Yeah.
My ride's one of a kind.
Show me.
Thought you
weren't stickin' around.
All right.
Slamming, huh? Look at that car.
At least let me drive.
Y'all better have some
real cars around here.
Okay, I see
somebody got jokes, huh?
Well, all right.
I don't know if you're
ready for them, though.
You look a little nervous.
What up, Tosh?
For when you
blow your wad, man.
Hear that?
It's still not right
for the way I drive.
I don't need a computer to tell
me about my throttle response.
Okay. Then we're done here.
You wouldn't have
that problem with a V8.
Boys.
All they care about is
who's got the biggest engine.
I'm a guy. It's in my DNA.
So y'all race with these things,
huh?
Cute little toys.
You know, I almost didn't recognize
you without your slippers on.
Don't you mean uwabaki?
Neela, right?
You're a quick learner.
So, where you from, anyway?
Here.
No, I mean, not where you live.
Where'd you come from?
Does it really matter
where I'm from?
Who's the tourist?
What's with you
and the schoolgirls, D?
You're moving up in the world.
You gotta elevate your company.
Wednesday, Wednesday,
meet Thursday.
God. Girl.
Ladies, hold that thought, all right?
All right, beautiful. Hold up.
Hey!
He was just leaving.
I'm sorry.
I don't speak Japanese.
Understand that? Gaijin?
Takashi.
We were just talking.
This isn't your scene.
That word you called me,
gaijin or something or other,
what does that mean exactly?
Means, turn around,
keep walking.
That's exactly what we gonna do.
Come on, man, let's roll.
Yo, look, man, he's Yakuza.
Now, see, that's funny,
'cause I thought this
was, like, a free country
where a girl could talk
to whoever she wants.
You know who I am, boy?
Yeah. You're like the Justin
Timberlake of Japan, right?
Leave.
Damn, man.
You know Yakuza? The Mafia?
Look, sorry, DK-san.
Monkey didn't have
his banana today.
Hey, D, let's go.
It's time to race.
Hey, good luck, Timberlake.
You're the one that's lucky,
'cause I'm about to race.
Then let's race.
With what, huh? Your skateboard?
Easy to sound cocky
when you got no ride.
Take mine.
Let's race.
What? I wanna see
what the kid's got.
Can he drive?
You know what DK stands for?
Donkey Kong?
Drift King.
Drift?
What do you mean, drift?
Still need a dictionary?
You know that
real famous painting?
The one of the woman
who's smiling all the time?
The Mona Lisa.
Right, right, right.
Mona Lisa.
Well, look, man,
this car right here's...
like the Mona Lisa
of the drift world.
Han rebuilt this bad boy
from ground up.
We talking forged pistons,
bigger turbo,
new rods, new crankshaft.
Hey, man, Han's labor
ain't cheap, man, you feel me?
Well, if I needed a 30-second
lesson on how to drift...
All right, look, man, there's lots
of ways you can do this, all right?
Hand braking is the easiest,
so the first thing
I want you to do,
I want you to rip that e-brake.
All right,
after you rip the e-brake,
then I want you to power over.
You know what?
Just don't mess up Mona,
all right?
All right.
Ready.
Set.
Go!
I told you.
Damn it!
Don't leave town.
Do you know what time it is?
I thought it was around 7:00.
You know,
US is a few hours behind.
Looks like the party
was better here, anyway.
Have you been racing, Sean?
You're out of here.
Go ahead.
You don't get it, do you?
You have nowhere else to go.
If it doesn't work out here,
you're going to jail.
Do you get that?
This isn't a game.
And I'm gonna tell you
one more time,
if you're gonna
live under my roof,
you're gonna go by
my rules or get out.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
Get in.
I'll get you your money.
Why you talking
like you have a choice?
There's a guy in there
with a paw...
that owes me some money.
A paw?
Go get me my money.
Okay.
Han said,
okane.
Han said, okane.
Let's go.
You're in the pickup
and delivery business now.
I might call you once a week
or once an hour.
I don't care
if you're sick as a dog...
or in bed with Beyoncé.
I call, you show.
Only if you teach me
how to drift.
This ain't a negotiation.
I wasn't negotiating.
What's he doing here?
He's paying me back for
that crumpled beer can...
sitting in my garage.
Hope he's not driving.
Gaijin.
When is your next race?
I'd really like to be there.
Why not be in it?
You heard me.
Ready to lose another car, Han?
I'm ready to take that
'86 Corolla off your hands.
All right.
Put up the '72 Skyline.
Done.
What do you think,
Morimoto, huh?
Get him out of here.
We have business to discuss.
Your shipment's late.
Since when are you
so worried about the details?
When is
the shipment arriving, Han?
Just sit pretty
and let me handle it.
Hey, Dad, it's me.
Uh, I had to stay after school...
for some extracurricular activities.
So I'll be home a little later.
Sir.
You really need to stop
following me around.
What are you doing here?
I thought I'd stop by
and ask your boyfriend
for some drifting lessons.
Trust me.
You don't wanna be
a part of this world.
It's good enough for you.
You don't know anything about me.
Well, why don't you think I know?
'Cause I'm a gaijin? An outsider?
Let me guess.
You're an army brat
who moved around a lot.
Your mama and daddy
was never home.
So you walked around
pissed off all the time.
And now you found your family
with these drift nuts.
Zero for one, cowboy.
Why can't you go find
a nice Japanese girl
like the rest of
the white guys around here?
Is everything okay back there?
I can handle DK.
I thought he's Yakuza.
His uncle's Yakuza.
He's just playing gangster
in his little storage room.
But I need him.
He keeps Uncle Kamata
from poking around too much.
What do you mean?
Well, his uncle gets
a piece of the action
from everyone on his turf.
We're on his turf.
50% of something is better than
100% of nothing.
So have you raced DK?
Why not? Is he that good?
What's the point of a race?
To see if I'm better
than the other guy.
Just proves you're faster,
that's all.
If I were to race,
it would have to be
for something important.
Or why else do it at all?
Why are you letting me race?
'Cause you're DK's kryptonite.
And you owe me a car.
Oh, shit.
What the...
Police cars here are
only factory-tuned.
You can do better than 180k,
they can't catch you,
so they don't even try.
You know what?
I'm beginning to like
this country already.
Danny!
You're looking good.
Disco.
We gotta catch up.
Get you a drink on me, huh?
Let's go.
Aha. Easy now, ladies.
Come on.
What's up? How you doing?
Hey, baby.
Keep your hands off the kid, girls.
He's underage.
Ladies, ladies, ladies.
Disneyland for grownups, huh?
All these girls, man,
they look like...
What, models?
Check it out.
See,
Tokyo is the fashion capital...
on this side of the planet,
all right?
Now, imagine
you been posing all day.
I mean,
that's a lot of hard work.
Not only do you get tired,
but, on top of that,
you wanna have a little fun,
but you can't
'cause you don't even know
nobody in town.
And most of
the guys around here are
too chicken shit
to even try picking up one.
So what do you do?
Man, you talk to the little
dude who makes you laugh.
Yeah.
Look, man, I don't just think
outside the box.
I tear it up.
That's my thing.
Yo.
Sean!
The red Evo's yours.
What do you mean?
You're representing me now.
What you think, I'm gonna
let you roll in a Hyundai?
Oh, man.
Damn it.
My mother,
she's blind in one eye
and she can drift
better than that.
Han, where did you find this guy?
Will someone please teach
this guy how to drift?
Is that yours?
Sure is.
What happened?
I don't know. I found
it this way at the base.
It's got potential.
Yeah, maybe. We'll see.
You know, Sean,
the Japanese have a saying.
"The nail that sticks out
gets hammered."
You're gonna be late.
Sean!
Come on, man, you broke it.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
There must be a misunderstanding.
Out of my way, or you're next.
Take it easy.
Look, man, I don't
do refunds, all right?
Okay, let's go, then!
Let's go!
Touch me again...
Here.
Try not to break this one.
Say, man!
What the hell is
wrong with you, huh?
Now everybody's gonna want
exchanges around here.
Damn!
Not easy saving the day, is it?
Maybe you could give me
some pointers sometime.
You're doing all right.
Thanks.
Hey.
Yeah?
Sorry about the other night.
Your life isn't any of my business.
It's okay.
Foul!
- Ain't no damn foul.
- That was a foul.
- Yo, you in my face.
Hey, Han, sort this wanker out.
A wanker?
What do I look like, a zebra?
So, how did you end up
over here, anyway?
Well, you know
those old Westerns...
where the cowboys
make a run for the border?
This is my Mexico.
Why'd you let me
race with your car?
You knew I was gonna wreck it.
Why not?
'Cause it's a lot of money.
I have money.
It's trust and character
I need around me.
You know, who you
choose to be around you...
lets you know who you are.
And one car in exchange
for knowing...
what a man's made of,
that's a price I can live with.
Look at all those
people down there.
They follow the rules, for what?
They're letting fear lead them.
What happens if they don't?
Life's simple.
You make choices
and you don't look back.
So, if you don't drift to win,
what do you drift for?
You really want to know?
Yeah.
Okay. Let's go.
There's no "wax on,
wax off" with drifting.
Learn by doin' it.
The first drifters
invented drifting...
out here in the mountains
by feeling it.
So feel it.
Again!
What's in this bag?
You'll see.
How much you got?
Keep going, keep going.
I'm so good, man, I could
sell rubbers to a monk.
Again.
Watch it. Watch it.
Not too early, now.
Go, go, go, go!
Don't lose it! Don't lose it!
Hey, Twink.
Get this man a bunk.
Pleasure doing business.
Yeah, baby. I told you.
I told you, didn't I?
They say if you want to
glimpse the future,
just look behind you.
I used to think
that was bollocks.
But now I realize
you can't outrun the past.
When we were kids,
you'd start fights
with the toughest
bastards in the yard.
But I was the one
who had to step in
and finish them.
You'd steal from
the corner shop,
but it was me
who'd brave the old man's belt.
I'd hoped you'd outgrown it.
That playing the gangster
made you harder,
smarter, better.
But deep down,
I guess I always knew
you'd end up like this,
despite everything
I did teach you.
Still,
you're my flesh and blood.
So you remain my cross to bear.
Rest now, little brother,
while I settle
your one last score.
You take care of my brother.
Anything happens to him,
I'll come by looking for you.
Here. Hold this.
Grenade!
Come on, Dom.
So where are you
taking me?
They say an open road
helps you think
about where you've been,
where you're going.
So you don't remember
any of this yet?
That's not fair.
You know I don't.
So what is it exactly
that you're trying to
show me?
That.
Race Wars.
We used to come here?
"Come here?"
We invented it.
Keep it under 9,000 RPMs.
Kid's gonna fry his pistons
after the first 200.
You know that's not my style.
I gotta ride or die, right?
How about you just ride
on this one?
Are you ready?
I know you're ready!
Go!
Hey, nice job.
Hey!
That's the girl
I heard so much about.
Where you been at, ghost girl?
Ghost girl.
Letty, what the hell?
Huh?
Damn, dawg!
Girl's still got
that swing, homie.
You never could take a punch.
Right, right.
Hey, man.
I'm glad you're back, man.
It's good to see you!
Good to see you, Hector.
All right.
We made it, Jack.
Yeah, we made it!
Yeah, we made it.
Now I just gotta find
that door button.
Buddy, where's the door
button at? Do you know?
Hi.
Hey.
Yeah, of course.
I'm new to this.
Yeah, you don't seem
like the minivan type.
No, not exactly.
Hey, buddy, you gonna
give me a high five?
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, high five!
All right. Yeah, buddy.
Appreciate it. Thank you.
Don't worry. You'll get
used to this in no time.
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
First time I saw this,
I thought it was kind of funny.
I guess now the joke's on me.
What are you doing?
What I should've done
a long time ago.
LETTYI Stop it!
Look at it.
It's the truth.
That's the date
that I lost my memory.
That's the date that Letty died
and I was born.
No.
You never died.
Do you know how hard it is
for me when you look at me
and you see me through
15 years of memories?
Every beautiful moment
we've ever had.
I see it in your eyes.
I can't give that to you.
I got nothing.
You got me.
And you've got
only a piece of me.
I have to find myself.
For me.
Goodbye, Dom.
You're disappointed, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
The last arrest.
He was too easy.
Target didn't even run.
Ah, it's okay.
Gives me a chance
to hit the iron.
Also lets me work on
my stamping skills.
You're a terrible liar.
See you tomorrow, boss.
I'll see you then.
Don't stay too late.
I'll stay as long
as I want, woman.
I knew you would say that.
Elena?
What's this?
It's the letter
of recommendation
you asked for.
Just know I meant
every word in there.
Thanks, Hobbs.
Thanks for everything.
Come on, way too
sentimental right now.
Get home. Good night.
Okay. Good night.
Just one sec.
You sure as hell
ain't the IT guy.
So you better start talking
before I break that finger
six different ways
and stick it
right where the sun
doesn't shine.
Agent Hobbs, right?
That's right.
I'm also the last man on Earth
whose computer you want
to be hacking into.
You just earned yourself
a dance with the devil, boy.
You're under arrest.
I don't care about
your computer.
I'm here for the team
that crippled my brother.
There ain't no goddamn team.
It was just one man,
and he's standing
right in front of you.
The lady was right.
You are a terrible liar.
Goddamn IT guys.
Hobbs!
On me!
Elena!
Hobbs?
Hobbs!
It's actually not bad.
I didn't even have
to put ketchup on it.
See, I'm not a total gaijin.
I hate that word.
It's what they used
to call me when I was a kid.
I thought you were born here.
Well, "outsider" can mean
many different things.
My mom died when I was 10.
She came out here
from Australia...
when she finished high school.
And all I know
about her is that...
she went to work in a hostess bar.
DK's grandmother took me in.
Well, my parents
split up when I was three.
Me and Mom moved around a lot.
Mostly 'cause of me.
Well, it was all 'cause of me.
Kind of made myself
an outsider, you know,
without even thinking about it.
But I realize now,
outsider or insider,
it doesn't really matter.
All that matters is knowing
what you really want
and going after it.
We used to come up here
when we were kids.
Even before we could drive
we'd cut class, sneak out,
come up here, and watch
the older kids drift.
Things were different back then.
Once I got my license,
I practically lived up here.
Back then, kids just drove
whatever they had.
You know, we just made do.
No one bothered us.
The day I got my license...
is the day I got
my first speeding ticket.
The day after that,
I won my first race.
I beat this rich kid
by three lengths.
I gotta admit, it felt good.
It felt like...
Like everything else
just disappears.
No past and no future.
No problems.
Just the moment.
Boy needs to chill.
Hey, Twink,
I'm gonna grab another set.
Whoa! Whoa,
whoa, whoa! Another set?
No. Look, that was
your third set today.
I mean, them tires ain't cheap.
DK, grab a chair.
We're about to
roast some marshmallows.
Yo, come on, man, look...
Stay away from her,
or the only thing you'll
be driving is a wheelchair.
Find yourself a new driver.
I'm all right.
What'd you expect?
You didn't just play with fire,
you soaked
the matches in gasoline.
It's over.
All this over a gaijin?
I am a gaijin.
You've changed, DK.
You say I've changed.
But we're not so different,
you and I.
We're both products
of fuckups, aren't we?
They say your mom
was the best trick...
in all of Kabukichō
back in the day.
Leave my mother out of this.
If we hadn't taken you in,
you'd be just like her,
doing anything for a buck.
Think anyone would take
a second look at you...
if it wasn't for your uncle?
We're the same, Neela.
Difference is I know who I am
and where I belong.
Do you know who you are?
Do you know where you belong?
Hey.
Come on.
Hey, brother.
I vouched for you!
Put my reputation
on the line for you!
We were partners!
You think you can keep
your side deals from me?
Come on.
We ain't in the Boy Scouts.
This is what we do.
Takashi!
What about now? Hmm?
Is this what we do?
Man, you need me.
You'd still be
shaking down teahouses...
for chump change
if it wasn't for me.
Get in!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on.
Sean. Sean!
All right, buddy.
We gotta go.
We're gonna be late.
Come on.
Okay, what do you think?
Parking brake slide
right up to the school?
Where's Mommy?
I don't know.
She's up there.
She's coming.
Oh.
Here we go.
Watch your head.
Dom, you have
a package out here!
It's from Tokyo.
Tokyo?
What? ls Han trying
to convert me over
to a turbocharger?
All right, you ready?
There we go.
Yeah!
Hey, buddy.
Cars don't fly.
This one did, huh?
Brian in a minivan.
Things have changed.
He's struggling, Dom.
He doesn't want me to see it,
but the white picket fence
is like an anchor on him.
I can tell.
I tried to talk to him
the other night.
You know what he said?
He doesn't miss the girls,
he doesn't miss the cars.
He misses the bullets.
Let him settle in.
Give him time.
How does nine months sound?
I'm having another baby.
And you didn't tell him,
did you?
You gotta tell him.
I don't want him to be
disappointed with his life.
With me.
He will never be
disappointed with you.
You're the best thing
that's ever happened to him.
Thank you.
Yeah?
Dominic Toretto.
You don't know me.
You're about to.
Get down!
Jack!
Pretty nifty magic trick.
Yeah, I've done better.
Now for the hard part.
Keeping you dead.
Takashi.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
Neela.
See you when Daddy's not around.
I'm putting you on a plane tonight.
Dad...
Sean, don't argue with me.
I did this. I can't run away.
I can't.
Sean, I'm your father.
I'm responsible
for your well-being.
And I'm responsible
for my mess.
I gotta do this.
Can you understand that?
At least you're not
redoing my mistakes.
You all right, man?
We're leaving town.
Look, I know some people...
I can't do it, Twink.
Look, DK wants your head.
All right?
And the trouble you
just made for Kamata?
You're done here, bro.
Maybe I should talk to Kamata.
What?
DK answers to him.
I know I just didn't hear that.
I gotta end this.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
What, are you crazy, huh?
Han is dead, all right!
Plus, you can't just walk
into Kamata's place, man!
It's all I got.
Something I think Han
would've wanted you to have.
What's this?
You're gonna need it
if you're gonna make it...
out of Kamata's place alive.
Don't you need it?
No, it's cool.
Look, I'll figure it out.
Sean.
You need to leave.
You came to the wrong place.
I didn't come here to see you.
Takashi.
You think...
you can walk in here,
dump some cash and walk out?
I know I'm only returning
what belonged to you...
in the first place, sir.
But that's not why I really came.
I came here to apologize.
I know your nephew and I have
embarrassed ourselves badly.
Sir, I'm here to offer you
a peaceful solution.
How do you plan
to accomplish that?
A race.
DK and I have caused
nothing but problems for you,
for us.
And I'm asking you
to allow us to settle this,
once and for all.
We race...
and the loser leaves town
for good.
I've already beat
this piece of shit once!
Good.
Then it should be easy.
The cops took all the cars.
Hey!
That's why she's spitting.
We almost there, Twink.
Couple more tweaks.
It's not the car
I'm worried about, man.
DK picked this road
for a reason.
This is his mountain.
He's the only one to ever
make it to the bottom.
Shattered his collarbone,
fractured his leg in two places.
He only regained
consciousness this morning.
The first thing he said was,
"Get me Dom."
He's in there.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
He's waiting. Let's go.
Got something for you.
Your files.
Thank you.
You risk life and limb
to save the free world
and what do they give you?
Jell-O and a bad
'70s TV show.
You know, it's got its perks.
Sponge baths
ain't that bad.
Dad!
I'm sorry, baby.
"Dad?"
Honey, I want to introduce you
to somebody. He's a, uh...
He's an old friend.
Go on and say hello.
Dominic Toretto, right?
My dad said he
kicked your ass once.
Young lady, watch your mouth.
Your dad's on heavy pain meds.
I can understand
if his history
is a little hazy.
- I doubt it.
-Alright, honey, that's enough.
I want you to go get
something to eat with Elena
while me and Toretto
have a talk. You hear me?
Come on, lady.
Let's get some cookies.
Watch that mouth.
Who did this?
You remember Owen Shaw?
The one we tore
half of London down
trying to get.
Well, this is his
big bad brother.
Take a look at this.
Deckard Shaw.
British Special Forces assassin.
The kind of unique asset
that no government
would ever admit
to employing.
Black Ops boys.
Worse.
They created a monster.
They felt Shaw
was a necessary evil
until eventually
they decided he was unnecessary.
The powers that be
felt that he knew
just a little bit too much.
The asset became a liability.
So they sent in 20 elite
operatives to retire him.
And they missed.
That was six years ago,
and Shaw's been
a ghost ever since.
Until now.
How do I find him?
The official answer
is, you don't.
He killed Han.
Almost killed my family.
He also tried to put me
in a body bag, too.
Which is why when I get out,
I'm gonna put a hurt
on him so bad
he's gonna wish
his mama had kept
her legs closed.
But until then,
my official answer to you
is stand down.
Now, you know I can't do that.
I do know you, Dom.
Which is why now I give you
the brother-to-brother answer.
You do whatever
it is you gotta do.
When you find that sumbitch,
just do me one favor.
What's that?
Don't miss.
Thank you so much
for letting us stay, Mando.
I hope it's not a problem.
Listen,
Dom needed a safe delivered
to Rio in two days.
That was a problem.
Hosting his family
in the Dominican Republic,
that is vacation.
Anyone messes with you here,
they mess with
the entire country.
You'll be safe.
Yeah, yeah, they're here.
I picked them up
myself at the airport.
Hold on. Your brother.
Dom.
Yeah, Mia, it's me.
How's it going there?
We're at Mando's.
This place is like a fortress.
You should see Brian.
He's in full FBI mode.
He built a surveillance hub
in Mando's garage
and everything.
What about you?
Did you find out
who's after us?
Looks like the sins of London
have followed us home.
How did Buster take the news?
I can't tell him.
If he knew about the baby,
he'd stay here with us.
And with all that's
going on, you're gonna
need him by your side.
Just watch out for
him. Keep him safe.
And come home together.
Tell Brian I'll see him
in LA in two days.
Where are you going?
Tokyo.
I'm bringing Han home.
Authorities are still
trying to determine
the motive behind
this daring attack
here at the office
of the US Diplomatic
Security Service in
downtown Los Angeles
less than 36 hours ago.
Facts are still coming in,
but what is known
is the suspect entered
the building's fourth floor...
Hey-
You okay?
Yeah.
This guy's just relentless.
That's why Dom needs you.
You two need to find
this guy and you
need to stop him
before he does
any more damage
to our family.
You know, I just...
I've screwed up so many things.
I couldn't live with myself
if I screw this up, too.
You won't.
I believe in you.
I believe in us.
That's all that matters.
I love you, Brian.
I love you, baby.
Just promise me,
after this, we're done.
No more jobs, no more enemies.
Come back to us.
I won't let you down, Mia.
I know.
Yeah!
Yes!
Come on.
Yeah! Come on!
Come on, Sean.
Let's go! Let's go!
Sean, you the boss. Let's go.
Damn! Come on, man!
That ain't right.
Yeah, baby!
That's what
I'm talking about, man.
I told you!
Hey, yo, Sean! Yo, Sean!
Hey, check this out, man.
This dude over here
wanna race the new DK.
Heard he's been beating
everybody around Asia, too.
Not tonight, Twinkie.
Said he knew Han.
Said Han was family.
All right.
Let's race.
Nice ride.
I won it from my friend Han,
a few years ago.
I didn't know he was
into American muscle.
He was when
he was rolling with me.
You know this ain't
no 10-second race.
I got nothing but time.
You ready, kid?
Come on, Sean! Come on!
Ready!
Set!
Go!
Han said you was fast,
but not that damn fast.
Who said American
muscle can't drift?
Han mentioned he left his
enemies in his rearview.
He never talked about it much.
Always playing it
close to the vest.
We found a couple
things by the crash.
Wasn't much left.
Gisele.
Oh, yeah.
There's one more thing.
I found this.
Must have meant
something to him.
When you find the guy
that killed Han,
what are you going to do?
Words ain't even
been invented yet.
They say to live
in the hearts of those
we leave behind
is not to die.
But he put you in this grave.
So now I'll do the same to him.
I can't do no more funerals.
First Han.
Now Hobbs is laid up,
of all people.
We're being hunted.
You know he's out there
somewhere watching, right?
I hope so.
Means he's close.
Just promise me, Brian,
no more funerals.
Just one more.
His.
You never should have
messed with a man's family.
I told your brother
the same thing.
Reinforced your chassis.
It's like going into a ring
with weighted gloves.
Your mistake.
I'm not here to play games.
See, you and me,
we're from
different worlds.
Trust me, I've seen a lot
meaner streets than
the ones you're used to.
Stick around.
It's gonna get a lot meaner.
You thought this was
gonna be a street fight?
On the ground.
Now!
Drop him
or I will drop you!
Whoa, whoa. Easy, guys.
We're on the same team here.
Mr. Toretto,
I'm here
on the recommendation
of a mutual friend of ours.
Mr. Hobbs.
Who the hell are you?
Me? I'm just a guy.
I'm Mr. Nobody.
It's a big entrance
for a nobody.
And the guy that put
our mutual friend
in the hospital?
You just let him get away.
I think I might
have just saved
your ass there, Dom.
Listen, you think
you could let go
of my guy there?
He's beginning to
turn a little blue.
I appreciate that.
Ah, here they come.
Listen, Dom.
There's a war going
on between shadows
and ghosts like me.
You and your team
unwittingly walked into
the middle of it in London,
and it appears it's
now followed you home.
It's up to you.
I'm gonna have a beer.
You're welcome to join me.
By the way, I can
get you Deckard Shaw.
Belgian ale.
Oh, man, those
monks got it right.
I mean, I don't know
about the whole
celibacy thing,
but when it comes to beer...
Would you like one?
I'm more of a Corona man myself.
Ah.
Your file's not only detailed,
it's, uh,
extremely entertaining.
Look, Shaw's power
is that he's a shadow.
He's really good
at getting in and out of
places without being seen
and leaving
nothing but a body count
in his wake.
I mean, he's a legitimate
English badass.
But to be honest
with you, Dom,
I don't give two shits
about Deckard Shaw.
It's you I want.
Because you and I
can help each other
get what we both need.
I'm listening.
Just recently a private
military company
led by a wanted terrorist
named Mose Jakande
kidnapped a hacker
known only by
the name "Ramsey."
Now, Lady Liberty's
got her panties
in a bunch over this,
but rightfully so,
because this Ramsey
has created
something interesting.
- Bring it up.
- Yes, sir.
Say hello
to God's Eye.
Now, this little bastard
hacks into anything that's
on the digital network.
That means every
cell phone, satellite,
ATM machine and computer.
Simultaneously.
If it's got
a microphone or a lens,
God's Eye can find you.
So you invited me
here to show me
a tracking device.
On steroids. Lots of them.
Let me put it to you this way.
It took us nearly
a decade to find
Osama bin Laden.
With this,
we'd have located him
anywhere on the planet
in a couple of hours.
Now, that's a serious
piece of machinery
that could be catastrophic
in the wrong hands.
But for some very nauseating
political reasons,
any rescue plans involving
any US government
forces or entity
has been strictly ruled out.
And that's why I need you.
But why do I need you?
I mean, I could go back outside,
enjoy the rest of the Coronas,
let Shaw come to me.
You could do that.
How's that working out
for you so far?
You got one friend
in the ground,
another one in the hospital.
And then, of course,
there's that little
issue of the bomb
that destroyed your home.
Shaw lives in a
world that doesn't
play by your rules.
Like it or not,
you live in that world now, too.
You wanna know
how to kill a shadow?
You just shine
a little light on it.
If you get the God's Eye for me,
I've already got authorization
for you to use it
until you get Shaw.
You go from the hunted
to the hunter.
And there's
no place on Earth
Shaw can hide from you.
More importantly,
you and your family
don't go to
any more funerals.
You get Ramsey,
you get the God's Eye,
you get Shaw.
Well, that's the wind-up
and the pitch.
Now that I've given you
this incredibly sensitive
and highly
classified information,
what do you think, Toretto?
I think you already know
what I'm gonna do.
Good.
But it'll be my way.
And my crew.
I assumed you might say that.
Which is why
I've taken the liberty
of gathering your team.
This is crazy.
What the hell is
going on in here?
Our intelligence
suggests that Ramsey
will be transported
by an armed motorcade
through the Caucasus
mountain range.
If they clear this range
and reach their destination,
Ramsey is as good as gone.
So let me
get this straight.
There's only one road
that leads in or out,
sheer drops on every side,
a motorcade from hell
protected by a small army
from one mile in
either direction?
Yeah, that's about it.
You done?
No, I'm not done.
So you all wanted me
to break into
a police station. Fine.
Then you asked me
to stop a tank.
I wasn't happy about it,
but I did it.
Then you came up with
this brilliant idea
to shoot down
one of the largest
airplanes ever.
I shot that shit
out of the sky. Mmm.
It's nothing.
But this right here, my friend,
happens to be
the stupidest idea
I've ever heard of
in my life.
I forgot that you
were the only one
to bring the plane down.
No, no. The only thing
I've ever seen him
take down was
"No Knees" Denise.
Remember, at prom?
Really, Brian?
You're gonna do
that right here?
See, y'all trying to
get me off my point.
All I'm saying is,
I'm tired of
everybody around me
making all the decisions.
This time, I lead.
Seriously. If I don't
start making decisions,
I'm out.
All right, Roman.
What do you got?
I mean, I wasn't
trying to get into the whole
leadership thing, like, now.
You know what I'm saying?
I was just, kind of,
talking about,
like, at some point.
Like, you know, when we...
Whatever. I mean, I think...
Let's hit it from here.
I don't think
that that's...
No, no, no, don't think.
That's my job.
Okay-
It is impossible
to hit it there.
That is literally
the most secure spot
on the mountain.
Why? Because you cannot
physically access it.
See, that's what
makes it so sweet.
Because it's the place
that they least expect us
to hit them from.
As much as I hate to admit it,
he's onto something there.
What do you think, Dom?
- Here?
- Yeah.
I think we got a plan.
Completely wrong thinking.
And I like it.
You see? I'm good at this.
"Good?" Okay.
How are you
planning on getting
on that road?
Well, Tej?
I think I may actually
have a plan for that.
What? I delegated.
That's what good leaders do.
Leader
You know, when I was
reading your files,
I was impressed with
what you've accomplished
with your team.
But meeting them now,
I've gotta say, Dom,
you've truly got a gift.
Consider my workshop
your new playhouse.
I think you'll find our
cars extremely appealing.
And your team is now complete.
I went to the house.
I was looking
for you everywhere.
You scared the shit out of me.
You will
never be alone.
Wherever you go...
Tell no one.
Where did you find that?
Found in Han's car.
It was left as a message.
A message I plan on returning.
Can you ride?
Yeah, of course I can.
Han was my family, too.
Brian!
We're gonna need
long-travel suspension,
limited-slip differentials
on all of them.
How you doing?
Tej!
I want the demon
love child between that
and that.
That's a lot of armor.
It's just gonna add more weight.
Slow you down.
This time, it ain't
just about being fast.
Yeah, I'm good.
From the streets.
You know what I'm saying?
It's nothing.
Hey, Roman,
you're freaking out,
ain't you?
No.
Yeah, you are.
I said no.
Listen, man,
it takes a grown man
to embrace his feelings.
If you need to cry,
just go ahead and cry.
As your friend,
you know I'm concerned
about your well-being,
which is why I took
the precaution
of putting some adult diapers
in your glove compartment.
Yo, can you just chill out, man?
I have seen
some crazy shit, Dom,
but this really
could make some waves.
So let's just try to keep it
as low-key as possible, huh?
Don't I always?
I'll tell you what,
you knock it down
a couple of notches this time
and I'll swap out my Belgian
for a keg of Corona.
You'd be doing
yourself a favor, there.
Can somebody just walk me
through what we're
supposed to be doing?
Come on,
Rome, this is your plan.
You gotta embrace it.
No, this was not my plan.
Oh, yeah, here we go.
Game time.
Roman,
you need some fresh air?
Because you're about to
get a whole lot of it.
Okay, here we go!
Just when you didn't think
it could get any better, huh?
Oh, shit!
Whoo!
Now we're moving.
Everybody good?
Everybody make it out?
You just didn't tell them
that this is not for you!
This is not your mission!
Hey, Rome? Hey, what's up, man?
Talk to me, come on!
- I can't do it.
- The hell you can't!
Come on, man!
You throw that thing
in reverse and get
your ass out here now!
Look, I can't do it, okay?
Listen to what I'm saying.
Now isn't the time!
I'ma stay up here
with the pilot.
We gonna circle
around and make sure
we holding it down from up here!
You're running
out of time!
The chute is guided by GPS!
You don't have to do anything!
Tej!
I'm already on it.
Hey, man, listen.
I'm sorry to
let y'all down, okay?
I'ma go ahead and stay up here.
No, brother.
I'm sorry to
let you down.
What?
What do you mean you're...
Tej! What are you doing?
Oh, shit!
Tej!
I hate you, Tej!
Get ready!
Ground's coming fast!
Come on, baby. Come on.
Oh, yeah!
Touchdown, baby!
Car check. Call it in.
Check.
I'm good. Let's do this.
Hello? Please, man.
Get me out of here, somebody!
No! The trees!
Oh, shit.
Sit tight, Roman.
We'll come back for you.
This is not the plan!
All right,
you got one chance
to hit them here, Dom.
You miss, they'll make
it to their black site
and they'll squeeze
whatever information
they need out of Ramsey.
The device and your chance
of ever getting Shaw
will be gone for good.
That ain't gonna happen.
I'll see you at the pickup.
Ramsey will be in the bus.
Then let's do this.
Captain, we have company.
Four cars, inbound.
Oh, shit!
Tej, shield!
I'm on the way.
All right, formation.
Bulletproof, baby.
Can't touch this
Punch it!
Strike! Ha-ha!
Guns free.
No!
Get out of the way!
Those aren't guns,
those are goddamn cannons!
Armor-piercing rounds!
Hook them up.
Brian, Tej, blow it!
Lock it up.
Huh?
Brian, you're up.
Little closer, Tej!
Ramsey?
Stay away from me!
Stay back!
Don't you touch me!
My name's Brian.
I'm gonna get you
out of here
but I'm gonna need you
to settle down, all right?
I'm gonna cut those
things off of you.
Sir?
Sir, we
have an unidentified
vehicle approaching.
Come on! Closer!
You're gonna
have to jump.
No! No! No!
We don't have time!
Come on!
We gotta get out of here.
Come on.
Look at me!
I'm not jumping!
You don’t jump,
we're gonna die. Okay?
You're jumping. Come on!
One.
Two!
Well, well, well.
Take my hand!
Welcome to the
party, Mr. Shaw.
Letty, stay with Brian.
Oh, shit!
What are you doing?
This is crazy!
Keeping you alive.
There's a Cliff. Cliff!
Cliff! There's a Cliff!
Shit!
Too slow.
Yeah!
I'm back, bitches!
You good?
Thank you.
Roman, get back
to the others.
What about you'?
Don't worry about me.
I have to say, I am impressed.
I would very much
like to know the
name of the man
who is causing me
so much trouble.
There's no way out of there.
What is he doing?
He's frozen like
a damn deer
in headlights.
Toretto ain't no deer.
Come on, Dominic.
Give us the girl,
and I'll let you live.
What are you going to do?
You might wanna
put on your helmet
for this one.
Helm...
Target the driver.
Damn it!
What is he thinking?
You're insane!
You're pointing the wrong way.
Am I now?
Fire on my mark.
Interesting.
Three!
Two!
Hold on.
One!
Fire!
Looks like our
demon love child worked.
That's one way down a mountain.
Where's Ramsey?
Hello Kitty is awake.
She don't look like
a hacker to me.
Oh, yeah? And what do
hackers look like?
They don't supposed
to look like that.
I'm just saying, like,
you know how they
normally wear them little,
weird glasses
that's all crooked,
and pimples all
over their face
from drinking soda?
I mean, trust me,
with a body like that,
you ain't gonna park it
behind a computer.
How are you feeling?
Did you hit your head?
Feeling nauseous?
Ears ringing? No?
Where's my shoe?
Oh, it flew off
when you crashed.
If you start experiencing
any of those things,
let me know, okay?
I don't know
whether to thank you
for rescuing me
or kick your ass
for throwing me
off a cliff.
Thank us or kick our ass, huh?
How about you tell us
where that device is?
I mailed it to a friend.
In Abu Dhabi.
That was pretty easy.
That other team
would have tortured you
for that information.
I didn't trust them.
I trust you.
Now, why would
you trust us?
You barely know us.
I know enough.
Ex-cop. Military,
something like that.
The way you took out
them guys shows training.
Tech guy, offended
by the hacker remark,
naturally.
Alpha.
Mrs. Alpha.
Joker
Wrong.
Double alpha.
Man candy. You know
what I'm saying?
Man, sit your candy ass down.
The disrespect is
real around here.
Life is binary.
Zeroes and ones.
Only two things
keep a group
like this together.
Fear or loyalty.
And I don't see
a drop of fear
among you guys.
Very impressive.
Just one thing.
They're not married.
She's so off,
it's crazy. You just
gonna roll with it?
You're telling me
there can't be
a double alpha in one group?
You work for US government?
We got similar interests.
Tej, call it in.
We're going to the Middle East!
Hey.
Hey, Dom.
It was pretty wild
on that mountain, huh?
No, it was too close.
But we got the job done.
You know what
the crazy thing is, is...
You miss the bullets.
Yeah, that's messed up, huh?
Brian, I've seen
you jump from trains,
dive from planes.
Hell, I saw your courage
the day I met you.
Right.
Want to know the bravest
thing I ever saw you do?
Be a good man to Mia.
Being a great father
to my nephew, Jack.
Everyone's looking
for the thrill,
but what's real is family.
Your family.
Hold on to that, Brian.
It's hotter than I
thought it would be.
Yeah, well, we are
in the desert,
so it would be hot.
Oh, no, I ain't talking
about the weather.
My, my, my.
Hmm.
Now, that is a woman
that's worth falling
out a plane for.
Get out of there, man,
I got dibs on that.
You've seen me looking at that.
Did you just say "dibs?"
What are you, in
the fourth grade?
Man, can you
just get out of there?
I mean,
it's a free market.
What are you talking about?
Get out of there.
Rock, paper, scissors for her.
Are you guys for real right now?
Look at you.
You both look whupped already.
You got stalker eyes.
I tried to call dibs
on Ramsey two years ago.
Her knee, my balls.
Trust me,
you don't wanna do that.
Hey! Ramsey!
Hello, Safar.
I see you make some new friends.
Yeah, some short-tempered
new friends.
I need the speed drive
I sent you. Where is it?
Oh, good. You will be
pleased to know I sold it.
You sold it?
You hear that?
I asked you to take care of it.
Why on earth would you sell it?
We're gonna need it back.
Impossible.
Safar, I stashed
something inside it.
It's important.
Okay, Okay-
Uh, good news. It is safe.
And the bad news?
It is very safe.
I sold it to a Jordanian
prince living up there.
Trust fund billionaire.
Said he wanted to use
it for his supercar.
Now, see, this?
This, I like.
Billionaire, supercar...
What makes it so super?
242 miles per hour, top speed.
And it's bulletproof.
242...
Am I the only one
aroused right now?
It's, like, you know
what I'm saying?
Whatever.
Where does he keep it?
In his penthouse.
Tower number one.
Now, why in the hell
would he keep his car
in his penthouse?
He's a billionaire, my friend.
He can do whatever he wants.
Now, tomorrow happens to be
the longest day of the year.
The prince wants to celebrate it
and host a party
tomorrow afternoon.
So you can get us
up there, right?
Sure.
But, uh, not dressed like that.
What?
Is something wrong?
There's a billion things wrong.
But not in this moment.
You look handsome.
I feel awkward.
You and me both.
Just seeing you
dressed like this
just reminds me of something.
Of what?
Old times.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Showtime.
No, no, no. Listen, man.
They're telling me
they party like
this every day.
On this level,
they party every day.
This is crazy. I might
have to move out here.
I think I'm gonna
start a new culture.
It's called Blarab.
You know,
like "black Arab."
How are we looking, Tej?
We're almost in position.
Okay, so this is how it works.
We got to move in sync
if we're gonna pull this off.
So let's go over it to make sure
everyone clearly
understands their roles.
Roman, that means you.
You know what,
you're being real
unprofessional right now, Tej.
The God's Eye chip
is hidden in a speed drive
installed in the prince's car,
which he keeps in
a safe room vault.
I make 8 to 10
plainclothes security.
Not to mention the prince
and his personal bodyguards.
Security cameras are
clustered by the north wall.
That's where the vault is.
We got to get in that vault,
we got to tap into
the security system,
which can be accessed
in the prince's bedroom.
All right, guys, I'm going in.
Excuse me.
Oh, I was just
looking for the...
The party is that way.
What?
This room is off-limits.
Now,
once we're tapped in,
Ramsey and I can
hack into the network
and pop the door
so you can get in
and get that shit.
Wait, wait, wait.
You missed a step.
What about my steps?
What am I supposed
to be doing?
No, we didn't miss anything.
You're special teams.
So when we need you,
do what you do best.
And that is?
Shine brightly like only
Roman Pearce can do.
Ha-ha.
See? Now we talking.
All right, Tej, I'm in.
All right, find the phone jack.
The tap always runs behind that.
It's gonna be
a 350-megahertz
CAT5e cable.
They probably got
a couple dozen back there,
but this will be
the bonded pair
with the plenum coat.
English, Tej.
It'll be the orange wire.
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
we are in the pilot seat.
Alright, Roman.
Do whatever it is you do.
It's your birthday, right?
Are you Jasmine?
Oh, God, no.
Not the birthday routine.
Take my hand-
Happy birthday to you.
This way, this way.
Excuse me, so sorry.
I'm coming through, sorry.
Right this way.
Listen, excuse me
one second.
My brother, my brother.
Man, you ain't supposed to...
Sir, thank you so much.
All right, listen, people.
Please, everybody,
gather around.
Understand something, right now.
Listen to what
I'm telling y'all.
We are here to celebrate
Jasmine's 18th birthday.
Happy birthday, my dear.
Happy birthday to you
To you
Oh, I wish I didn't see that.
Ramsey,
open it up for us.
Copy that. You're in.
Do you realize what this is?
Lykan HyperSport.
$3.4 million.
Zero-to-60 in less
than three seconds.
There's seven of these
things in the world,
and this guy keeps it
locked up in a vault.
Nothing's sadder
than locking
a beast in a cage.
And now I really want
to punch him in the face.
Okay-
Let's get to work.
You got this, right?
Go.
Would you believe
I knocked him
out with my charm?
You ain't
that charming, bitch.
No, no, no!
Tej, your magic trick
is failing.
We're losing systems.
I know.
I see it.
Tej, talk to me.
I'm trying,
but their security system
is locking us out.
All right, listen,
ladies and gentlemen...
Oh, there he is.
These are your dancers?
This is a party, baby!
Some of y'all probably
went to the bathroom
and noticed that all
the hairspray was missing.
Yep. She did it.
Thank you.
And we're so happy
for you to be here.
You look like you
got some missiles
underneath that dress. No?
He did not just...
Did you just say that?
Oh, shit! Not the gate!
Not the gate!
Brian, faster!
We're playing all
the defense we can up here
but we're gonna lose.
You gotta hurry up.
Thank God you showed up.
These parties bore me to death.
Aah!
Guys, get out of
there right now.
You've got an army
heading your way.
Brian, get out! Forget it!
Tej, we're taking the car.
This is what I do.
You know what I'm saying?
As far as I'm...
My man, what's...
Letty?
Letty, talk to me.
Are you okay?
Guys, I can't hold it.
I'm losing the final gate.
You gotta get out of there.
Tear out the dash!
Go through it.
Wait, wait, wait. Now,
just hold on, man.
Time to unleash the beast.
Let's go!
Stay with me,
I got you.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Dom, cars don't fly!
Cars don't fly!
Holy shit!
No brakes!
What?
Shit!
No, no, no!
No!
Oh!
Got it!
Get out!
Still miss the bullets, Brian?
Ah! There they are.
Disaster.
I'm sorry.
I get you an invite
to the most exclusive
party in Abu Dhabi.
Safar...
No, no, no.
You steal the host's
car, and you jump it
between two buildings.
Actually, it was
three buildings.
Oh!
Two, insult. Three, honor.
My bad.
Well, well, well.
I have to say,
you've got an interesting
interpretation there
of "low-key," Mr. Toretto.
You know, Dom,
I thought we had
an understanding.
Sometimes you have
to play the hand
you're dealt.
That's why I prefer
to be the dealer.
Good night.
Ah!
I'm being kicked out
of my own garage.
This is great.
Uh, may I?
Brian,
give it to him.
All that trouble for this little
thing.
With all due respect, Dom,
you really did
great work back there.
All of you.
All of my men
are now standing by
and are fully at your disposal.
Your call.
Ramsey.
Fire it up and find me Shaw.
Oh, damn, this is crazy.
Thank you.
All right, give me a second.
What is it doing now?
It's hunting.
Hacking into
the security cameras
at Etihad Towers.
That's the last
place you saw Shaw,
so that's where we'll start.
That's him, right there.
Wait, wait. What are these
numbers right here for?
It's bio-mapping Shaw's face.
It'll run it
against every camera.
Every audio device
in this hemisphere.
Bingo. Looks like
he's holed up here.
That's perfect.
Automated factory, no people,
lots of places to hide.
You just changed the face
of manhunts forever.
Congratulations.
Hey, can I check
my email real quick?
Dawn's up in two hours.
We're gonna go
take down Shaw then.
Go get changed.
We should go now.
Just you, your team, and me.
I thought you said at dawn.
My guys are racers,
the best drivers in the world.
But they ain't killers.
Told you
he'd say that.
I know you too well, Dom,
and I'm going with you.
Well, looks like we got
a nice little hunting party.
Let's go bag a shadow.
Ten klicks out, boys.
Get ready to rock and roll.
Here we go. Weapons hot.
You ready for this?
Yeah.
I hope you're enjoying
your last meal.
This is it?
This is all I warrant?
A dozen men?
I think you'll find
it's more than enough.
I'm ready
to meet my maker.
Are you?
What were
you expecting, Toretto?
To catch me off guard?
Me standing here,
waving a white flag?
You ever heard the saying,
"The enemy of my enemy
"is my friend?"
I don't have friends.
I got family.
Well, I got a lot of friends.
Two-two formation!
Sheppard, peel one!
Brian, leave it!
Get down!
l90ty0u.
JAKANDEI God's Eye.
You didn't really think
I was gonna walk in
there naked, did you?
You got hit bad.
Look, Toretto.
I know you won't listen to me.
You're not gonna want to
hear what I have to say.
But the truth is,
you really ought to
try that Belgian ale, man.
It's something special.
Belgian ale, huh?
Hey, we gotta get
you to a hospital.
No, you're not.
I carry my own health insurance.
SOCOM medics on standby.
They're already inbound.
Pull over, kid.
Dom,
you gotta protect Ramsey.
As long as she's alive,
she can lock them
out of God's Eye,
and they know that.
That means they're
not gonna stop coming
until they've got her.
And this time, when they come
they're gonna come
with everything they've got.
I'm not leaving you.
You're not.
I'm leaving you.
Go now, Dom.
A war is coming to us,
whether we like it or not.
If a war is coming,
we're gonna face them on
the streets we know best.
I'm all for winging it,
but this is crazy, man.
We got mercenaries with
some real heat on us.
I mean, I ain't scared
or nothing, but...
Man, I don't even have a gun!
Gun?
We got a whole city.
And we may have
more than that.
If they use God's Eye,
it'll tap the cameras
around town to
find our location.
Which means we could
plant a virus.
And then break in
when they access it.
So you're talking about
hacking my hacking device.
It's brilliant.
Yeah, but there's one problem.
The signal strength.
We can't start a hack
on them until they're
within a two-mile range.
- That's really close.
- Close?
These guys are military.
If they're within
two miles of us,
we're already dead.
I don't know about y'all,
but I didn't really plan
on dying today.
Only one way
to stay alive.
We play keep-away
with Ramsey.
What?
They can't hit
us if we keep moving.
And I'll take Shaw.
So, basically,
we're just gearing up
for a big game of
hot potato, huh?
Which car
is the potato?
Girl,
you're the potato.
Why does it feel like
I'm not gonna see you again?
I'll come back for that.
Promise?
Promise.
- Brian, are you okay?
- Mia, listen  to me.
Something's about to go down.
And if you don't hear
from me in 24 hours,
I need you to take
Jack and move on.
You understand?
You understand what I'm saying?
No, I can't do that, Brian.
No, I can't.
We're gonna have another baby.
It's a little girl.
And she's going to
need her father.
So you have to finish
what you're doing
and you have to
come home to her.
You have to come home to us.
I'm sorry I didn't
tell you before.
I was scared
you'd be disappointed
with domestic life.
You know,
the best decision I ever made
was stepping into the store
and buying that first sandwich.
It was such a bad sandwich.
I know, right?
But I ate a lot of them.
Uh...
I love you, Mia.
Don't do that.
What?
The way you said it.
It's like goodbye.
Say something else.
Okay. Kiss Jack for me.
I will.
I love you, Brian.
I love you, Mia.
One last ride.
Boot up God's Eye.
Find them.
I'm getting something.
I got a positive ID.
It's Toretto.
God's Eye is placing him
at Hill and Seventh.
Should we follow him?
No. Let Shaw
take care of him.
Find Ramsey.
Yes, sir.
I don't know
why we gotta keep
driving around like this.
Why can't we just
pull over somewhere,
park, gather our
thoughts in, like,
a bunker somewhere?
Because it does not
work like that.
We gotta stick close
enough to the bad guys
in order to get in range
for Ramsey to hack them.
But we gotta be mobile
enough not to get shot
like fish in a barrel.
So, do me a favor,
focus on the mission
and keep us from getting killed.
Got her. Target acquired.
She's riding shotgun
in a blue GT-R.
Guys, they're here.
How many cars?
Uh, none.
And that's kind of the problem.
Okay, let's give them the tour.
Break on my mark.
Three, two, one.
Go!
Splitting up won't work.
Can't hide from God's Eye.
They're in range.
Ramsey, start the hack.
Initiating.
Now.
Sir, I think
someone's trying
to hack the system.
It's Ramsey.
Send in the Predator!
Take her out!
Releasing Predator.
I think we lost the chopper.
I think we got
bigger problems than that!
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
We're going old school!
Watch out!
It's coming
back around!
Predator's back on him.
- Ready missiles!
- Roger that.
Fire!
Oh, shit!
Football's hot!
I need to lateral!
Rome, where are you?
Running back charging in!
Meet me on Third and Spring.
You got it!
I'm halfway there.
Grab your computer!
Get in the window!
Why?
Do it! Now!
You gotta go! Right now!
Fire!
Come on!
Hit!
He made it!
I can't believe
we pulled that off.
Wait, wait, wait.
We're still being hacked.
What?
God's Eye is
still tracking Ramsey.
Keep the drone
in pursuit of her.
The signal has to be
coming from somewhere.
Back to
throw. Here comes the blitz-
Number 94 sacks him!
Breaking news
out of Los Angeles tonight.
In what can only be described
as vehicular warfare,
police are engaged in
a high-speed pursuit...
I got it. They're
piggybacking the hack
off that satellite
tower right there.
Take it out!
Toretto.
Wait. What happened?
We were almost there.
They've cut the signal!
I can't finish the hack!
What do you mean?
Brian, they took out the tower!
Dad,
what's going on?
Daddy's gotta go to work.
All right, baby girl.
Elena's gonna be here
in a little bit.
You know our drill.
Give me three for the road.
You thought this was
gonna be a street fight?
You're goddamn right it is.
There has to be another way.
Wait. I'm seeing
half a dozen
cell towers between
Sixth and State.
Brian, if you can get to the top
of any one of those
buildings around there,
we can reroute
the signal manually
and finish the job.
I'm on it.
Sir, did you hear that?
O'Conner is on foot,
heading for a repeater.
He's going to try to
reinitiate the hack.
Keep the drone on the girl.
Net,
O'Conner's on foot
somewhere between
Sixth and State-
Don't let him make it there.
Them boys is on us!
Man, them boys
ain't ready for this!
Shit!
First the tank, then the plane.
Now we got a spaceship?
That's not a spaceship,
that's a drone!
Oh, it's a drone?
Now, you gonna break it down
and be articulate
like you already know
what the hell is going on?
Shut your ass up
and drive the car!
Letty, the football's on fire!
We need help!
Hang on! I'm coming!
Ramsey, get ready to go again!
Drone has missile lock.
Fire!
Target destroyed.
Let's see if we have a connection.
If I can get back in...
Wait, wait, wait!
God's Eye still has her.
How can that be?
Get up. Come on!
Let's go! Let's go!
They switched her
under the bridge.
What?
Gotta get out of here.
It's on your trail
and it's coming fast.
Got it.
So, if this car goes down,
who's coming to save us?
Save us, honey?
We're it.
Where are they now?
Six blocks east, hauling ass.
Where are we
headed, Tej?
There's a service
elevator past
the maintenance sector.
It'll take you
directly up to the repeater.
Brian, you gotta hurry!
Too slow!
It's coming back!
We'll lose them in the tunnel
Got it.
Fire!
I can't shake this thing!
Predator has missile lock.
Take it out!
No way.
Wait! What happened?
Sir, someone just
double-tapped our drone.
What?
Hey, did you bring the cavalry?
Woman, I am the cavalry.
Of course you are.
Who is that?
That's Hobbs.
I'm at the repeater.
The access cable's in the base.
Just plug it into your phone
and Ramsey will
be back online.
Ramsey, go!
Brian did it. We're back in!
We've got God's Eye back.
We lost the God's Eye!
What? Shit!
Military's inbound.
Three minutes and closing.
We need to get
the hell out of here.
Tej, Roman, I'm on my way!
All right, homie,
I'll see you there.
I have eyes on Toretto.
Shaw is in the way.
Then it seems our
friendship is at an end.
Do it!
Thing about street fights,
the street always wins.
Goodbye, Toretto.
Take him out!
Take down the bastard!
This son of a...
No!
Duck!
I need some
help over here!
We're getting nailed!
I need some backup!
No! No! Son of a bitch!
He's getting away!
No! Stop him!
Don't miss.
Dom!
Come on, buddy.
Is he breathing?
I want you to keep his head
tilted up, all right?
Keep it back like this.
Pinch his nose,
keep his head tilted.
Breathe into him, now. Go.
Good. Come on, Dom.
Come on, Dom. Come on!
God damn it!
You come on! You breathe!
Go, go! Breathe.
Come on. Damn it. Let's go.
Come on, Dom,
I need you to breathe.
Come on! Come on, Dom!
Come back! Come on, buddy.
Stop it.
Dom, come on! Come on!
Back off!
Will you stop?
Breathe into him.
Get off of him!
You breathe into him!
Back off!
Please.
Dom.
Dom, baby. I know
you're hurting right now.
But I want you to listen.
Stay awake
and focus on me.
I remember everything.
It came to me like a flood.
I remember that night
in the Dominican Republic.
The night we got married.
If you die, I die.
And I'm not ready to
leave this place yet.
This moment is still ours.
I remember everything.
I remember it all.
It's about time.
Why didn't you tell me
we were married?
Because you can't tell
someone they love you.
Holy shit.
You sure you brought
enough backup with you,
Hobbs?
Oh, they ain't mine.
They're here to protect you
from me killing your ass.
You do know none of this
will keep me, right?
Well, once you dig through
38 feet of concrete and steel,
my fist and a body bag
will be waiting for
you on the other side.
So I suggest you
get to digging, boy.
Whoo-hoo!
Daddy! Come play.
Yeah.
Look at him. Look at him.
Yeah, buddy.
- Duty calls.
- It does.
Hey, babe, come on.
Let's get Mama. Yeah!
Here we go.
Because the sun is out,
I'm kind of medium rare,
but I can get,
like, well done.
Like, really dark.
What you nudging me for?
Close your mouth
for two seconds.
Just open your eyes, man.
Beautiful.
That's where he belongs.
Home.
Where he's always belonged.
Things are gonna
be different now.
One more time.
You aren't going to say goodbye?
It's never goodbye.
Hey. You thought
you could leave
without saying goodbye?
I used to say
I live my life
a quarter-mile at a time.
And I think that's
why we were brothers.
Because you did, too.
No matter where you are,
whether it's
a quarter-mile away
or halfway across the world,
You'll always be with me.
And you'll always be my brother.
- No way!
- Yeah.
This is the Cuban spirit.
Dom. Dom.
You know I can't make a
living without my car.
Not my problem, bro.
Dominic Toretto, I heard about you.
Welcome to my island.
Why you hookin' up my cousin's car?
He needed money, I gave it to him.
He can't pay, I take the car.
I just need a few more days.
"Few more days" wasn't part of the deal.
Come on. You make a deal,
you gotta live up to it.
You make a deal, you gonna live up to it.
"Gonna" live up to it?
Oh, so you're one of those types.
You take everyone's ride,
and then ship it back to the States?
You watch your mouth.
Now you got a problem.
I'm gonna keep it about the cars.
You want a car, get it the right way.
How?
Race for it.
I already own it, bro.
Not that car.
Mine.
Dom, his car is
the fastest car on the island.
Do you know what he has under that hood?
He knows it doesn't matter
what's under a hood.
The only thing that matters
is who's behind the wheel.
You think so?
I know so.
Then race his car.
And we ain't racing no quarter-mile, here.
We race the Cuban mile.
Done.
I appreciate what you're trying to do,
but my car is the slowest car on the island.
Was.
Pull the seats, the doors, the battery...
If it ain't the motor, take it off.
Laughing gas?
Nah, Fed. This is Cuban NOS.
You guys are crazy.
What are you doing?
Poor man's turbo.
Pull the vacuum line and hold on.
Old trick that Buster used to play,
in case of emergencies.
You know that's way too much
boost for that engine.
It's gonna be fast.
It's gonna be a bomb.
Only needs to go a mile.
Vámonos!
That car belongs in the trash, bro!
- Where are they going?
- I don't know. Let's go!
Ghost him.
Sí.
Adiós, Toretto!
Okay, Buster.
Let's see if this works.
That's impossible.
Look out!
A deal's a deal.
You won my car.
And you earned my respect.
Keep your car.
Your respect is good enough for me.
Yo, cousin...
Sorry about your car.
Yours was too slow for a Toretto, anyway.
Your Impala? Are you serious?
Look at that smile.
I love it when you smile.
You make me happy.
Mmm, I think this place makes you happy.
It's like it speaks to you.
You remember that guy, the racer and his dad?
The one with the boat engine under the hood?
Yeah!
- Yes.
- Of course.
I was looking at them, and I...
And I couldn't help but to imagine
what you'd be like if you were a dad.
No, no, no! I'm not pregnant.
Is that what you want?
It's not about what I want or what you want.
It's about why we haven't asked the question.
- What?
- You need a hand?
Yeah, I think I do.
- Sounds like you're not getting any fuel.
- Yeah?
Probably the shut-off solenoid.
Let's see if we can get some power to it.
What brings you to Cuba?
The same thing that brings
everyone else to Cuba.
Culture, people, the beauty.
What brings you to Cuba?
- Work.
- Must be casual Friday.
How's that honeymoon going, Dom?
Your fuel relay is missing.
I know.
I love to play games.
I've beaten the best of 'em.
But I'm kind of in a rush,
so if you've got something to say to me...
Oh, this is a very different game,
that I can assure you.
This... There's something
much greater at work here.
This is fate.
I choose to make my own fate.
Not today.
Is this the road you take
to your apartment every morning?
What else is different, Dom?
Was Santiago's closed?
Did you have to cross two blocks
to go get your Cuban coffees?
What is it, black, no sugar?
Yeah.
I put a lot of work into
getting you here today.
Well, now that I'm here, what do you want?
I want you to work for me.
Work for you?
Oh, I could've saved you a lot of time, then.
See, I don't work for anyone.
You can't walk away from this, Dom.
We're gonna have this conversation,
one way or the other.
You see, that's the funny thing about fate.
It's cunning.
It can bring you beautiful things,
and it can also bring you moments like this.
Oh, you're gonna want to work for me.
You're gonna betray your brothers,
abandon your code, and shatter your family.
You see, your team is about to go up
against the only thing they can't handle.
What's that?
You.
Oh, and, Dom,
I wouldn't mention this to anyone.
They are gonna be hitting us
with everything they got.
So we wanna engage with maximum speed.
Neutralize their shooters,
and then move on to our objective.
There's two things
I want you to keep in mind.
Number one, I chose you for this squad
because you are the most
fearsome warriors on the planet.
And number two, you go out there,
you do your job, and you take 'em down.
Everyone. And I mean everyone.
Mani's and pedi's at the mall later on today.
Monarchs!
What?
I don't wanna play anymore.
All right, let's go, girls.
Let's go, let's go!
Final two minutes.
Quite the cheering section.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's the moms.
They come out to support the kids.
Except there seem to be more moms than kids.
Way more moms.
Yeah. It's a big soccer town.
Let's go, girls!
So, your intel was spot-on.
That Damocles 7 EMP weapon
that went missing in the Gulf?
Arms dealers from the Liberation
Front have it in Berlin.
Shit!
This thing can wipe out
an entire electrical grid in a major city.
No lights, no power.
Instant Stone Age.
Chloe, Maya,
you can't let her run by you like that.
- Let's go, let's go! Cross!
- Agent Hobbs, this is a Class Four WMD.
Do you have any idea what's at stake here?
Yes, I know exactly
what is at stake here, okay?
If the Pink Butterflies beat my Red Dragons,
that means we lose the championship.
Which means I have 20 little girls who
are crying, and that's not a good thing.
Which then means I have to spend
a lot of time in ice-cream shops
and a lot of time at Tay Tay concerts.
Tay Tay?
Taylor Swift. Gotta be shittin' me.
Get it together, okay?
Let's go, girls!
We need you to do this.
It's a lot of lives at stake.
All right, but I need to be clear here.
The US government cannot sanction
this operation in any way.
- You're on your own.
- Hey.
If this thing goes sideways,
you don't just get burned.
You go to prison.
And there's nothing we can do to get you out.
Let me tell you something.
The only thing that I love more
than saving lives is my daughter.
So, if you don't shut up
with this government bullshit right now,
and start showing some team spirit
and respect for the Red Dragons,
I'm gonna have all 20 of them line up
and kick you right in the tay-tay.
Go Dragons!
Say it again.
Attaboy. Go Dragons.
Go Dragons.
- I'm open.
- She's open! Go, go!
Yes!
That is my daughter right there. Yes.
Yes, come here.
How did I do?
Awesome.
Nice job, kid.
- Daddy's gotta go to work?
- Uh, yeah. Daddy's gotta go to work.
Now, you're gonna need
to get a team you can trust.
Oh, I already got one.
Hey, Dom.
Hey, Hobbs.
I got a job in Berlin
and I need a favor, brother.
No problem.
I'll grab the team and meet you in Berlin.
Thanks, man. I'll see you soon.
You were only supposed
to create a diversion, Roman.
That was a diversion!
How many of the damn explosives did you use?
I don't know, Tej.
- All of it?
- Wait, all of it?
Roman, Jesus Christ.
We got more of your fan club ahead.
They're still on us!
These guys are taking this personal.
Roman, we just blew up their facility
and stole their EMP.
Other than your doctor's cold finger,
I'd say it's about as personal as it can get.
Phase Two!
Phase Two? So you just
gonna keep that to yourself?
What happened to Phase One?
What about that part?
Yeah. Remember the airplane?
Everyone drove their cars out but you?
I told you, my engine seized up.
It's your balls that seized up.
Just follow my lead, okay?
And, Roman, whatever you do, don't think.
Huh?
Tej, drop it!
Bombs away.
Split, now!
Holy...
Great plan, Tej.
But just so you know, you missed some.
Oh, just wait for it.
Oh, shit!
I hate you, Tej!
Got your ass.
You good?
I'll see you when it's done.
All right, great job, team.
Let's break off and meet me
at the safe house.
A hell of a job, brother.
When we get back to the base,
the beer's on me.
You lost your goddamn mind, Toretto?
Toretto, you put hands on that thing,
you're gonna have the whole world
gunning for you, including me.
I don't know what you're doing,
but you better think about this, Toretto.
It ain't too late to stop this.
It is now.
That sumbitch just crossed us.
- What?
- Wait a second, what are you talking about?
Dom took the EMP.
Bullshit.
Where are you?
It's too late for me. Get outta here.
Saw that look in his eye,
and I've seen that look before.
Dominic Toretto just went rogue.
All right, I got his phone records, y'all.
It's a whole bunch of calls
to untraceable numbers.
Burner phones, right?
Nah, scrambler.
Same number, but they got some sort
of micro-router to bury the signal path,
which means Dom is clearly communicating
with somebody that's above our pay grade.
Look, I don't know Dom as well as you,
but if we just look at the facts,
Dom's been having highly
encrypted conversations
with some mysterious person.
He took out Hobbs.
He stole an EMP. Now he's disappeared.
So, what are you saying?
Maybe we should consider
the fact that Hobbs is right.
Dom did go rogue.
Letty.
Before you judge the man,
remember, you're breathing right
now because he saved your life.
You just gonna let her bump
your shoulder like that?
I'm just saying,
that was a little aggressive.
What you gonna do, email her?
Check.
Moment, will you, fellas?
Thank you.
Well, this is an exciting new look.
It's a little tight in the crotch, as always.
What boy-band bus did she fall out of?
It's my new junior associate.
He's working with me on this. All yours.
Mr. Nobody and I have been given
the authority to get you out of this.
All you have to do is agree
to the terms and you're free.
What's training wheels talking about?
What terms?
Confess to your crimes in Berlin.
Treason, international espionage,
massive destruction of civic property.
You do that, we close the case.
- And?
- And the DSS blacklists you.
Germany loves that.
Officially, you will be a criminal.
Wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You need to work on your delivery, all right?
Unofficially...
You're off the books. You come work with me.
I'm not a criminal.
Luke, come on. Labels.
There is no confession.
There are no backroom deals.
I got myself into this,
I'm gonna get myself out of it.
- You know that.
- I do, and that's what I told him.
Well, there you have it.
Good luck in the courts, man.
What about your daughter?
You know, if you're not gonna do it for
your country, at least do it for your kid.
Big mistake, kid.
Hold on. Luke, Luke.
He's still working from the manual.
I mean, he doesn't even
really know the rules.
Now, come on, give him a break.
Give me a break.
Luke.
Appreciate it.
It's good to see you, Nobody.
You, too.
Rule number one...
Know your audience.
I gave you your shot. You shit the bed.
Now I'm gonna show you how to get this done.
You're dead, cop. Dead!
I'm gonna slice some bacon
off your back, pig.
Well, well, well...
Luke Hobbs behind bars.
Would you look at that.
The bent cop got his day.
You know, that color looks good on you.
Yeah, it'll look a whole hell of a lot
better with your blood on it.
Yeah, good luck with that, Hercules.
Lawman gone bad, huh?
Such a cliché.
Oh, well, welcome to the club.
I wouldn't get that twisted, son.
We ain't in no club,
we got nothing in common.
And unlike you, I ain't gonna be here long.
What, you bring a shovel, did you?
Because it's 38 feet of steel and concrete.
Or so I've been told.
Better get to digging.
Wanker.
Yeah.
Move.
Say that again.
If I say it again, it'll be to a corpse.
I'm gonna enjoy this.
Welcome back, Dom.
Nice job out there.
You excited about tonight?
You're going on this?
You're with me, Dom.
Showing me your shoe collection?
Yep.
A pair for every occasion.
You have enough guns in here
to outfit a small army, huh?
Oh, this is just the tip of the iceberg.
You know what I like about you, Dom?
You're a genuine outlaw.
I mean, you're a man
who lives by his own rules.
Which is surprising,
because when I saw you in Cuba,
I heard about a guy who almost
killed you with a motorcycle,
and you let him keep his car?
Oh, that confused you?
Hmm.
'Course I could've taken his car.
But it's about something bigger.
This way...
I changed him.
That's not your responsibility.
- But it's who I am.
- Is it?
Let me ask you something, Dom.
What's the best thing in your life?
- Family.
- No, it's not.
Not if you're being honest.
It's the 10 seconds between start and finish,
when you're not thinking about anything.
No family, no obligations.
Just you.
Being free.
I gotta tell you,
this whole saving-the-world, Robin Hood
nonsense you've been doing recently?
It's bullshit. It's not you.
Be who you are.
Why live only a quarter mile at a time
when you can live your whole life that way?
Is that it?
Is that all those
bloated-out muscles will give ya?
All show and no go.
Oh, I got plenty of go.
You must've misplaced that when I kicked
your arse up and down that office of yours.
Yeah.
Just like you Brits, rewriting history, huh?
All I know is, it wasn't me that was
thrown out of a four-story window.
Jumped.
I jumped out of a four-story window,
saving my partner's life.
'Cause where I'm from,
we don't settle fights by throwing bombs.
Well, that's funny, because where I'm from,
we don't need women to run to our rescue.
I mean, do you really believe
you can stand in front of me
and beat me in a straight-up,
old-fashioned fist fight?
Let me tell you something.
Me and you, one-on-one, no one else around.
I will beat your ass like a Cherokee drum.
Maybe one day we'll find out.
Oh, you better hope that day never comes.
I said no, Mr. Nobody.
I'm not leaving this cell.
I'll get out my way.
The right way!
Hey! Why's the door open?
Get back in your cell!
Relax. It's just a malfunction.
- Get back!
- Just a malfunction.
Stop him! Don't let him get away!
Hobbs!
I've been waiting a long time for this.
Keep waiting, bitch.
Rubber bullets. Big mistake.
Well, that took longer than I expected.
- Two questions.
- Yeah.
- My daughter?
- With your sister.
Toretto?
It's interesting you ask.
This is my new base. Welcome to nowhere.
It's a little sterile for you.
Listen, there's something
I wanna talk to you about after.
Hey, listen, guys. Thanks...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What? Handcuffs? What is this?
It's called abuse of power.
You told me to round them up.
I didn't tell you to hand...
Cut 'em loose. Oh, man. This is embarrassing.
I'm sorry, guys, really, I...
So, this is how you treat old friends?
Friends? We don't even really know
who the hell this guy is.
Doesn't matter who I am, Tej.
I'm, like, nobody, okay?
Nobody. So, then, who is he?
Him? He's nothing. He's, like, less than me.
Clearly, we're getting nowhere with nobody.
I've been in here for four hours,
and my ribs are showing.
I don't know about y'all, but I'm out.
- I wouldn't recommend that.
- What?
Well, thanks to your botched Berlin job,
you all made Interpol's
Top 10 Most Wanted list.
- Top 10.
- Mmm-hmm.
That's all right.
- Well, not you, Roman.
- What do you mean?
You just missed the cut.
You're number 11, so...
- I'm... I missed?
- Yeah.
That's impossible!
What number did they come in at?
Six, eight, nine, ten.
- She's 10?
- Mmm-hmm.
That's impossible. There's no way she's a 10.
Oh, she's definitely a 10.
How about we focus on someone who
we're not gonna find on anybody's list.
We're awaiting hard confirmation,
but I believe that's the cyber
terrorist known as Cipher.
Wait, no. Cipher's an organization.
Not a person.
Not according to our sources.
What does she want?
No one knows.
Cipher is like a digital act of God.
They... Well, she can manipulate
world systems from the shadows.
Anything that can be hacked
is hers to play with.
And here's the kicker.
You'll never find her linked to any of it.
Her digital identity is scrubbed
every few seconds, worldwide.
So, basically, she's the bogeyman.
Damn, she's one of the hottest
bogeymans I've ever seen.
I mean, if y'all know her,
tell her to get at your boy.
- What are you, 12?
- That was my shin, mother...
Let's just say, people are scared
of the hacker group Anonymous.
But even Anonymous won't mess with her.
What the hell does
any of this have to do with us?
Probably nothing, Letty,
but I do find it interesting that,
apparently, for some reason,
she's now working with this guy.
He's already delivered a fully
operational EMP into her hands.
Detonate that, they can turn any city
in the world into a war zone.
So, then, what is it you're suggesting we do?
Maybe we find Dom, huh?
Well, first, let's catch him,
and then figure out why he's turned.
So, y'all want us to track Dom.
Yeah, I know, Roman, it's kind of a big job.
It's impossible.
Which is why I'm bringing in
an extra pair of hands.
Ah, my day just got
a whole hell of a lot better.
Mr. Nobody, you wanna tell me why
you just put me in a room with this
tea-and-crumpets eating, criminal sumbitch?
What a big mouth on a small head,
coming from Prisoner 6753.
Don't think we've forgotten
everything that you've done.
We are not teaming up with this guy.
Let's get one thing clear.
I ain't on your team.
I don't care about you,
your crew, or your little family.
I'm here for Cipher.
What are you gonna do,
apply for a job? Head Asshole?
You know, I think that tight T-shirt's
cutting off the circulation to your brain.
You should get a bigger size.
Cipher came to me first.
Wanted me to steal Nightshade for her.
When I said no, she went after my brother.
Ah, yes, brother Owen.
Who could forget him, huh?
Former hell-raiser and current guest
at a nasty little black site prison.
Cipher corrupted him and left him for dead.
So, if I get a shot to take her down,
believe me, Flex, I'm taking it.
You're taking my boot right up your ass,
is what you're taking.
Guys, guys. The fastest way
to find Cipher is through Toretto.
Now, aside from myself,
there's only two men in the world
that have ever managed to actually
track him down with any success.
And guess what. They're both
standing in front of me right now.
So, like it or not,
you two are gonna work together.
You got that?
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
Am I the only one seeing this?
Oh, this ought to be good.
Use God's Eye.
We put our lives on the line,
running around the world
trying to figure this thing out.
It can find anybody, right?
Let's use it to find Dom.
Roman, that is a great idea.
Did you hear that? "Great idea."
No, no, no, don't tune it out. Huh?
Mr. Nobody, let's fire it up, huh?
Got him. He's in London.
Yeah.
Wait. We've got a second match in Hong Kong.
Beijing and Seoul.
And Tokyo.
And just about every
other major city on the planet.
And so, God's Eye was where we started.
But Cipher's already created an evasion
that masks their location by pinging
random spots all over the globe,
but it was a good thought, Roman.
So, she's made my program obsolete.
And that, Ramsey, is why you're here.
See, simple solutions
aren't gonna cut it here, slick.
Why you look at me when you say that?
Wait a second. Wait, wait.
Simple solutions might just cut it.
You see, in order for God's Eye
to give off all these false pings,
means they have to be using a FLEA relay.
Watch these two.
Which means it has
a decaying sync randomizer.
Which we can reverse...
And track it back to the originating source
and find Dom's true location.
I'm telling you, they got skills.
That was my idea.
That's what I was saying. Remember in there?
All right, let's try this.
It's working.
Time you wanna check your manual
and start organizing a force response.
Let's get a hold of
our international assets...
He's still green.
Yeah, like fresh baby shit.
As soon as we have Toretto's location,
I want to mobilize.
Let's get a hold of a better asshole.
No one respects you... Cover.
Get away from me.
All right, they're not in China.
Or Russia.
Europe's clear.
But this one's not going away.
This is interesting.
Why?
Because that's here.
Did you all enjoy that?
Next-generation concussion grenade.
It scrambles your senses.
Don't worry, it'll wear off in an hour.
Probably.
Hello, Deckard. Nice to see you again.
Look at this, body's not even cold, Dom.
Your family's already replacing you.
You chose the losing team.
I guess your brother is smarter than you.
Smart move, embedding God's Eye
into the mainframe.
Irritating to make me have to come
all the way down here to get it, but...
Let's go.
Dom!
You're gonna turn your back
on family? Just like that?
Let's go.
You okay?
That wasn't him.
I don't know what she's got on him,
but that wasn't Dom.
Brian would know what to do.
No!
We can't bring Brian and Mia into this.
We agreed on that.
I know.
Back there, was that for her, for me, or you?
And was it even necessary?
Necessary?
Nothing is necessary.
Everything is a choice.
And I simply made one. But so did you.
You could've stopped me,
but you chose not to.
I wonder what Letty thought about that.
The problem with putting
your foot on a tiger's neck
is you can never let it up.
I think I need to remind you
why you chose to be here.
Elena.
Dom?
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't have come.
Nothing could have kept me away.
Now she has the three of us.
Do you wanna see him?
See Papa?
See Papa.
Papa.
When I realized I was pregnant,
you had just found out Letty was alive.
So I decided when Letty and you got
back from your honeymoon,
I was going to tell you.
But then she took us before I had the chance.
His name?
I call him Marcos.
But that's his middle name.
I thought his father
should give him his first name.
I'm sorry, Dom.
There's nothing to be sorry for.
Whatever happens,
just save our son.
Your son.
Good visit?
I know. I know what you're thinking.
I just let the guards go, so there's
only two opponents in the room.
Rhodes has the gun,
so you'll take him out first.
I know you.
And then you're thinking, Elena's a cop.
Maybe the two of you
can fight your way out of here.
So much to think about.
Let me make it easier for you.
Do with it as you wish.
Have you heard of Choice Theory, Dom?
There is a bunch of axioms,
but only two you really need
to concern yourself with.
One, the only person's behavior
we can control is our own.
And, two, the only thing we can truly give
another person is information.
So, let me give you some.
You see these cameras in here?
The moment you make a move,
highly-paid men with weapons
will make their way into this room
with one very specific instruction.
It's not to save me.
It's to kill your son.
Now, that's a lot of bullets,
and it only takes one
for you to lose everything.
So, I have to ask you,
because I know family is so important to you.
Is that really a choice you want to make?
Because I'm ready if you are.
If I pull this trigger,
and God knows I want to,
if I killed everyone on this plane,
I still couldn't get in there.
'Cause of your two-man fail-safe system.
Since I'm alone,
I got no choice!
I didn't think so.
You want to see the old Dom?
Watch.
Bitch.
- Don't, don't.
- Sweet dreams.
Please!
Damn it.
She wiped it all. Took God's Eye.
That was the one thing
we could use to find them.
We lost everything.
What do you got, Princess?
Finding Toretto.
But I got a couple of minutes to spare,
if you want me to send you
to the hospital. Again.
- Yo, Rules.
- First off, that's not my name.
- Little Nobody.
- Don't call me that.
Oh, that's definitely sticking.
Great. Do me a favor and tell Your Majesty
over there that we're gonna find Toretto.
We find Toretto together as a team.
And when this is all over with,
I'm happy to slap that
whisker biscuit right off his face.
Wait a minute, guys,
I think Deckard's actually onto something.
How do you think Dom and Cipher
got into the country without us knowing?
Ghost flights.
I thought untraceable aircraft
was all Internet conspiracy stuff.
It's not.
Satellites and radar grids
all across the globe
shift like an ocean.
They've got channels that open and close.
And theoretically, if you know the right
people who know the right patterns...
You can fly right through the blind
spots completely undetected.
So you know where Dom is headed?
Yeah. New York.
You see there, Luke?
You guys are gonna get along just great.
Which proves rule number two,
you never lose everything.
Fire up the chopper.
Well, guys, have a ball in the Big Apple.
And why are we traveling like this again?
Because Dom took God's Eye,
so we need to stay off the grid.
But like this?
Look here, man.
Before I throw up in my mouth,
let me ask you, what are we doing here?
That's a good question, Roman.
Let me show you.
Welcome to our new base of operations.
No, seriously. What is this place?
This is heaven.
It's the agency garage.
They call it the Toy Shop.
This is where we house every vehicle
seized from drug dealers on the East Coast.
Now, Mr. Nobody said that if we're
gonna have a chance at catching Dom,
we're gonna have to be damn fast.
Figured this would help.
We got a tank.
750 horsepower,
6.6 liter, V8 Duramax engine
with an M153 CROWS remotely
operated weapon station on top.
You didn't get this from drug dealers.
No. No, that, uh,
the United States Army lent me.
See, the Army's developing machines like this
that soldiers can drive from a mile away,
so they can stay safe and alive.
But, luckily, there's a backup driver's seat
for those of us that like
to get more "hands on."
I'm sitting here wondering this whole time,
will this thing fit in valet
at Cheesecake Factory?
No one is getting "hands on."
She doesn't go on city streets.
Wow. I'm in love.
Again, no, no.
That's a million-dollar show car.
The point is to not draw attention.
It's reverse psychology.
Dom would never see it coming.
It's neon orange.
The International Space Station
would see it coming.
Go choose anything less conspicuous.
No, no, no. Calipers are my...
- This is ridiculous.
- Not happening.
Hey, my man,
you can put that down right there.
This is a gift, a real gift.
I know what you're doing.
I like your beard.
You're Blanta. Black Santa?
No, I'm serious. Put it down right there.
What are you doing?
Engine's misfiring. I gotta check it out.
No, that's not part of the plan, Dom.
Clearly.
But unless you want
the engine to seize on the job...
You have five minutes.
Five minutes.
I want another visual.
I got an ATM.
I don't like this.
I want to see Toretto.
- There are no more cameras.
- Then find something!
Punch in on something reflective.
A car mirror, anything.
Do you know who I am?
It's why I'm here.
Do you know what I'm capable of?
I'll give you until I finish me cuppa.
And I'm fucking thirsty.
I've got limited time,
so I won't take up too much of yours.
No, you've already taken everything
I have of value, Mr. Toretto.
What more could you possibly want?
To give you something back.
Talk to me.
Something's not right here.
First time I saw my son
was behind a bulletproof glass.
When he reached for me, I couldn't hold him.
It's the worst pain I ever felt.
I know you know exactly how that feels.
Maybe we could change that.
Now, why do I think
you're about to suggest something
really dodgy, Mr. Toretto?
It's why I'm here.
Jesus, punch in on something.
I'm not liking this. Something's not right.
- Rhodes, you close?
- Yeah.
Go.
The delivery truck's moving.
I know.
"Captain Deckard Shaw: distinguished
himself by acts of gallantry"
"at the risk of his life above
and beyond the call of duty."
"His bold actions saved the lives
of hostages and his teammates."
"Recommendation: Victoria Cross."
Highest honor the British
government has ever given
to a traitor.
Something about this whole thing
that just doesn't add up to me.
Well, that would be
the same kind of funny math
that says a DSS agent who has
a Silver Star for valor stole an EMP.
Sound familiar, huh?
You want to give me a hand?
- On three?
- Yeah.
One, two, three.
You know what, Twinkle Toes?
In another life, I bet me and you
could've done some serious damage.
- Yeah, we could've.
- Yeah.
Shame I'm gonna have to bounce your head
off the fender when this is all over.
Ah, well, with all due respect, Captain,
when this whole thing is over,
we're gonna find a location,
and I'm gonna knock your teeth
so far down your throat,
you're gonna stick a toothbrush
right up your ass to brush them.
Give me God's Eye.
God's Eye, active.
Good.
Let's find us a Russian.
I spy with my little eye,
a Minister of Defense.
Upload those coordinates to Dom's nav.
Copy that.
He's in the third car.
It's a Guard Class limousine.
Where's my team?
- Where's his team?
- There's no sign of them yet.
They're off the grid.
They're probably just
bunkered down somewhere.
We're closing in on 'em.
You guys ready?
One thing I can guarantee,
Dom, no one's ready for this.
I want every chip with a zero-day
exploit in a two-mile radius
around that motorcade now.
There's over a thousand of them.
Hack 'em all.
It's zombie time.
I'd buckle up if I were you.
What are you doing?
Safety sensors overridden.
Thank you.
Hey!
Target the motorcade.
And here they come.
Ouch.
Police escort down.
Take out the lead and follow cars.
- Two more down.
- They're still under warranty.
We got an army of cars driving themselves!
Send backup, send SWAT!
I don't care if you send
the goddamn Boy Scouts,
just send 'em some help!
Now, that's Dom.
The motorcade just turned on Seventh.
Perfect. Make it rain.
Target immobilized.
You're up, Dom.
Give me the case.
Good work, Dom.
Meet you at the pickup.
I think I know where my team's at.
- Where?
- Right in front of me.
This is on you.
Get out of there, Dom.
Guys, I know why Dom's here.
Police scanners are saying
he stole a nuclear football.
It's over, Toretto.
Get your ass outta the car now.
So, that's how you wanna play this?
Let's play.
Don't do this, Dom.
He's going for it!
- What are you doing?
- It's a trap!
Damn it!
Now I know what it feels like
to be every cop ever chasing us!
I'm gonna get a little closer.
I'm gonna PIT him.
Oh, so, you just gonna PIT Dom?
Little Nobody has clearly
lost his little mind.
I'm on him.
Easy. Work together.
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh, sh...
I'll take the shortcut!
Look out! Watch those people!
Big Sexy comin' through!
Not this time, Dom.
Watch the drag or the line will snap!
Stretch him out! Hold him!
He's gotta have about
2,000 horsepower in that thing.
Try 3,000!
Try five.
Get out of there.
I'm working on it.
Stop working on it and do it.
No, no, no, this my Bentley!
No! No!
Get that case and run.
Move.
They thought this was
gonna be a street fight.
What are you waiting for, Toretto?
No!
Letty, stop!
What are you gonna do?
I don't know why you're doing this,
but I know one thing.
You love me.
And you are not gonna shoot me.
You should've given him the case,
'cause I won't chase you.
Okay.
I will just take it from a dead girl.
You willing to die for it?
Let's go, then.
Jesus, Mum.
You're supposed to avoid the nerves.
Oh, shut up. Don't be such a baby.
Did Toretto hold up his end of the deal?
He gave us this little thing here.
No, no, no. Don't touch.
You can track Cipher with this,
but you can't do this on your own.
There's gotta be two of ya.
Fine. I've got contacts.
No, you're gonna take your brother.
- Oh, dear...
- Yes.
Toretto knows where he is.
He's got this thing. It can see everything.
It's like... It's called
the Devil's Bum Hole or something.
It's called the God's Eye.
Yeah, well, whatever.
There's no way I'm using Owen, all right?
He's a lost cause.
He's your brother, Decks. He's my son.
He's our family.
And our family don't die in bloody cages.
How can you talk like that about Owen?
I can't believe you.
You've gone and upset me.
You've really upset your mother.
Call yourself a brother? You're...
Look, come here... Mum. Okay, okay.
Every time.
Anything?
They're gone.
And DOD confirmed it was a nuclear football.
He's got an EMP and nuclear launch codes.
I don't know what it is,
but they're building towards something.
Deckard?
He didn't make it.
I'm disappointed in you, Dom.
When push came to shove, you were gonna
let Letty just walk away with the codes.
You got the codes!
Rhodes got the codes.
You made the choice to let her go.
And now I have to make one of my own.
They are adorable little things, aren't they?
God, I hope I don't hurt him.
Look, psychotic, I did exactly
what you asked me to do.
Don't do this.
This is your doing.
My doing?
Da-dada.
Dada.
Da-da.
Please don't hurt him, I'm begging you.
I don't want you to beg.
I want you to learn.
Learn what?
I understand why you did
what you did. I really do.
Da-da.
But it was the wrong choice.
This is the consequence of that.
No!
No! No!
Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
Save your son!
No!
Can you pull up the footage
from the guy in the alley?
Traffic cams.
I got you.
I knew it.
I recognize that guy.
That's Connor Rhodes.
I met him when I was working
with Shaw's brother.
He wanted us to get
the Nightshade device for him.
Connor Rhodes.
He's also linked to somebody
I'd quite like to forget.
It's Mose Jakande.
Warlord who tried to get God's Eye.
Which means that's twice that Dom
has messed up Cipher's business.
Everything you're feeling right now,
this rage, a sense of loss, it's not real.
It's a survival instinct
wired deep into our brains
to ensure continuation of the species.
When early man would visit a watering hole,
if they didn't watch their child,
and it got snatched by a crocodile,
our brains would create
a painful but instructional memory,
so it would never happen again.
This idea of "family"
that is so core with you,
that rules your world,
it's a biological lie.
You don't have to accept it.
I don't.
Did you really think you
could destroy two of my teams
without any repercussions?
I wouldn't have even looked
your way if you hadn't done that.
You didn't even know you had a kid.
You can thank me for that and start
doing the job I'm asking you to do.
Help you start a war.
Is that what you think I want?
That's so limited.
I didn't take that football to start a war
any more than I took
your son to start a family.
Taking your son got me the codes.
The codes will get me the nukes
and the nukes will get me what I want
today, tomorrow, and every day after that.
And what's that?
Accountability.
The second I fire off one of those nukes,
I put the superpowers
of this world on notice that,
when they cross the line,
I'm gonna be there to hold them responsible.
Because the truth is, Dom,
to the world out there,
I am the crocodile at the watering hole.
We've got one last job to do.
Cipher.
If I were you, I'd kiss my son.
Because whether
you value it or not, all of this,
your plane, your security, and you,
are still on this earth because of him.
The problem we've had with tracking
Cipher is there's nothing to trace.
But now, we have Rhodes' information.
And we're getting snapshots of his data
before it's scrubbed off the net.
That looks like somebody's bank account,
so why don't we just go ahead...
It's a longitude.
Given the fact that Dom
hit a Russian motorcade,
it's safe to say it's Russia.
Go ahead and bring up the map.
Good. Let's start here
and run the possibilities.
Yalta, Poltava...
It's like they just threw letters together.
Kronyurt.
It's "Vladovin."
- What are you doing here?
- What?
Told you I was gonna check in on you from
time to time to see how you were doin'.
By the way, not so hot.
But there's nothing in Vladovin.
It's just ice.
That's funny.
Could've sworn there was
a secret Russian naval base
where they retrofitted Cold War submarines.
Well, technically, it's not Russian anymore.
The base was taken over
by a terror group of military
separatists about a month ago,
and the Russians haven't taken it back yet,
so there is a little window
of opportunity here.
Russian submarines. Nuclear football.
It sounds like everything we do,
our legs gonna be blown off.
It sounds like you still
number 11 on the list.
It sounds like you've changed
since your little punk-ass
facial hairs done came in.
Guys, guys.
Hey, we gotta call this in.
All the way up the chain.
That's good thinking, champ,
except unfortunately,
the Russian Minister of Defense
got himself involved in a little
incident on US territory,
and the two governments aren't talking
to each other for a while.
By the time they do, it'll be too late.
So, any other suggestions?
Yeah. I got one.
How about we just stop them ourselves?
You're talking about a Russian military base.
Separatist.
Whatever. It's suicide.
It's stopping World War III.
What's it gonna be, rook?
You gonna close your eyes on this one, too?
Pray that the apocalypse doesn't come
knocking on your mama's front door?
Or, are you gonna saddle up, be a man,
and save the entire goddamn world?
You know, I think I figured it out.
What's that?
- Rule number three.
- Which is?
There are no rules.
What'd I tell you, Luke?
I knew he'd get it in three.
Aerial transport leaves in an hour.
Take whatever vehicle you want.
All bets are off.
- All bets are off?
- Bets are off?
Do svidaniya!
Letty, I don't like telling you this one bit.
But the game's changed.
Before, we were just trying to catch Dom,
but now, after all this,
I want you to know, if I have to,
I'm gonna put him down.
Then you might have to take us both down.
I'm freezing, man.
This ain't for me.
I come from a different
kind of lifestyle, brah.
Ladies know me.
They know where I'm at with it.
I tried to take a piss,
I didn't even recognize myself.
Man, that's entirely too much information.
I'm just sayin'.
Well, one thing's for sure.
Dom's gotta be either working
with them or making a trade,
because no one would be this insane
to hit this place without a damn army.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Speak of the devil.
All right, Dom, you're one step
closer to that family reunion.
400 meters to base.
Prep the EMP. Let's take these defenses down.
We have a possible threat approaching.
Raise the barricade.
We've lost power, defensive positions now.
Gates are open. Let's get this party started.
- EMP is recharging.
- How long?
Sixty seconds.
All right, Dom, you have
one pulse left in that EMP.
That sub is heavily insulated.
You're gonna need to be right
underneath it for this thing to work.
Come on.
Yes!
Two birds with one stone.
We've got control of the sub.
Dom, we are good.
Head over to the rendezvous.
Okay, Matty, let's take this baby for a spin.
Damn!
I think Cipher just rebooted that
sub to slave its command system.
What the hell is he talking about?
In layman's terms,
she just carjacked a submarine.
We can't let it get away.
There's the control room.
If you can get me into that wheelhouse,
I can tap the network
and counter-hack Cipher.
Keep it from lowering into the water.
No, what we need to do is get me on that sub.
I find the weapons room
and I can pull the launch chip
before she can fire any of those nukes.
That is too crazy.
What you're saying is too dangerous.
We'll do both.
Knock, knock.
Five vehicles just breached the base.
They just don't give up, do they?
All right, let's haul ass, team.
Double time, double time!
Letty, let's roll!
Go! Go, go, go!
Change of plans, Dom.
I'm sending you new coordinates.
Head there immediately.
I'm done. I want my son.
I'll tell you when you're done.
Your team is in play.
Now, meet Rhodes and follow my instruction.
I've got you covered! Go!
Move, move! Get outta here! Go, go, go!
Okay. How do you like this?
- Remote link has been severed.
- I'll take care of this.
Hi, Ramsey.
She's regained control.
Damn it. She's good.
They're entering the weapons room.
Oh, that's cute.
Pull! Pull!
Roman, Roman! We gotta find the chip, go!
Oh, she's slick.
Gonna have to do better than that, though.
Okay, now you're starting to piss me off.
Ramsey, how much time we talkin' here?
You're smart, but not smart enough.
She's locked me out.
Tej, I can't stop her.
You're gonna have to pull that chip.
I can't! This thing's gone into attack mode!
The door's not gonna open
until you pull the chip!
Tej, we got no idea
what the hell we're looking for.
I got it!
What in the hell are you guys doin'?
It wasn't me. It wasn't me, okay?
It'll be labeled "Guidance Go."
- Guidance Go, Guidance Go...
- Okay, I got somethin'.
- What?
- It says...
Do you understand that?
Wow. Nasty.
Quite a show.
We're arming the nuke.
(POWERING UP)
Nuke's going hot!
She's tryin' to fire this thing!
Roger that. We're moving out.
(OVER RADIO) Disable the nukes!
Roman, what are you seeing?
Come on, talk to me.
I don't see shit. I'm holding on!
And we have a countdown.
What the hell is goin' on, man?
We're about to launch a nuclear missile,
is what the hell is goin' on!
Pull the damn chip!
Countdown, countdown! Look for a countdown!
What countdown?
The missiles need to activate to launch.
The countdown timer won't be in Russian.
The countdown...
Let's show the world what we've got.
No, no, no! Don't press that!
I got it.
Something's wrong. It won't launch.
Get that sub outta there. Now!
Move your ass, Roman!
You all right?
There's nothing all right about any of this!
- Let's go!
- What about the missiles?
We got the chip. No nukes for her.
Hell, yeah. Let's roll.
Guys, we got company. A lot of company!
All right, team, here's the plan.
There's a sea lock at the opening of the bay.
We get there first and close it,
we can stop the submarine
from escaping into open water
and disappearing forever.
I've got the location.
It's 10 miles southwest.
Ten miles?
We're not gonna make it ten seconds!
No, no, no! This is not good!
What's the matter, Roman?
Forgot your snow tires?
Whoa!
You lovin' that Lambo now?
Whoa! Ah!
All right, everyone.
We'll deal with that launch chip later.
Right now, I want that sub
in deep water where no one can find it.
Find me the fastest route out of that bay.
Copy that.
Why are they shootin' at me?
Maybe 'cause you're in an orange
Lamborghini, I don't know.
Shut up, Tej!
Dom...
Do you really wanna put that car in gear?
Do it.
Huh?
I didn't think so.
They're heading for the sea lock.
They're trying to trap the sub in the bay.
I should have taken care
of this a long time ago.
Rhodes, take his team out.
I'm on it.
Roman, get in front of me!
Okay, y'all wanna play rough?
Now it's my turn.
Yeah, baby!
Guys, we got snowmobiles on the right.
They're gonna flank us!
No, they ain't!
Oh, shit!
Tej!
Roman, hold tight, I'm on the way!
I don't wanna go swimmin'! No!
Really, Tej?
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, shit!
Roman, grab your door!
Tej!
Grab the door, Roman!
- It's so cold!
- Shit!
Oh, shit!
Whoa!
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
What is going on?
Roman, hang on!
Tej!
Get me off of this thing!
Come on!
Argh!
All right. I've had enough of this shit!
Number 11, my ass!
Yo, shrinkage! We got a sub to catch. Get in!
What?
Depressurization alert in the cargo hold.
Drop it to 10,000 feet.
I know how much these people mean to you.
So I will let you pick the first target.
I don't pick a target from a mile away.
I stand face to face
and look 'em dead in the eye.
Okay.
The wife it is.
Nice plane. I'm gonna enjoy having this.
Hey, don't go gettin' any ideas.
You and planes don't have a good history.
No shit.
Okay, let's go, Scarface.
These assholes ain't gonna kill themselves.
Pull up surveillance right now.
Surprise.
You're supposed to be dead.
We have a security breach in
the cargo hold. Take care of it now.
Get to the pilot.
He's got the second key. Wait for my signal.
Give Cipher my regards.
Owen.
In position.
Go.
I'm in.
I've got the package, Toretto.
All 12 pounds of him.
Ah.
Dada. Dada.
You made me miss my shot.
What you think you're doing?
Looking at you dead in the eye.
That was for Elena.
Rhodes.
He's no longer with us.
Rhodes picked the wrong target.
Congratulations, Dom.
You just killed your son.
You're wrong. I just saved him.
And you just took your foot
off the tiger's neck.
All right, governor, it's gonna get noisy.
This is for your ears.
Good?
Let's go.
No! Stop him!
Do not let him get off this plane!
We got another problem.
That truck's got
enough missiles to take us all out.
Then don't give 'em a target.
Everybody, get in front of us,
line up, and we'll take the hit.
What? I need to switch cars right now!
- Roman, here comes the bad part.
- What?
Hang in there, guys.
We're almost to the lock.
It's easy for you to say
when your ass ain't on fire.
All right, little man,
this might be a little scary,
but it's gonna be a lot of fun.
How's the music, good?
Ah.
They're locking on.
Sorry, guys, I got no tricks left.
What do we do now?
We start prayin'!
Hell, yeah!
There's Dom!
What, is this guy on our side now?
Who the hell cares? He just saved our ass!
Good to be riding with you again, man.
Toretto just cleared the way for them.
Someone, give me something!
Torpedoes are ready.
Then launch them!
Shit.
- Take the wheel!
- I ain't takin' shit!
Take the wheel!
Where you goin'?
This is crazy!
Speed up!
- Left and back!
- What?
Turn the goddamn wheel
to the left really quickly!
Boom, baby!
Goin' for a ride.
Back in a sec.
- Where's that smile?
- Ah.
There it is.
You were gonna shoot a baby?
You sick bastard.
You're not gonna wanna see this.
Is that you or him?
Him. Good.
The torpedoes missed.
They're gonna reach the lock
before the sub does.
The hell they are.
Get ready for this.
Oh, shit!
We're gonna need a bigger truck.
It's right under us! Get out the way!
Get us out of here!
Why are you always yelling?
This bitch is crazy!
Look out!
That's not good.
Please tell me there's nothing
to worry about!
We got this.
That's my girl.
The sub's too close.
We ain't making it to the gate in time.
We're just going to let it get away?
Not if I know Dom.
You lose, Dom.
I destroyed two of your teams.
I killed your red-headed boyfriend.
And I put two killers
on your untraceable plane.
You lost the minute
you interrupted my honeymoon.
Now guess who I'm coming for.
Put a heat-seeker on him now.
Now!
Fire!
That's a goddamn heat-seeker coming at us!
Peel off! Head to the shore!
All right. Come and get it.
No, no, no.
Dive! Dive!
This...
This is for my son.
Dom!
You're out of bullets, Deckard.
Not like I'm gonna need a gun
to take care of you.
How did you find me?
Resourceful.
You have a lot to answer for, Cipher.
What you've put my family through.
My mother.
I'm gonna make sure that never happens again.
To anyone.
There is only one flaw in your plan.
What's that?
Only one of us has a parachute.
Told you this would be fun.
Time to land, boys.
You know I never left you, Letty.
I know.
And you know I never will.
I have so much to tell you.
Yeah, you do.
And you can start with that bitch.
Now, that's Dominic Toretto.
Hey, Dom!
I'm just throwin' it out there,
we need to get up outta here
'cause there's all kinda nuclearism
happening under this ice.
Relax. Without the trigger chips,
those nukes are harmless.
Okay. So we good, then.
Let me go on and get
my young selfie levels up.
You realize this is classified, right?
Not today.
Unbelievable.
All right, can we get up
outta here, now? I'm freezin'!
It's okay.
Don't worry. He's gonna be here soon.
I get it. Y'all got a lot in common.
Computer hacks, God's Eye,
geeks, nerd... You know.
But we got a lot in common, too, right?
Like what?
We walk in the room
and we're oozin' sex appeal.
Me and you, hip to hip, is a problem.
I'm askin' a real question right now.
Is it gonna be Revenge of the Nerds
or The Dark Knight? Huh?
To be honest, I like both of you.
But just before we get into all of that,
let me ask you one question.
You can ask me anything.
Anything.
What's my last name?
When you guys figure it out,
then, I guess you can let me know.
It's gonna be Parker.
That's all that really matters.
- Jones.
- Mrs. Parker.
- Right?
- Hey, Mrs. Parker...
Hey.
Letty.
I wanted to thank you.
No need.
Well...
Cipher's still on the loose.
There's been some reports she's in Athens,
but she won't be nuking
any cities anytime soon.
Thanks to you guys.
So, I got you a party favor.
This can't be good.
Your record's been cleared.
Full reinstatement.
You've got your job back.
That is, if you want it.
If I want?
Mmm-hmm.
You know, after 16 years,
I figure it's time for a little break.
Wow.
Daddy's stayin' home.
Nobody.
Keep in touch.
Ah. Hang on a second.
This could be interesting.
What made you think I'd do it?
Brotherhood.
I saw that look you gave Cipher,
knew you wanted revenge.
Glad I did it.
I can't believe you went to see my mother.
All this fuss over you.
Yes.
Elena, I promised to keep our son safe.
And now, he always will be.
I wanna introduce you to the most
important person in my universe.
One who never gave up on me.
He's beautiful.
You've heard me say that you
never turn your back on family,
and I wanna thank you all
for never turning your back on me.
You wanna meet them?
All right.
Everyone,
meet Brian.
To Brian!
Welcome to the family, Brian.
Okay, I guess it's my turn to say grace.
We thank you for giving us family.
We sit here in praise.
Thank you for giving us the strength...
All right, touchdown in two.
Rules of engagement.
Electric rounds only.
MI6 wants them alive for questioning.
The target's in a metal coffer.
Every agency and terror cell
is looking for it.
Freeze! Down on the ground!
-Drop it! Drop your weapon!
Don't move! All of you, get down!
Asset secured.
Ml6.
Freeze!
Whoa, whoa. I'm a fan.
Fantastic job, and I think you look
amazing in your matching outfits.
Who the hell are you?
Bad guy.
Get on the ground now!
Nah.
Bulldog Two.
The team is down.
We've been betrayed.
She took the virus.
One of the soldiers
got away with the virus.
I want her on the run
with no place to turn.
She is a wily one.
Monitor all channels
and make sure she takes the fall for it.
-Understand?
-Yes, sir.
What you want us to do
with these assholes?
Clean it up. I don't care. No witnesses.
I'm gonna get it back.
Who's gonna stop me?
-Where?
Who the hell are you?
Ooh. I'm what you call
"an ice-cold can of whup-ass."
Who the hell are you?
I'm what you might call
"a champagne problem."
What you got, big man?
Really thought that would have broke.
Uh-uh.
I'm gonna kill you!
You gonna die!
Ooh.
All right, all right. No, no.
That's my favorite jacket. Don't do that.
Hi, sweetheart.
Could you pass me that gun, please?
Thank you very much. Nice tats.
All right, ass-clown. We're gonna play
a little game. It's called hangman.
I'm gonna ask you some questions.
When you give me an answer I don't like...
Okay, you get the idea.
I've been tracking some
dark web chatter about a super virus
that's coming up on the auction block.
Why don't you tell me about it?
I swear, I don't know.
I don't like that answer.
A little bird told me
about a shadow outfit.
Black tech. Blood ops.
Real assholes. Like you.
They're called Eteon.
And you're gonna tell me
where to find them.
You're not gonna tell me
because I'm hanging you out of a window.
You're gonna tell me because
I'm the guy willing to drop you.
All right, bonus round.
Where's the virus?
No! No, wait!
Don't leave me out here! Please!
Don't leave me! Don't leave me!
What did he write?
"A, A, A." Excellent.
Oh, by the way, your Old Man and the Sea
report from last week?
You did so good, it was awesome.
-Thanks, Daddy.
-Give me some. Yes. Yeah. What's that?
Um... It's a social studies assignment.
It's a family tree.
It's just a sketch.
Oh, yeah.
That's our family tree right there.
It's super easy to read and very clear.
Yeah.
But I was going to use this.
I found it in a garage drawer.
That's you, isn't it?
Who's Jonah?
Is that your brother?
Yup. That's my brother.
Why don't you ever talk about Samoa?
Did something happen?
In life, things happen.
You may not want them to, but they do.
You just gotta do your best...
and move on.
And the fact of the matter is
I'm your family.
I'm your people. Me.
-And you're a whole lot.
-Oh, I am a whole lot.
Look at this. Perfect timing.
Oh, no, this is the mini.
-Yup.
-Thank you so much.
-Cheat day?
-Cheat day. Yeah.
Thank you so much.
Is that really necessary?
Come on! She's 71 years old.
What's the matter with you lot?
Sir, the prisoner will
only be allowed more leniency
when she proves
to be less of a security risk.
If someone leaves a back door open,
it's a bit daft not to try and use it.
What's daft is paying
one of the screws to leave it open
but not paying them enough
to keep their mouth shut.
Yeah, well, my point still stands.
If you can't break out
of a shitty prison like this,
then you're seriously slipping, Mum.
You cheeky bugger.
Speaking of breaking out,
where's my birthday cake?
The one with the ﬁle in it?
They're baking it.
Who wants a bloody ﬁle?
What I want is a nice little bit of C-4.
Listen, if you want out of here,
just say the word. I'll handle it.
Oh, Decks,
I'm just having a bit of fun really.
Being banged up doesn't bother me.
I quite enjoy the peace and quiet.
You know, nice walk,
bit of reading, loads of sudoku.
It's like being retired. Love it.
Now listen,
have you spoken with your sister?
You know I haven't, Mum.
-Give me your hand.
-There she goes.
I mean, you and your sister,
you used to be inseparable.
What happened, Decks?
What happened between you?
I remember you, Owen, and Hattie
playing out in the backyard.
Your little games, your little grifts.
Robbing banks.
You used to give
your little scams code names.
Do you remember?
-Oh, what was that one?
-The "Keith Moon."
Yeah, that’s right. It was
called the "Keith Moon" because it--
It involved lots of explosive percussion
and permanent ear damage.
That's my boy.
No wonder we left the family business.
She loves you, you know?
All you gotta do
is pick up the phone, Decks.
Look at me. You're her big brother.
She looks up to you.
Used to.
Well, one day, I just hope
that I walk through that door
and | see the two of you sitting there.
How many years you got left?
Two, with good behavior.
-So how many, really?
-Four.
Well, you know what they say.
"Never say 'never.'"
Time's up.
You behave yourself.
Will do. Love you, darling.
Love you too.
-All right.
-Lucas Rebecca Hobbs.
I haven't seen you in forever.
-"Rebecca?"
-Do you even age? How long's it been?
-Six months.
-Time ﬂies.
-When we're apart.
-What is your skin care regimen?
Because you look
like a young Shirley Temple.
-Go, go, go, go, go.
-Daddy, who is this guy?
Well, this guy is Locke.
And he works for the CIA.
-Your dad and I are old friends.
-We're not old friends.
Actually, we're...
We're best friends. Here's the half heart.
I don't know what that is.
-We got some ink together as well.
-We did not get ink together.
-Oh, we didn't?
-No, we did not.
-Interesting. I seem to remember...
-We never got ink together.
...getting a little something like this
at one point on my body.
-Jesus.
-Christ, I miss our playful banter.
You have one minute
to tell me what you want
before I knock one of your lungs loose.
You and I are after the same thing.
Say hello to the CT-17 virus.
It's a programmable bioweapon
of biblical proportions.
Affectionately code-named "the Snowflake."
What does the Snowflake do?
Oh, nothing much.
Just liquefies your internal organs.
Basically turns your body
into a giant bag of hot soup.
She is nine!
-Seen worse.
-Where?
Game of Thrones. Janet's house.
-I've never heard of it.
-A Lannister always pays his debts.
You're never going over there again.
But there's a new
wrinkle in the case, Rebecca.
The specifics... are all in the brief.
There you go.
-She's ready, Becca.
-She's nine.
This is the only unit of CT-17
in existence,
and this Snowﬂake is now in the hands
of a rogue MI6 operative in London.
Dad, are all spies that pretty?
No. She is unusually attractive.
And deadly.
Last night she was part of an MI6 team
tasked with securing the virus.
She then proceeded to kill
her entire black ops squad.
She stabbed one guy in the chest
using a brick.
Do you know how hard that is?
To stab someone using a brick?
-Get to the point.
-The point is there's no sharp edge.
How did she get an entire brick
into another person's chest?
She either had to be really strong
or the other person had to have been,
like, born without, like, bones.
-Get to the larger point.
-She stole the Snowflake.
-She went totally off-grid.
-Who's this?
That's the scientist
we believe created the virus.
Great. Where do I find him?
He's off-grid too.
Impossible to ﬁnd. Maybe dead.
-You're very helpful, Locke.
-And you're the world's best tracker.
I'm sure you'll figure something out.
Oh, no, no, no. I'm DSS, you're CIA.
I don't work for you.
Your boss loaned you out.
You do now, dickface.
-What'd you just call me?
-Hey, hey, hey!
Let's just settle down. All right?
We've already got
a black site running in London.
There's an operative there.
Top of his game. He'll be your contact.
I don't need anybody else. I work alone.
We got bigger problems
than your fragile ego,
or the fact that a moment ago
I most deﬁnitely shit my pants.
The entire world
is at stake here, all right?
This thing gets out, we're looking at
a lot of liqueﬁed organs,
and I mean, like, everywhere.
And not just yours and mine.
Uh... He knows I can see him, right?
He knows nothing, Jon Snow.
So what's it gonna be, Becky?
You gonna partner up?
-I'm in.
-Of course you are.
Do you remember what I told you in Rwanda?
-"Stop watching me sleep."
-I said:
-"We are not friends at all."
-We're best friends.
-And to watch your back.
-Wash your back, yeah.
-Oh, I remember.
-Watch your back.
Lot of back. I got you.
Hey. Same old Hobbs, huh?
Same old Locke.
All right. Who's on the case?
-Mr. Shaw.
-Whatever it is, I ain't buying it.
You don't know what I'm selling,
or who I am.
CIA.
-How could you--
-Sunglasses, cloudy day, sensible shoes.
I have fallen arches, and I don't have
a lot of choice in what I--
Anyway, I'm Agent Loeb, and I need
to talk to you about our shared interest.
How'd you find me?
I got a tip from an acquaintance of yours:
Mr. Nobody.
Little joke for you, Loeb.
What do CIA operatives
and baseballs have in common?
People cheer when you hit them with a bat.
No.
They are two things
I don't give a toss about.
That works too.
The weapon she's stolen
is not like anything we've ever seen.
It's a programmable disease
that can target any DNA sequence
with a 100% mortality rate
inside 72 hours.
If MI6 ﬁnds her,
they’re gonna treat her like a traitor.
We need you to surrender the virus.
What is your location?
What, you think I killed them?
But if you help us ﬁnd her,
if you bring us the virus,
we'll grant her immunity.
We've set up a black site here in London.
You've got everything you could need
at your disposal,
and we're bringing in an asset
from the States to assist you.
I don't need anybody.
Maybe not, Mr. Shaw.
But she does.
-My guy's in.
-My guy's in too.
Is your guy gonna freak out
when he ﬁnds out who my guy is?
Didn't they just do a job
together in New York?
Didn't they just destroy
the DSS field office in LA
by throwing each other through it?
I don't know. Look,
I don't know about your guy, but my guy?
He's gonna get this.
He's gonna pull this off. You know why?
We've been best friends
our whole goddamn lives.
Well, my guy beat the shit out of me
at a bar in Krakow 17 years ago,
and he doesn't even remember me.
So we all have our histories.
Anyway, it's the fate of the world here.
It's the fate of the world.
The planet's population is in their hands.
Serious stuff.
You'd think they'd be able to put aside
any petty rivalries to save the world.
Mm. Mm.
-No fucking way.
I'm not working with this guy.
I've been there, done that.
The minute he gets involved,
you can kiss goodbye to any ﬁnesse,
because She-Hulk here
only knows how to smash.
And Mr. Arson here
only knows how to blow shit up.
-The fact is...
-And the fact is...
-no offense...
-oh, no offense...
-this guy's a real asshole.
That's "sumbitch" in your native tongue.
That'd be "wanker" in your native tongue.
Are you ﬁnished blubbering?
You sound like a giant tattooed baby.
I'm not listening to this horseshit.
I got a job to do.
Tell your mom I said hi.
Actually, I'll tell her myself.
Don't you ever talk about my mother.
I'll put your head through that wall.
Secondly, I'll have this job done while
you're still putting on your baby oil.
Good luck, slick.
That's it. You just reminded me.
That's exactly why
I hate working with you.
It's your voice.
It's your nasally, prepubescent,
Harry Potter voice.
Every time you speak,
just imagine this for a second,
it's like dragging my balls
across shattered glass.
-And it hurts.
-Well, for me,
it's not your voice.
It's your face.
Your big, stupid face.
Looking at it makes me feel
like God is projectile vomiting
right in my eyes.
And it burns.
It really burns.
What you gonna do now?
Throw a bit of furniture?
For your information, I was gonna
take this chair and turn it sideways
and shove it right down your throat.
Of course you are,
'cause that's your answer to everything.
Smash a hole through every problem
in a massive truck.
-That's not gonna work here.
-I think it'll work fine.
Guys, why don't you two take a seat
and we'll talk through this?
Me and you? Us? I've been down this road.
It's a total waste of time.
For once, I couldn't agree with you more.
Yeah? Well, I'm doing this my way.
If anyone's got a problem with that,
I suggest you come out here and stop me.
I'm not going in there.
Well, I'm not going in there.
Smart lads.
All right, now that we got rid of
that fun sponge, we can get to work.
I want you to pull up every CCTV camera
around central London.
We already have two dozen agents
scouring footage.
Don't you talk back to me, Opie. Uh-uh.
I just care about the coverage.
I ain't gonna ask you again. Pull it up.
Now zoom in on the area of the heist.
Now invert it. Highlight the areas
that the cameras don't cover.
She's smart.
She just killed her entire team
and stole a deadly virus.
She ain't waiting around for no picture.
Got a lot of nasty people looking for you.
Are you nasty?
Well, it all depends on what happens
in the next 30 seconds.
Promises, promises.
So here's how it's gonna go down.
We do this the hard way or the easy way.
-Are you serious?
-I am.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Hmm. Well, it's a tough decision.
-No, it's really not.
You want me to freeze?
Let me see your hands.
Fine.
But you're not gonna like what's in 'em.
-Think I made up my mind.
-You seem like a smart woman.
I am.
The hard way.
Look-- Hold on!
Stop!
Jeez.
Hey! No.
Oh!
-Are you taking it easy on me?
-For the moment.
Bet you wish
you didn't take it easy on me now.
I wish a lot of things right now.
You're going to go to sleep now.
It's all gonna seem like a bad dream.
It's more like a nightmare.
This whole thing is a nightmare.
All right,
let's me and you have a little chat.
The director called.
He ordered a new baseline for you.
He has everything ready for you
in medical.
Perfection is a painful process, Brixton,
in ourselves
and in the pursuit of a perfect world.
Humanity must evolve
before it destroys itself.
Eteon will carve out all human weakness
and replace it with mechanical perfection.
And you will lead the way.
I'm gonna ask you a question.
It's not what you think it is.
Do you like to dance?
What, the Electric Slide?
The Macarena? No, I don't.
No, no, no,
I was thinking about... the tango.
-Where it takes two.
-Yeah, don't know that one.
Must be different generations.
Yeah, well, either way, the music started,
so let's see what kind of rhythm you have.
-Where's the virus?
-Look, I told you,
-I've no idea what you're talking about.
-Okay, that hurt.
You just stepped on my toes,
that didn't feel good.
Let's try it again.
I think you're better than that.
-Where's the virus?
-I didn't ask to dance.
And why should I talk to you?
You're not CIA.
No? How do you know that?
Where shall I start?
There's two types of CIA agents.
Intelligence and espionage.
Those guys over there
can barely lift a pencil.
That's what intelligence agents look like.
You look like you could
pick up a building.
But espionage is about blending in
and about being subtle,
and there is nothing subtle about you.
Yeah.
That's good.
-I'm impressed.
-I didn't kill anybody.
I know you didn't.
How do you know that, then?
Because you can learn a lot about somebody
when you fight them.
And when we fought,
you weren't fighting to kill me.
You were fighting to run away.
But either way, the world thinks that
you're a murderer and a thief,
so you're not going anywhere
or getting any goddamn phone call
until you give me some real answers.
You have no idea what is happening here.
-Then tell me. Help me understand.
-I can't.
-You're wasting my time.
-I can't either-- You're wasting time!
Virus gets in the wrong hands, that's it.
It's game over.
Does that mean it's time for curls?
Just like the CIA,
always flexing the wrong muscle.
You know, the mind
is the strongest muscle in the body.
Maybe you should try
exercising that a little bit more.
"There's more wisdom in your body
than in your deepest philosophies."
Let me guess. That Bruce Lee?
No, Nietzsche.
'Cause I'm flexing this.
And all of that.
Come here.
If she moves, I want you to shoot her.
Yeah, he can't shoot me.
-Yeah, not allowed.
-In the face.
You can't. You'd go to prison.
-You can shoot her right in the face.
-No, you can't. You'd go to prison. Sorry.
I want you to shoot her
two times right in that face.
-Okay?
-Yeah.
Hi, Dad.
Did you catch the hot spy lady?
Come on. It's me.
I catch everybody I hunt.
How long have you been doing this?
'Cause you seem... new.
She's actually quite annoying.
You know, Dad,
sometimes people annoy each other
when they're actually, like, ﬂirting.
Where'd you hear that from?
Okay, look, me and the spy lady,
we're not flirting, all right?
Zero chemistry.
I don't know.
When you saw her photo,
you definitely gave the eyebrow.
What eyebrow?
-You know, Dad, that thing that you do.
-What thing?
-I don't do that.
-Yes, you do.
No, I definitely don't do that.
I don't even know what you're doing.
That’s the silliest thing I've ever seen.
Let me get going,
I got business to take care of.
I'll see you when I get home, okay?
I love you.
Love you.
Hey, one more thing.
Goddamn it.
This is not the dance
you wanna do with me, woman.
-Oh, really?
-I eat bullets all day long.
Oh, for breakfast and lunch?
'Cause it's dinnertime.
I'll count down for you. Three...
-Two...
-Hobbs.
-Freeze.
-Put that down.
Get your greasy
sausage fingers off of her.
-What are you doing here?
-Saving you.
I don't need to be saved.
No, no. This is my house and your
goddamn girlfriend ain't going anywhere.
-That's disgusting.
-"Girlfriend?"
That is my sister.
Bullshit. She's too good-looking
to be your sister.
Very funny.
Hat, there are people after you.
Believe me, I know that.
It's gonna stay that way
unless you tell me where that virus is.
Listen to me, pinhead. She's gonna die
if I don't get her out of here right now!
We're all gonna die if
she doesn't tell us where that weapon is.
Actually, everyone's gonna die
'cause I am the virus!
It's embedded in capsules.
I need to find a way to get them out.
Bag the asset.
-Now or never.
-I'm more of a now type of guy.
-On my three.
-Sure.
One, two, three.
No one tells me what to do.
Now I take you to school, son.
Deckard Shaw. It's been a long time.
Good to see you, Brixton.
-I think you're out of bullets there, son.
-Lucky for you, I am.
Yeah.
-Nice suit.
-Bulletproof.
-State of the art.
-Could've done with that
the last time I put a bullet in ya.
No, actually, it was three bullets.
Two to the chest, one to the head.
Just like they taught us. Do you remember?
It's a shame you didn't join Eteon.
You could've had all this, my friend.
-"Friend?"
-Yeah.
-You're not the man I knew.
-No. I am way better.
I'm the future of mankind.
Stop!
Hattie, get in the car.
We're all going.
Not you.
Just the girl.
I said, we're all going.
Disable the car. I need the girl alive.
What the hell did you do, Hattie?
A big brother lecture now, really? Huh?
I injected myself. I didn't have a choice.
He was gonna take it.
Program intercepting vector.
-You might wanna--
-Ah!
Might be time for some curls.
Let go!
Very good.
You wanna tell me just what in the
fresh turkey hell we're dealing with here?
Long story.
He's a ghost. Supposed to be dead.
Eight years ago,
I put a bullet through his brain.
Great, so we're being chased
by the Terminator.
I don't think he's gonna make it.
I don't think he can see
over the steering wheel.
Buckle up, fat boy,
I'm gonna save your life again.
You want a war, then?
Okay.
Okay, ride's over.
We gotta lose this car.
Update.
I've hacked the mainframe
of every news agency and outlet.
How many do we control?
Hundred and seventy-four broadcasts,
2,000 odd.
Double it.
I want 100% control of this story.
-Standard frame job.
-No, standard will not do.
I need something special for these guys.
So listen up. Narrative:
Hobbs, Shaw, big guy, little guy,
have been ID'd.
They've been blamed
for the recent attacks on the CIA.
They shared a prison cell
where they hatched a plan
to start their reign of terror.
Just got real.
-Who the hell are these guys?
-Eteon.
They're a secret tech cult, with
a mercenary army and plenty of dark money.
And delusions of saving the world
by augmenting the human race.
That's it.
Apparently they control the media as well.
Heard rumors about these people.
Everybody thinks they're a myth.
I've seen it firsthand
how real they are.
If you don't fit into their plans,
you've already dug your own grave.
All right, let's get to
the nearest lockdown facility--
Hey, no. You don't get it, do you?
Brixton's a tier-one assassin.
Best I've ever seen. I know him.
He ain't never gonna stop
until he gets that virus.
And besides, that's my sister.
Family business.
Is your name Shaw? No.
Then she's going nowhere with you.
When it comes to the fate of the world,
it becomes my business.
I don't care if she's your sister,
that woman ain't going anywhere--
-Where are you going?
-I'm going away.
I don't have time for your alpha male shit
right now. You're both idiots.
You clearly can't work together
and so you're absolutely useless to me.
So I'm gonna go find the man who can
help me get this thing out of my system.
-See ya.
-You mean this man?
I was tracking him before the attack.
He's hard to find,
but I think I got a hell of a lead.
Russian newspaper.
Not just any old paper.
There 's only one place
in London that sells that.
Call the director.
Well, well, Deckard Shaw.
How complicated for you.
Not really.
He's also working with DSS, Luke Hobbs.
Hobbs. We have a history.
They're formidable.
Small fry.
I'll eliminate the two of them.
Get the asset back ASAP.
You get the girl,
extract the virus
and reprogram it for phase one.
We use that weapon to eliminate the weak
and anyone who would get in our way.
We ’re building
the perfect system, Brixton.
Turn them.
"Turn 'em?"
Sorry, I don't follow.
I want them turned.
I want them working for the cause.
Understood?
They can't be turned.
What makes you so certain?
The last time we asked,
I got shot in the face.
That makes me very certain.
So, I suggest that
we take another approach.
-Which is why--
-I'm not asking, Brixton.
You show them the consequences of refusal.
Or perhaps I'll show them to you.
Is that a threat?
I'd remember who you're reliant on
for your survival.
All for the cause.
Look, honey, I have to talk to you about
something. It's very important right now.
Remember how we spoke about
what would happen if things went sideways?
We called it a "code red."
Well, it's happening.
Is there anything I can do?
You need to stay home.
You're gonna be safe there.
As a matter of fact, we've got the CIA
listening in on this call right now.
Watch this. Hi, Locke.
Everybody's safe, everybody's great.
I'm actually at our old diner here.
It's super weird being here
without you guys.
Think it's closed.
Thank you, brother.
Honey, I've already talked to Aunt Lisa.
She knows exactly what to do.
I’m gonna be home as soon as I can.
-Love you.
-I love you back.
Goodbye.
Luke Hobbs and Deckard Shaw.
While Hobbs is an agent in the American--
Tell us everything you know about this.
My God.
-When were you exposed?
-About 30 hours ago.
Then the capsules containing
the virus are still intact.
So we need to neutralize it.
No, it is not that easy.
It's not programmed to any DNA sequence.
It's fatal to everyone.
In 42 hours, the capsules will dissolve,
and she will be infected.
Then the virus will go airborne.
We are talking global contamination
within a week.
Why in the hell
would you create something like that?
-Because I thought I was one of them.
-Eteon.
They told me they wanted
to save the world through science.
I believed in their cause.
I developed the Snowflake
to be a carrier for vaccines,
a panacea for the whole world.
But they redeveloped it
into a programmable apocalypse.
To attack the weakest of us. Those not
worthy of Eteon's vision of the future.
For a scientist,
you seem incredibly stupid.
Well, I'm a two-times Nobel Prize winner,
but who's counting?
All right, you said the virus is
programmable. So... reprogram it.
I can't reprogram it in a host.
Just tell us how to
get this thing out from me.
Well, there are two options.
And the first is easy.
-Go.
-Finally.
-You kill her.
-Excuse me?
And burn the body, of course.
-Of course.
No, I mean really burn it.
-Really burn it.
-To ash.
-To ash?
-Beyond all recognition.
Let's assume that that's not an option,
shall we, genius?
Yeah, it doesn't work for us.
Option number two.
There is a machine that could
preserve her life and extract the virus.
That should've been option number one.
Because it's impossible to get to.
We'll decide what's impossible.
Where is it?
A secret dark-tech complex
fortiﬁed by an army
in the most godforsaken
part of the planet.
But if you go there,
all three of you will die.
So basically what you're saying is:
she dies no matter what.
Well, who needs a drink?
I know just the place.
Wow, look at all these.
Somebody's overcompensating.
If anything, I'm under-compensating.
And a teeny-tiny one. Just your size.
Used it for a job over in Italy.
Shame we didn't need
a weightlifting bus driver.
Would've given you a call.
Drink?
Yeah, I'll take a little one.
I'll write to someone in Moscow.
An old friend.
Yeah, we have a long history.
She and her crew are paying a visit
to some locals.
Particular Russian criminal element.
-They have things that we're gonna need.
-Considering your history with friends,
how many bullets you put
in this one's head?
They can set us up with gear,
and I don't hear any other ideas.
We know getting out of this country
is gonna be extremely difficult.
We have every major intelligence agency
already hunting us down.
And there's the fact that you disgraced
MI6 when you betrayed your team.
Don't believe everything they tell you.
Smile.
No, regular back channels
aren't gonna work this time.
We're gonna have to
do our best to blend in.
Hide in plain sight.
-That's why we'll be flying commercial.
-Commercial?
We're gonna get spotted too easy at--
Don't worry that pea-sized brain.
I handled it.
Cloned our cell phone signals
around the world.
Should buy us at least 48 hours.
We'll pick up new gear
when we get to Moscow.
Should get us past the wandering eyes
at the airport.
This is probably the only thing
that's gonna fit.
Fit what, a Smurf?
I think that's one of my old ones.
I apologize in advance
if it's a little loose around the balls.
Okay. What do we got, tough guy? Come on.
I've created new identities
and altered your biometric profiles
so the airport scanners don't recognize
your faces or your ﬁngerprints.
You're Sarah Atkins.
You work in insurance.
Hello.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
I'm Franz Gruber.
I'm a freelance architect,
avid mountain climber,
and a part-time ski instructor.
-Thank you.
-And you, you're Michael Oxmaul.
"Mike Oxmaul."
I go by Michael.
-Freeze! Stop, sir! Stop there!
-Stay right where you are!
-Stay there!
-It's Mike. It's Mike Oxmaul.
It's not small. And my name's Michael.
They've stopped him for what, exactly?
Whatever it is, it's gonna involve
rubber gloves and a body cavity search.
Let's go.
Hands on your head, Oxmaul.
Can't believe you did that.
He was gonna slow us down.
We can't pull this off. We both know it.
It's bad enough
I got this thing in my blood
that's gonna kill me and everyone else,
but were you seriously gonna break
this mysterious machine
out of some
high-security death virus complex
and magically get it to work?
-Frankly, that sounds completely--
-You still wear that silly thing?
Didn't know you still had that.
Put the pin back in.
You haven't changed.
Wish I could say the same about you.
Hey, you're gonna be okay.
We're gonna make this work.
It's what we do.
And what if we don't?
-What if the only option is for you to--
-It's not happening.
Hi, I'm here. I'm Michael.
Hi, yeah.
Hello. All right.
Oh, yeah, let's see. Where's my seat?
F-one, F-two...
F you.
Hey.
You are an asshole.
You were quicker than I thought.
Yup. Because I have
a secret weapon.
People actually like me.
You wouldn't understand that
because you don't have any friends.
I love your babushka.
Couldn't have booked an emergency row
for a little bit more legroom?
Not everybody has hobbit legs like you.
Hey, look, in case you didn't realize,
I couldn't give a damn about your comfort.
So why don't you be a good elephant,
suck up another kilo of peanuts,
put your chair back and relax?
Listen, don't ever tell me to relax.
Don't tell me to do anything.
Any time you ever say anything,
it makes me want to take my boot
and shove it so far up your ass,
you're gonna be
spitting out Shoelaces all week.
Hey, you know what the problem is?
I'll tell you the problem. This job.
This job requires stealth.
And you... look at you.
I mean, granted, it's not your fault.
But you're too obvious.
You stick out. Like balls on a bulldog.
Dangling down in all the wrong places.
Seemingly harmless.
And the next thing you know,
they're trying to impregnate your sister.
What?
-Impregnate your sister?
-You heard.
Oh...
Now I get it.
You do? Good. I'm glad. Yeah, I'm glad.
-I'm very glad.
-You actually think that
I'm going through all this effort,
on this mission,
trying to save the world,
by the way, for a fourth time,
because I'm really good at it.
You think I'm going through all of this
just so I can do the horizontal-hula,
sexy, sexy time with your sister?
Not all. Most.
Let me break it down for you, Frodo.
This ain't 1955 anymore, all right?
Despite the fact that that girl sleeping
right there is related to you,
she's still one of the toughest,
baddest, most capable women
I've ever encountered in my entire life.
And if she chooses to look the way
of this big, brown,
well-endowed, tattooed
mountain of a man, then guess what.
I'm gonna let her climb this mountain
over and over and over again.
You stay away from her.
I see what you're doing.
You think I'm stupid?
Of course I think you're stupid.
But you know what? I'll do you a favor.
I'll knock that dumb right out of
your skull. You just say the word, jack.
You know what I wanna do?
I wanna do an Irish jig
on your arse-ugly face at 30,000 feet.
-Oh, 30,000 feet.
-Yeah.
-So you wanna dance right now?
The only thing holding you back
is air and opportunity.
And there goes the air.
-Bring it on, Don Ho.
-"Don Ho?"
That's enough! Hey, cut it out.
Both of y'all, cut it out.
Oh, see? You woke up the air marshal.
You woke the air marshal.
-How'd you know I was the air marshal?
-Unaccompanied.
-Late boarding the plane.
-Aisle seat.
-Golf shirt.
Let's just call that an educated guess.
Air Marshal Dinkley, at your service.
I'm sorry, did you just say "Dinkley?"
What's the problem? Dinkley.
I understand this big fella,
because it's my job to observe.
Thick neck, your head's been on a swivel
since you've been on this damn plane.
Every passenger that's got on here
you been checking out.
You're a lawman.
And you, Mr. Armani pants, you're a spy.
-He's pretty good.
-Not bad.
I get it. We're all big guys.
The three of us. Alphas.
Three apex predators cooped up in the sky.
Tensions get high.
What you throwing up on the bench?
Three, four hundred pounds?
-Little less.
-Yeah, light work.
I'm doing the same thing. Slagging weight.
Clanging and banging.
What you into?
Hot yoga? Pilates?
Probably mess around in the Octagon.
Yeah, you wanna know what I do?
I sit in a can of farts all day long.
That's what I'm dealing with.
It's an occasional terrorist
and a lot of recycled ass.
I would give anything
to be on the front line again
"Again?"
-What?
-I was a compartmented element for JSOC.
You were in Delta?
Sabre Squad Echo, 24/7, baby.
"Echo?" Those guys were the warlocks
because of the magic they could do.
-That's right.
-If that's the case,
then I'ma say "abracadabra," bitches.
You're looking at the magic.
You know what your problem is?
Your balance is off.
You need a third squaddie.
-No, no, we're good.
-No.
I know the game.
You hear me? I know the game.
-What are you doing?
-What do you mean, "What am I doing?"
-Don't talk like that.
-You sound different.
-Do I?
-That's not your voice.
Use your regular voice.
This is my regular voice.
I'm talking like the warlocks talk, baby.
They don't talk like that.
I'm just showing you.
That's all, guys. Look...
all I'm saying is I could complete
this holy trinity that you guys have.
Three would be too much.
Here's my résumé. This is my card.
'Cause if you need stuff, I'm the guy
that you call to get what you need.
You want a Citation X? You want a GV?
You want a Boeing 747?
You want a helicopter?
You want something stealth?
I'm an air marshal. I'm your guy.
Please. Please let me go.
What do you want?
I want our property
out of that girl's blood.
No, the virus is too dangerous. I can't!
Humans must evolve, Professor.
Without Eteon's upgrades,
the human body's
really not worth that much.
Maybe 11 pence worth of magnesium,
couple of pence worth of calcium,
little bit of iron.
Not worth much.
I'd say, all in all,
probably about three pound.
Three pound fifty, max.
The entirety of a man's worth,
small change.
You're gonna reprogram that virus for me.
I won't.
Ah, your friend's a Russian mobster.
This girl steals from Russian mobsters.
Actually, she steals from everyone.
It's kind of her thing.
Deckard Shaw.
Margarita.
Oh, I did not see that coming.
I wish I didn't see that at all.
Me too.
I got your list.
It's long.
I asked for a house on a runway.
Not sure a dozen Russians in duct tape
were on the list.
Well, give me more
than three-hour notice,
and I wouldn't have to
resort to such extremes.
Not sure three hours has anything to do
with your extremes, Margarita.
Qué mierda, Deckard.
Eteon. Could you pick
a harder place to break into?
We need to find the C-17 viral
extraction machine. Could be anywhere.
That facility is
three square miles of research labs.
Yeah. And it's a powder keg
packed with munitions.
We've gotta pull a Mick Jagger.
This sounds like a fun game.
We're not getting you on the inside. No.
When Deck and I were kids,
we'd spend our time coming up with grifts.
A "Mick Jagger" was a job
that required one person to showboat
to draw all the eyes
while the others made the music.
A typical inside job.
Guys, you heard Andreiko.
They have to use the extraction machine.
So they'll take me right to it.
No, I can do it.
We can do it.
So now the only question is
how to ring Eteon's dinner bell.
Oh, I can handle that part.
But ﬁrst, let's get you geared up.
These are your HALO parachutes.
Earbuds for encrypted communication.
Scorpion EVO 3 with optical sights.
Ultra-thin bullet-resisting Kevlar.
Infrared cameras for seeing through walls.
And last but not least,
compact hydrogen detonator.
Put it in the right spot,
it'll blow the place sky-high.
How do I look?
Looks a little tight.
How you holding up?
You know, if things go south in there,
you can't leave me alive.
We're gonna get you out of there.
Let me tell you something else.
"The key to immortality
is first living a life worth remembering."
-Is that more Nietzsche?
-Nah.
That's Bruce Lee.
Come on.
How'd you ﬁnd her?
You've heard about me. I'm good at my job.
Was she alone?
Yeah.
If you're lying to me,
I will cut your heart out.
Do you understand?
I'd be afraid if I had one.
Now that's a ride.
What a ride.
I got shotgun.
-I got shotgun.
-No, no, no. Don't start. I got shotgun.
We're entering the drop zone!
-Are you ready?
-Yeah, I'm ready.
-On my three!
-Okay.
-One!
-Uh-huh.
Ah! You asshole!
Whoo!
Nobody tells me what to do.
So, I'm intrigued,
do you wash the blood off your hands
before you count your money
or is it afterwards?
Dismissed.
You don't get it, do you?
You know, the weak deal with money.
We deal with evolutionary change.
Change that sometimes require
acts of violence.
Like killing innocent people with viruses?
Only the weak ones.
We're dealing with the future of
the planet. Things that money cannot buy.
Oh, like your soul back?
My soul?
Your brother took my soul.
The boys in the lab made me a new one.
Now, that's progress.
Welcome to the extraction room, Miss Shaw.
Get her ready.
It won't be long.
I tell you, we ain't gonna want
to be here when this thing goes off.
Looks like she's 400 yards through there.
Looks like they're holding her
in some sort of medical pod.
Timer's set for 45 minutes.
We get in and get out.
Blow this death factory to pieces.
Remember the hallway.
-No guns.
-Right. Those guys have to be alive.
Because at the end of the hallway,
the retinal scanner needs a match
to open the door.
-Pick a door.
-I'm right there.
Nope, that's my door.
What's the matter with you?
I made a mistake. This is your door.
Oh, no. No backsies. What's the matter?
You got a lot of bad guys
behind that door?
Watch this. You might learn something.
Watch this.
Eh.
Enter corresponding match.
Access denied.
You come and do it!
Access granted.
Doors opening.
Very good. Well done, boys.
I'm impressed that you even got in here.
That-- That's... That's not possible.
-No. What are you doing?
-Having to extract it myself.
Wait!
There he is. Nice and rested?
Get your full eight hours?
I was gonna order some room service.
What do you fancy?
French toast? I'll get the order in.
I just dreamt they killed you
before I woke up.
Pretty disappointed right now.
It's a little elaborate, I must admit.
Old-school interrogation technique
we picked up in black ops.
Shock will kill a man in three.
Do you remember that, Deck?
Yeah, I remember
a lot of things from back then.
I reckon you've only got
four shocks in you, boys.
Yeah? I think we could take ﬁve.
"Five?" Well, all right.
You had to open your big mouth, didn't ya?
I thought it was a cool thing
to say in the moment.
Do you remember
when we were real brothers?
Task Force Black.
Do you remember that, Deck?
Man, we ended up
seeing the worst in people.
Worst in our countries, our leaders,
our enemies, our friends.
You don't know
the meaning of that word anymore.
But don't worry about it, neither does he.
He shoots them right in the head,
but in your case,
I thought it was a hell of a good idea.
Big man, you still talking?
I said I thought it was a hell of a good--
Shit.
You know, it's funny
how humanity's hate for each other
is stronger
than its own self-preservation,
which is why we're here.
Remember eight years ago, Deck,
when Eteon asked us to join their mission?
Oh, you mean their death cult.
-They're lunatics.
-Visionaries.
Visionaries of a future.
A bigger future. A brighter future.
You remember the data they gave us, man.
What with environmental damage,
capitalism, terrorism,
humanity wipes itself out by 2096.
Now, that is scary to me.
But if we fulﬁll Eteon's vision,
-you save their world.
-You don't save the world with genocide.
Genocide, schmenocide.
You know what this virus is?
This virus is a necessary
shock to the system.
Whoo! That's three.
I love this thing.
Told you then, I'm telling you now,
your metrics are off.
One good reason:
You assume the worst in people.
People cannot be trusted to do
the right thing. Look at the two of you.
The fate of the world is in your hands,
and you can't even get along.
But you know all about doing
the right thing, don't you, Shaw?
Little souvenir, huh, bro?
You come to kill me,
I'll do the same every time.
What'd you expect? A shiatsu?
Anyone talking to you?
Your mama.
Yeah!
I get it. You're still mad.
You're upset because,
hey, when you wouldn't turn,
they asked me to come and kill you,
and, of course, I had to
because you knew too much.
But I think about that night a lot.
I think about it.
Because what I realize now
that I did not realize then
is that when you shot me,
you gave me a gift.
Look at me. I'm black Superman.
Bulletproof, new spine,
and the more machine I become,
the more humane I am.
This is what you wanna fight for.
I'm giving you another
chance to join us, Deckard.
And the boss wants big mouth as well.
If not, I kill you both.
Which, honestly, I'd love to do.
You know Eteon.
You know what they're capable of.
They rebuilt me. Dismantled him.
Made it look he killed his own team.
Even your own sister... disowned you.
Just say the word, bro.
Say the word and all of this goes away.
Your sister lives. His daughter lives.
We get you some upgrades,
and we go on to saving the world.
What's it to be?
Join the evolution of man,
or die with the weak?
Just get it done.
I told the boss you wouldn't
change your mind.
See you later.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait!
I think we should join.
Join?
You said some really compelling things.
I mean, that black Superman thing,
that really got me. I love that.
What are you, deaf, stupid, or both?
We ain't joining.
There you go again, you're just thinking
about yourself. You're such a diva.
What about my feelings, for once?
Let me tell you something,
if we were a band, you know who you'd be?
You'd be Mick Jagger.
"Mick Jagger?"
Mick Jagger.
Oi, what's it to be?
In or out?
-We're not gonna join.
But since you're standing there,
here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna rip the arm off this chair.
I'm gonna smash him right in the face.
Stab him right in the neck
for looking that way.
Kill all 13 guys in seven seconds.
And here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna slip out of these chains
and dropkick him,
him and him right in the throat.
No, not him, that's my guy.
You gotta pick another guy.
What do you mean that's your guy?
That's my guy.
No, no. That's face-smash guy.
You gotta find another dropkick guy.
You want a face-smash guy?
I'm gonna find you one.
See that guy over there?
The big one. The big one.
-That's face-smash guy.
-No, he's way too big.
Let 'em go.
All right, boys, stay calm.
We need her alive.
Let them go, or what?
Or you're gonna get a nice new breeze
there at the center of your forehead.
You're not gonna shoot me.
Because you need
an activation chip to fire that gun.
Sorry.
Try this gun!
I'm not small change.
-Let's roll.
-You think?
Dick.
There she is.
-Hattie, where's the machine?
-It's in the second truck.
On it.
Mick Jagger.
Never fails.
We're not out of this yet, Hattie.
Got the machine.
Get a move on!
Train's leaving the station!
That sumbitch really is black Superman.
Engage drones.
We're running out of road.
Hold on!
Route to intercept.
Whoo!
On your left.
Brace yourself.
Hobbs, this ain't gonna make it.
Bringing her to ya.
You thinking what I'm thinking, Shaw?
Let’s trade some paint.
Trade some paint.
Hattie.
-Huh?
-You trust me?
Gonna need a ride.
I know what you're thinking.
Just keep driving. I'll make it.
Take the wheel.
Ah, there he is.
-I got him.
-No, I got him.
I thought you were strong.
I'm sorry, brother.
This thing is really damaged.
Well, there goes option two.
-That only leaves the first one.
-Come on. Stop it, Hat.
I'm tired, Deck. I am done running.
-We still got time.
-"Time?"
Time for what? The machine's destroyed.
-Yeah, well, we'll ﬁx it.
-How?
We need to find a place
to get off the grid.
Where? We're wanted all over the world,
and Brixton won't stop.
We can't risk millions of people.
I told you on the plane,
we should've gone with option one.
-It is done now, Deck.
-It's not done.
-It's done.
-It's not done!
It's not done.
Look at me.
Remember that thing you used to say to me
when we were kids? Huh?
Used to look at me and say,
"Deck, it's never over till it's over."
We used to laugh. Remember that?
No, Deck, it went,
"It's never over till I say it's over."
Yeah, that was it.
So say it now. Say it.
Remember who we are.
We're the Shaw family.
We never, never, never give up.
We've got a day.
More than a day.
We don't even know where we'd go.
I know a place.
Where?
It's the last place on earth
I ever wanna go.
Home.
Abracadabra, bitches.
I told you that I could get you anything.
And listen to me, from Moscow to Samoa,
that is not an easy flight to charter,
but I got it done.
Well, that's why
we're calling you, Dinkley.
We just wanted to say thank you
for getting us that bird to Samoa.
Warriors help out warriors.
So all you need to know
is that you got a third squaddie over here
that is ready to go
whenever you need me to.
-I'm just sitting in my lair.
You in a bathroom?
Potato, potah-to.
Wherever I am is where the magic happens.
We ain't gotta get into specifics.
Just to make sure
you got all the contacts.
You got the cell, you got my e-mail.
-Got 'em all.
-I'ma shoot you
my mom number too.
I'ma make sure you got that,
'cause if you can't get me, she can.
I got a Hotmail address
that’s still active. Hit me on that.
LinkedIn. That's my profile.
-...account thing I've been doing.
-I'm just making sure you got everything--
-We're losing ya.
That was my phone.
I hope this brother of yours
is as good a mechanic as you say he is.
Jonah is the best mechanic I know.
And he's gonna help us.
That is, if he doesn't kill me first.
Yeah, take your time.
It's only my sister's life and
the fate of the world we're waiting on!
Oh, here we go.
Bet you a bullseye 50 quid
he punches him in the face.
Deal.
Jonah.
You know what comes next?
Yup.
See? Not just me.
Your face,
it's all over the bloody news, boy.
You're not welcome here, police.
You got a bloody cheek.
Coming here after 25 years.
Bringing your problems here to this house.
You betrayed our family,
bring shame on our house.
You betrayed your own blood!
Jonah, I hear you.
But we ain't kids anymore.
You better watch how you talk to me.
It's not the size of the dog
in the fight, boy.
It's the size of the fight in the dog.
No, it's always the size of the dog.
Hey! No fighting under this roof, huh?
Is that my Luke? Oka...
My baby's home.
Hey, Mama.
Oka, I miss my baby boy.
But look at you, all skin and bones.
-Come over here and eat.
-No, no, no, Mama.
There's no time.
I'm sorry. I didn't want
to bring trouble here.
You should've stayed away.
What did you bring here?
-I brought the truth here.
-What truth?
The truth is we were set up.
We were framed by people
who created a deadly virus.
-Oh, come on.
-It could go global if it's not stopped.
We could all die. All of us.
Everybody here in this fale,
everybody on the island.
And everybody around the world.
Jonah, I need you
to help ﬁx this machine.
I need you to help my friends,
and I need us
to build defenses around here, now!
You think you can just come back in here
and we're gonna help you
-after everything you did?
-Yes!
-Not gonna happen!
-It's bigger than you and I!
-I don't care!
-It's bigger than you and I! We could die.
Good, because I would rather die
than help you, polo head!
Listen, I know your brother's
hard to be around, believe me.
But I trust him, and he brought us here
because this place has something
that nowhere else on the planet does: you.
You don't know me! I don't know you, okay?
Time for you all to go.
Take your machine with you. Go, now!
-Go!
-Jonah Hobbs!
You have some respect for your use.
If he needs anything,
we gonna give it to him.
The food off our tables,
the clothes off our backs,
even the mana of the islands.
And you boys, all you boys,
you show our guests here fa'aaloalo,
or so help me God,
I'm gonna take this here slipper
and I'm gonna sasa your big, fat heads!
You boys hear me?
I'm sorry to bring this here, Mama.
Luke, this is your home.
We Samoans. We can handle troubles.
You were right.
You don 't turn soldiers like them.
Do what I built you to do.
You're a one-of-a-kind war machine.
Bring us back my virus.
No handcuffs this time.
You can have your revenge.
I will.
We found 'em.
They hopped an unregistered cargo plane.
-To where?
-Samoa.
Gentlemen!
This is where you earn your upgrades.
Bring me back my virus.
Yeah.
It's quite the operation.
Yeah, for a chop shop.
Your dad was a car thief, then?
No. My dad actually stole everything.
Drugs. Guns...
Sounds just like my family.
Mama raised us till we were teenagers,
and my old man
started coming around again.
Taking a real interest in his sons.
The truth is,
he was just looking for a new crew.
And I was the only one
to see through those lies.
So the jobs my dad pulled
me and my brothers into
just got bigger and more dangerous.
Then eventually he knew,
and he was okay with,
getting me and my brothers killed.
So I turned him in.
Or you protected your family.
So after I put him away,
I left Samoa and I never came back.
Well, at least one good thing came out
of me jamming that thing into my hand.
Yeah, what's that?
Got to bring you home, didn't I?
Lucky me.
You went legit.
Yeah, 100% clean now.
Custom shop, international clients.
See those bikes? Going to Tokyo.
And that car? New York.
That one over there's going to London.
Turns out people like our stuff.
I needed to do something
to hold our family together.
After you abandoned us.
Hey, good news. Change of clothes. Hats.
Your mum said you might like to wear this.
Must be your favorite size. Spray on.
Why don't you throw another jacket on?
It's 110 degrees out there.
Hey, look, down to business.
We got any weapons?
Oh, we got weapons.
Mama, where's all our guns?
I get rid of 'em.
Very noble, Mrs. Hobbs.
We're in serious trouble.
That is an understatement.
These guns, they kill all my family.
So we gonna ﬁght.
Gonna fight with this
and we gonna fight with this.
'Cause no take a real man
for pull one trigger.
All right, we're going to war
with the family heirlooms.
Got it. We're gonna need a lot more.
We're never gonna survive their ﬁrepower.
It doesn't take a man to pull a trigger,
but for Eteon,
it does take an activation chip.
You still got that glove?
You're thinking closed-system hack.
It'll level the playing ﬁeld if you can.
Certainly buy us some time.
Shut their guns down.
I'm on it.
You ready?
War is what I do.
Let's go old-school.
Take a look around.
This is where we draw the line.
Who would've thought this is where
we're gonna save the world?
We need to make 'em play by our rules.
Tomorrow morning there I] be a storm
raging on the north cliffs.
We'll build a no-man’s-land there.
And if all else fails,
that'll be our last stand.
How many more of these we gotta do?
Just keep digging, brother.
When we were in Kandahar running raids,
Brixton would always strike
just before dawn.
It's when the enemy's most tired,
still under the cover of night.
When the battle shifts into high gear,
you got the sun at your back.
We let 'em all in.
And we make sure they never leave.
Kill box. I like it.
Not like we got a ton of resources.
But the island will provide, brother.
-Give me the good news, Hat.
-I'm in.
The only thing is, I could only block
the signal repeaters on the satellite
for six minutes.
Six minutes might be all the time we need.
Better than a sharp stick in the eye.
Which is basically
all we've got to fight them with anyway.
Done more with less, haven't we?
Hi.
-Drink?
-Sure. Thank you.
Just taking it all in,
in case it's the last sunset we see.
I shouldn't have believed
that Deckard went dark.
Wasted so much time. I'm...
I've spent my whole life running away.
-Me too.
-Yeah?
Yeah.
I haven't been back here in 25 years.
I mean, my own daughter
doesn't even know her family.
Well... you can change that.
Yeah.
So can you.
I got an idea. Why don't you and I
make a promise right here, right now?
That when we see tomorrow's sunset,
we begin to fix the mistakes we've made.
That's just sealed it
so you can't back out. That's all.
I don't think there's any chance in hell
I would back out.
You wanna seal it again or...
-Deﬁnitely not.
-Okay.
Maybe tomorrow, if I survive.
-Jonah.
-Look, don't rush me.
It's almost dawn. He'll be here soon.
Make it happen now! Now!
Hey, don't rush me.
That's how mistakes are made.
And how long does this process take?
It's 30 minutes and 33 till I go viral.
Deck, I think we need to
seriously consider option one.
Don't strike a match just yet, Hats.
We are seriously gonna miss this window.
-Let's do this. Come on!
-Jonah, now!
Fine, fine, okay. Here goes nothing.
Brace yourself, Hats.
-It ain't gonna be pleasant.
-No, it's gonna be fine.
It's working. It's working.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Hey. They triggered the alarm!
That's him.
-As we planned?
-As we planned.
Usos!
It's time.
Jonah.
Just wanna say that...
if this thing goes sideways and...
and this is it...
I'm sorry.
I may have had my reasons,
but the fact is...
I left you and I left our 'aiga.
I should've come home.
If we make it through this,
you have my word
I'll never let that happen again.
I love you, uso.
I love you too, uso.
Okay, you're mobile.
Do you think I need to be so close
to the front line?
Yeah, we keep you close.
Keep an eye on you
in case we need to make a quick getaway.
Hey, this is what we do, right?
It is what we do.
Deck...
I overheard what Brixton said.
That you stayed away to protect us.
I never should've believed all that stuff,
I know it now.
-I don't know why I did. I'm so sorry.
-Don't be.
Don't be. Hey, look, I've done things,
done things I'm not proud of.
Things I... have to make amends for.
All thanks to what that bastard
put me through.
But right now,
the most important thing to me
is getting my little sister home safely.
Eteon, hold!
-Do it.
-Light 'em up.
What's going on?
How long before the guns get back online?
I've no idea.
Shaw.
Air command.
Bring me the chopper.
Deck!
Do it quick, Hats.
-It's in, it's in, it's in. Is it working?
-Machine's on.
-We're good.
Let's go.
Hobbs!
Go, go!
Let's go fishing, Shaw.
You catch him, I'll gut him.
Hold on!
-Welcome to my island, you--
-Take it up!
You get us close and I'll get her.
I'll keep his nose down. You reel him in.
Take it up! Take it up!
Have a day off.
What are you doing?
We're going for a ride.
Shit.
We're coming, usos!
-Let's go, Jonah.
-Come on, brother.
The axle, the axle!
Timo, you got this!
Ah!
We're gonna need more weight.
Yeah!
Bring it in nice and easy, clean.
Hell yeah, usos!
-It's too much weight!
-All right, drop 'em.
Stay there!
Hit 'em with the moonshine! Now!
Hang me off a cliff, huh? My turn.
Sir, the weapons
-are back online.
-Let's go, let's go!
-Goodbye.
Incoming!
We got a little trouble back here, Shaw.
We'll lose 'em in no-man's-land.
Let's get this up!
All right, now hit that stake.
We're losing the rotor!
Shit.
What the--
I got you, Hobbs.
Hey!
-The rotor!
-Losing power.
Guys!
Hattie! Jump!
Hey, get up. Get up!
Hey! Get up!
You don't die until I tell you to die.
You see the extraction timer?
When it hits zero, empty this clip
into her heart, do you understand?
Hattie!
This doesn't end your way, boys.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
The numbers don't add up for you.
The evolution of man is coming,
whether you like it or not.
You know, I almost feel bad for you.
'Cause it's not just metal
they ﬁlled your head with.
It's bullshit.
I was beginning to like you two,
you know that?
Oh, well.
What's the problem, boys? Does it hurt?
Must be hard being so... human.
-Did you see that?
-Yeah.
-We work together, we can hurt him.
-You're right.
-Time to work as a team.
-There's two of us and one of him.
-I'll take a punch and let you land one.
-I'll do the same.
I got your back, brother.
And I got yours.
Let's go unplug this sumbitch.
Here comes the kryptonite.
I got it.
You did it, Hat.
Never had a doubt.
Let's get it into safe hands.
You set me up as a traitor.
Turned my own sister against me.
Forced me to kill my own brother. You.
And here we are again. Come on!
Shaw, compared to the cause...
one life doesn't mean anything.
I don't know what
happened to you, Brixton.
But you made me kill you once.
I ain't doing it again.
Brother, you may believe in machines...
but we believe in people.
You may have all the technology
in the world.
We have heart.
No machine will ever beat that.
You boys, you're gonna get
one Samoan ass-whupping.
Shut Brixton down.
So that's how it is?
It's a hell of a business, boys.
Brixton never really lived up
to our expectations.
But you three,
you outperformed your analytics.
You don't remember me, do you, Hobbs?
You will.
It's gonna be a hell of a reunion.
You’re on our radar now.
And you're on ours.
Hey, thanks for being my sidekick
through this whole thing, brother.
You were great.
Hey, how 'bout I side-kick
that stupid look off your face?
Yeah? How 'bout you show me right now?
Okay, guys.
Let's go home.
-Yeah.
-All right.
Look, Batman had Robin.
Dr. Evil had Mini-Me. You're my Mini-Me.
Han Solo had Chewbacca.
Kermit had Miss Piggy.
That's a low blow. Don't say that.
Don't argue with me on my island.
You're my sidekick.
I'm so happy you're back.
Brought you that cake you wanted.
I wouldn't eat it.
Let's get out of here.
How long have you been working here?
Sam, this is your grandma.
I love you.
Good to have you home, uso.
It's good to be home, uso.
Hobbs. I hope you're sitting down,
buddy, because we got big problems.
God. I feel immediately better
just talking to you.
Is that weird?
Anyway, look.
The Snowﬂake virus, totally ﬁne.
On lockdown. In a secure asset vault.
But what we're dealing with
right now... is another virus.
The last one, well, that melted
your insides, but this one...
melts your outsides. Literally.
Your skin drips off. It's like removing
a silk kimono in a hurricane.
It's so gross. The point is
we need to get on this, like, now.
I need both of you.
What do you say, Becky?
Hey, Locke. This is Sam.
-Sam?
-You must wanna talk to my dad.
Oh, my God. Sam.
Wow! You sound exactly like your dad.
It's freaking me out right now.
It's like listening to a mirror.
-Can you put Hobbs on?
-I'm on.
I know, but I need
to speak to Hobbs, sweetie.
I'm on. What do you want?
I mean, seriously, record yourself
side by-- It's crazy.
Before you say another word,
tell me you took care of the Snowflake.
I got it. It's done. We're good, okay?
'Cause I care about people.
-I care about our family.
-You are not family.
I know. What we have is so much deeper.
Listen, hey, real talk...
Can you believe
that Game of Thrones ending?
I didn't see it.
You watched the shit out of it,
you dirty little liar.
What's the problem?
You said there was a problem.
My problem is that Jon Snow
had sex with his aunt, then killed her,
and nobody wants to talk about it.
That's what my problem is.
Jesus. Hang on a second here.
Are you okay?
Okay.
I'm definitely wounded now, so...
I'm gonna really need
that extraction, Big Papa.
I'll tell you what, sit tight.
I'm coming to get you.
Also, if you didn't mind, you could
bring a couple of pints of blood as well.
-Locke--
-Don't you wanna know my blood type?
What's your blood type?
It's B-positive.
Just like my life outlook.
-Imagine that.
-Locke.
-Locke?
-Jesus, I'm bleeding a lot.
God. I'm bleeding so, so much right now.
Oh, no. Actually, wait,
hold on a second. That's not my blood.
That's not my blood.
Oh, God, I thought that was me!
By the way,
I stabbed a guy with a brick.
How crazy is that?
Turns out, it's not that hard.
Let me guess.
You have a mission to save the world.
You just can't do it without me.
No, man.
I was just checking in on you.
Seeing how my good friend is doing.
And I...
I really wanted to hear this.
Police! Come out with your hands up!
We know you’re in there, Hugh Janus.
You bastard.
I warned you, you bald-headed sumbitch.
When you least expect it... expect it.
You have no idea what you've just started.
Well, I'm pretty sure it involves
rubber gloves and a body cavity search.
Not a chance.
-Police!
-Get on the ground, Hugh Janus!
This ain't gonna go down
how you boys expect.
I'll be seeing you, Hobbs.
Looking forward to it, Shaw.
Three-eighths ratchet.
Three-eighths driver.
Six-inch extension.
Are you sure?
Remember what your daddy
told you.
Be precise in life.
It can make all the difference.
Now, watch this.
- See how it's working now?
- Mm-hmm.
And you see what's happening?
It's turning the screw.
You're right.
Water heater's out again.
It's the price we pay
for peace and quiet.
Want to come and give us a hand?
Are you expecting someone?
Brian, remember
what we practiced.
Yo, yo!
We come in peace.
We come in peace!
It's me!
Roman?
Maybe you don't recognize me
'cause I've been tanning
all week, bro.
B, come out, son.
What you gonna do
with that thing, man?
What, you out here trying
to kill elephants or something?
We would've called first.
Except you actually need phones
in order to get phone calls.
You know that, right?
- Little b!
- Wow, you're so big.
- Hi. - Wow.
- Hi.
Now, I know you don't carpool.
So what's up?
Mayday! Mayday!
My plane is under attack
by a rogue agent!
We're being boarded. I've got
dangerous cargo on board.
I need you to assemble the team.
Still alive. I'll explain...
It's an SOS transmission
from Mr. Nobody's plane.
It came through with
a mess of encrypted data,
most of which
I'm still trying to crack.
- Did anybody else get this?
- Well, that's the thing.
He sent it only to us.
Why just us?
He caught Cipher.
But there was a midair attack,
and she was extracted.
It seems his plane crashed
somewhere here,
over the northwest region
of Montequinto.
If Mr. Nobody survived,
we need to find him.
But the whole area's sealed off.
Isolationist, run by military.
We're not on call anymore.
Wait, wait.
Dom, this is Cipher.
The woman who killed
the mother of your child.
Things change.
Listen, we're wheels up
at 8:00 A.M.,
if you change your mind.
Thank you.
Daddy, do you know where God is?
- Where is God?
- In your heart.
He's in your heart, too.
And you know something?
I'll always be in your heart.
Hey, little guy.
I have a gift for you.
Your father gave this to me.
And now I'm gonna
give it to you.
It's very special.
Take care of it.
Good night.
This isn't who we are.
Brian and Mia got out of the
game when they became parents.
We're not them.
Under attack by a rogue agent!
We're being boarded. I've got
dangerous cargo on board.
Assemble the team.
Still alive. I'll explain...
alive. I'll explain...
Coming up on the signal,
two miles.
It's deep in the militarized
zone of Montequinto.
- I hope everyone's ready.
- Ready?
Y'all want to make jokes
about me
not making practical decisions?
This is as prepared as it gets.
We all see you, man.
Nobody thinks you're
compensating for anything.
- I'll take point.
- Careful.
Careful's when you get hurt.
Right now, we have
a ten-minute window
between patrols.
Mr. Nobody's signal is close,
but we've got
to move quickly, guys.
We do not want to cross paths
with the military here.
- It's inside.
- Cover us.
The source of the SOS signal is
coming from inside this thing.
Somebody wanted in.
Plane must have gone down
before they could cut through.
Or it was sent down
on purpose to stop 'em.
Yeah, well, their mistake
was trying to cut into it.
But just give me a minute.
I can get in.
Dom.
There's not a soul in sight.
No sign of Mr. Nobody.
Got it.
What the hell is this?
Whatever it is, Mr. Nobody
wanted us to find it.
How's that work...
Go!
What?! You don't know who I am?!
You think I'm scared?!
Roman, where the hell are you?!
Who's compensating now, Tej?!
"Peligro minas."
What does that mean?
Tej, how fast we got to go
to clear 'em?
Please don't tell me
you're thinking
- what I think you're thinking.
- Why?
What does "peligro minas" mean?
- Tej, how fast?
- I don't know, man.
Somebody answer me!
What does "peligro minas" mean?
"Peligro minas" means
- "danger, land mines!"
- What?!
How fast, Tej?
Assuming a 50-foot blast radius
and a-a half a second trigger
delay, I'd say about 80.
I can't!
My speedometer
only goes up to 70.
- What do I do?!
- You put your foot to that floor,
and you pray!
Get to that palm plantation,
and then we're clear.
Whoa!
Roman, you good?
My ass is en fuego!
Tej! Wait! Land mine!
How in the hell
are you not dead?
Wait, okay, I think
I found us another way out.
Two miles to what looks like
a bridge across the border.
Good. The sooner we get
out of here, the better.
Letty, on the right.
The device.
Get in.
That was Jakob back there,
wasn't it?
Always check your mirrors,
bitches!
Oh, hell no.
Are we supposed to drive
across that?
Well, I said
it looked like a bridge.
Oh, my God!
The military's not giving up.
We got to get past the border.
Where's the bridge?
No. No, no.
Dom.
Well, that was new.
Look, we're in the clear.
But this thing is a mess.
The headlines out there?
Secret spy plane crashes
in a hostile country?
Followed by some kind of
covert ops firefight?
I'll get you where you need...
And then I'm gonna need
to back off.
I appreciate the favor.
I got to stop doing
so many favors.
What we doing, Ramsey?
Like, where are we going?
I-I was able to decrypt the data
that came through
with Mr. Nobody's SOS,
and I found GPS coordinates,
definitely included on purpose.
You knew about Jakob?
Question: Who is Jakob?
Jakob is...
Or was Dom's brother.
Oh, my-my bad.
I'm sorry. I'm just processing.
Brother?
You got a brother?
Who also happens to be
some kind of super spy
with his own private army,
who drives literally like
a bat out of hell,
who preplanned an aerial jump
and landed at the bottom
of an airplane?
Who does that?
Who does that? A Toretto.
Jakob.
I simply cannot believe that
magnet trick actually worked.
It looked so damn cool.
Look at this here.
I got this off the cockpit feed.
Oh, I love being rich.
It was sloppy. He almost had me.
- She say anything?
- Nope. Nada.
You know, I look at her
and I feel creeped out.
And sort of turned on
at the same time.
Is that weird?
Nice operation.
You snatched me off
Mr. Nobody's plane midair
without a scratch,
and you took him down.
Money well spent.
- Do you know who I am?
- I know who you are.
Do you?
East L.A. is a tough enough
place to grow up.
But it was your brother's shadow
that turned you into this.
Isn't it?
So your whole life, you pushed
yourself to be faster than Dom.
Smarter than Dom.
Stronger than Dom.
Tell me, do you hate him enough
that it keeps you up at night?
Still?
All these years later?
I should've just hired you
instead of coercing your
brother a couple of years back.
I don't work
for the competition.
That's cute.
You thinking
you're the competition.
Says the woman in the box.
Look familiar?
The other half's hidden
in one of the agency's
thousands of vaults.
I need you to find out
which one.
We secured the master drive here
from Mr. Nobody's plane.
The rest of the hardware
is a bit dated.
Pre-Internet.
To make sure you don't go
hack into anything
we don't want you to.
Say you get what you're after.
A weapon so dangerous
it shouldn't exist
for another half century.
What would you do with it?
Launch some global attack?
Sell it to the highest bidder?
Or maybe you see yourself
as a necessary shock
to the system.
I bet all you ever wanted
was a hug.
You read my psych eval.
Good for you.
I read your second-grade
report card.
That's what I do.
Your chin... it's distinctive.
I know the Torettos have
quite the mixed bloodlines,
but I never detected
a Nordic strain.
Finding the two halves of
project Aries is the easy part.
Add in your brother Dom
to the mix?
You don't have a chance.
Plans are in motion.
Qasar Khan.
What?
Genghis Khan's little brother.
Nobody's heard of him either.
Talk about off the grid.
I don't think they had grids
when this place was built.
If a ninja turtle pop out on me,
tell you right now, I'm out.
No way this place was
sanctioned by the agency.
This was definitely
Mr. Nobody's secret hideout.
What now, Dom?
Whoever Jakob has become...
and whatever he's up to...
it's on me.
And me alone.
Nah.
Whatever's on you, it's on us.
Let's get to work.
Y'all ever thought about how
many wild missions we been on?
How we somehow...
- Always survive?
- Yeah.
- So far, so good, I guess.
- It's just luck.
No, no, no, see,
y'all not listening.
Think about this.
We've now been
on insane missions
around the world,
doing what most would say is
damn near impossible.
And I ain't got one single scar
to show for it?
I mean, look at my jacket.
Those are bullet holes from
14 dudes trying to take my head
clean off its shoulders.
We've taken out
cars, trains, tanks.
I'm not gonna even
mention the submarine.
And yet we're still here.
Exactly.
Ramsey, what happens
when you test a theory
over and over again only
to come to the same result?
A hypothesis becomes fact.
But you're not actually
suggesting that...
I don't know,
but when the improbable happens
again and again,
that's more than luck.
Maybe we're not so normal.
That's what I'm saying.
We are not normal.
Okay, um...
Just to clarify,
are you two maybe suggesting
that we're what,
invincible?
- Maybe.
Or maybe...
You're just a dumb-ass.
Take your dumb-ass jacket
with you, man.
Pretty impressive driving
out there.
You miss the old life.
Do you?
Every day.
Guys.
We got a little company.
Think you know this person.
- It's so good to see you.
- I missed you.
Thank you.
Of course.
You should've told me.
She deserved to know.
Jakob's my brother, too.
I need to be here.
You get involved here, you put
everything you have at risk.
Your kids and the whole world
that you built.
We're all risking something.
Dom, listen to me.
My kids and yours are
in the safest hands possible.
With Brian.
Our world's grown, Dom.
I got this one.
The firewall on this old thing
is actually pretty good.
But, you know, port scan,
UDP, message peek,
pop to root shell, and...
say hello to project Aries.
What is it?
It's what we got from
Mr. Nobody's plane.
Or at least part of it.
Aries was designed
to override and assimilate
anything that runs on code.
Any computer anywhere.
If it operates on zeros
and ones, it's vulnerable.
If you take Aries
and upload it to a satellite,
it'll spread like a virus.
Then it'll be a matter of time
before someone can control
any weapon system...
Traditional, nuclear,
stuff we haven't even seen yet...
And just point it
wherever they want.
Jakob reboots the world order
within minutes.
Ares is the god of war, right?
If Jakob gets his hands on this,
he'll be the god
of damn near everything.
Because of how dangerous it was,
the Aries prototype
was recovered
and split into two halves
by Mr. Nobody.
Both of which are worthless
without the activation key.
Jakob now has one of the pieces.
He'll be going after
the other half next.
As for the key, it's...
It's vanished.
So we find it.
If we're gonna beat Jakob to it,
we're gonna have to split up.
Roman, Tej,
I know a couple of guys
operating out of Germany that
could get us anything we need.
I'm on it.
Wait, there's one more thing.
Mr. Nobody's transmission
had one name
connected to the key.
You guys are gonna want
to brace yourselves for this.
No way.
That's exactly what I said.
So you're saying
Han's death is connected
to all of this?
He has to have
something to do with it.
I'll look into it.
Tej, can you send me
- all the files you have on Han?
- Yeah.
I'll go with you.
Letty.
I got this the day Han died.
Mexico.
Check the postmark.
Whatever he was up to,
it ended here.
Tokyo.
What are you gonna do
about Jakob?
I'm gonna find him.
How?
An old friend.
...and beating the shortstop.
Line drive over the head of Gonzalez
on the field for a base hit.
Up next...
Place still looks the same.
Just like your dad left it.
I'm looking for Jakob.
Can't help you, man.
I know you took Jakob in
after my father died.
The worst thing
you can do to a Toretto
is take away their family.
That's what you did to Jakob.
You've got people who love you,
count on you, care for you.
He ain't got no one.
You get in his way,
this ain't gonna end
until one of you guys
are in the ground.
I know you did
the best you could, buddy.
But we both know he's about
to cause a lot of hurt.
I did my best
to take care of Jakob.
But I'm no Jack Toretto.
You've got to make peace
with the past if you...
if you want hope for the future.
He's in London.
That's all I know.
Dom.
I hope you find your peace.
The chance for peace died
that day on the track.
Arigato.
This place is a dead end.
Do you think Jakob could be
onto the Han connection?
If he has all the information
we do, probably.
I never told Dom...
I stayed in touch with him for
a while after what happened.
He was over at buddy's
for about a year, and then...
He was gone with
a message not to follow.
But after he disappeared,
I was so desperate to find him
that I would've...
Would've done anything.
I even broke into
a police archive,
but I didn't find anything.
You what?
You were like 16.
I did what I had to do.
Yeah.
How about you?
How are you doing?
It's a change of pace, huh?
Just as I was remembering...
who I was,
everything changed.
It slowed down.
There's peace for me
in the chaos.
It's like I... I need to face
the world head-on or something
to feel alive.
Seeing little Brian
hiding in a hole because
we had unexpected company...
that got to me.
We never used to hide.
Hey, Dom's my brother, but you
will always be my sister.
Funny how we all have secrets.
What?
You got to be kidding me.
What is it?
Remember what Han used to say
about Tokyo?
You mean how
in all the old westerns,
cowboys would make a run
for the border to get away
from the law,
how Tokyo was his...
Mexico.
No way.
She's ready to roll.
No. No!
No, Sean!
Tell me you are not modding
the quick disconnect valve
on the lox line.
Hey, man, chill out.
All right? It's all good.
- That tweak just saved us 0.4 seconds.
- "All good?"
This isn't Top Gun, Maverick.
You don't follow
the rules here, you die.
Hey, come on. That's a bit much.
When you know what too much
pressure in the lox line
can do, come talk to me.
Till then, stay in your lane.
Yo, you're lucky
to even be in my lane.
In case you forgot,
I'm the one that figured out
how to let us build
rocket engines and get paid.
This whole thing was my idea.
So who are you gonna trust
with your brilliant idea,
this glorified mechanic...
Or a rocket scientist?
Without me, you'd be
working at Jiffy Lube.
Guys, guys.
Look, it's all good.
Who cares about who did what?
Kind of hard for you
to do anything
when you pee your pants
every time you fly, Twinkie.
Did I hear that right?
You a runner
and you afraid of flying?
"Twinkie?"
So you must be
"Ding Dong" and "Snoball."
- Right?
- Yo, uh...
I don't go by that name anymore.
You went by that name ever?
Like, ever?
I... that's-that's-that's...
- Hey! We're up.
- Oh, good.
Hey, fellas.
Y'all seen ten-second cars?
Well, say hello
to the two-second car.
Is that a Pontiac Fiero
strapped to a rocket engine?
Impressive, I know.
No.
No, that's not impressive.
Eyes up! Here it comes!
Let the race begin!
Plane's taking off!
Go, go, go, go!
Yes!
We did it!
Uh... I'm confused.
Y'all didn't actually
beat the jet.
It didn't explode.
- Yeah, or melt.
- Yeah.
She's still in one piece.
You mean "pieces?"
Hey, Jiffy Lube, next time,
will you listen to me?
Look, we heard y'all could
get us some wheels.
Preferably the kind
that don't explode.
Is that possible?
Well, the Honda dealership's
about 3,000 miles that way.
Dominic Toretto sent us.
Who's Dominic Toretto?
Hmm.
Nice necklace, Queenie.
Diamonds and emeralds
never looked so good.
Dominic Toretto.
The word on the street is
you got locked up.
Yeah, well, in and out,
you know.
When are they gonna learn?
Some birds can't be caged.
Are you looking for
one of me sons?
Not tonight.
You do the driving,
I'll cut you in for 15%.
My thieving days are over.
Mine ain't.
You coming?
I'm looking for someone.
Would've shown up in town
a little while ago.
A lot of guys,
a lot of resources.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
word did go round
on a crew that just turned up,
led by an American.
Yeah, he bought some arms
off a local seller.
Rumor had it he was into
something big up in Edinburgh.
Local seller, huh?
She wouldn't happen to be
wearing a stolen necklace,
- would she?
- He paid well.
What was I supposed to do?
This geezer was about
your height, actually.
Similar features.
Oh, bloody hell, he's not your
cousin or something, is he?
He's my brother.
Get the hand brake for me,
would you, darling?
Glad I'm not the only one with
a family full of eccentrics.
He offered payment
for something else.
You.
You know,
nothing's more powerful
than the love of family.
But you turn that
into anger and resentment,
nothing's more dangerous.
Dom?
Don't get yourself killed, okay?
You're my favorite American.
This is your kind of party,
isn't it, Dom?
Beautiful women, best cars,
best everything.
You know, best security, too.
I'm Otto.
I'm your brother's partner.
Well, fi-financier.
But, you know, my dad,
he's a dictator,
so we're not talking
regular people rich here.
No, no, no, no, no.
Everything you see here, I own.
These girls, if you want
to meet one of them,
maybe two, maybe three,
just let me know.
They're on the payroll.
I offer a bomb-ass dental plan,
too. Huh?
Where is Jakob?
He's inside.
The brother
you're looking for...
He's from an old life.
- He's long gone.
- All I see is the same
scared little kid
that killed our father.
That's your mistake.
The spy game...
This is my world.
So here's my offer.
It's the same one you gave me.
You leave.
Now.
You drive away,
and you never come back.
Ever.
A deal?
I showed you mercy!
And I won't show it
to you again.
Toretto.
Since my dad is head of state,
it makes me a foreign dignitary
and this place an embassy.
Which means you just trespassed
into my country
and attempted murder.
So, naturally, I called in
a little favor
with all my good friends
from Interpol.
You keep digging around
in the past, Dom,
you're not gonna like
what you find.
And here I thought my dad
was a pain in the ass.
But your family is
a train wreck.
Well, now that your brother's
finally out of the game,
it's time we go to Edinburgh.
Get the second piece, maybe
do a little sightseeing, huh?
Any news on the key?
Don't worry about it.
Our men are closing in.
One week from now, there won't
be a superpower in the world
can take a piss
without our permission.
One week from now,
your dad will be asking you
for an allowance.
I'd like that.
Whew.
What's up?
- Well done, Leysa.
- Please.
If it wasn't for you, I'd still
be stealing gas in the D.R.
So, Queenie treating you right?
Like a princesa.
I'm her number-one pick,
you know.
Cara's little sister done good.
Good?
You saw my fine ass
in that white dress.
You see how I been rocking shit?
All this crew,
this is mine. Huh?
I been around the world.
Oh, I almost forgot.
You might need this.
Your boy Jakob biometrics
are encoded to this gun.
You'll have no trouble
tracking him now.
Hey, Letty.
Yeah.
Come look at this.
What the hell?
Han never mentioned
a girl, not ever.
Letty, Mia!
Down, now!
You okay?
Welcome to Saint Giles'
Cathedral of Edinburgh.
The High Kirk has a history
stretching back over 900 years.
Renowned for
its stained glass windows,
you can see
the intricate craftsmanship...
We're a go.
Ramsey, talk to me.
What do we got?
I pulled Jakob's biometric
signature off the gun,
and the algorithm I've run says
Jakob's team is
right on top of us.
Anywhere between
80 and 100 meters.
80 meters?
That's a lot around here.
This whole area
seems pretty packed in.
So, we don't know
where the secret vault facility
Jakob is looking to hit is,
now, do we?
Wouldn't be a secret if we did.
You know what?
I'm starting to think
your little English accent
makes you sound smarter
than you are.
Man, can I point out
that a good old-fashioned
tracking chip would've put us
within like
six feet of this dude?
But, nah, instead,
we out here with biometrics
and facial recognition imaging.
Feels like we looking
for where's Waldo
- in Harry Potter world.
- Yeah, uh,
strong argument there, Tej, but
tracking chips follow the chip.
Before we know it,
we'd be chasing some expensive
yet tacky jacket
to the dry cleaner's.
Biometrics, on the other hand,
are impossible to...
Wait.
Guys, okay, we have a problem.
Cameras are going down
all around us,
and my equipment is
freaking out.
What the hell, Jimmy?
Security alert.
Cameras are down.
Damn.
You see anything suspicious?
Uh, where do I start?
First of all, all of this
looks a little spooky.
I even seen
these two ladies walking
with George Washington wigs
on their head from the 1700s.
I feel like I'm in Transylvania
or some damn where.
Ramsey,
we're looking everywhere.
I just grew a new bunion.
This is hopeless.
What?
- You see that?
- See what?
The ears.
They got cauliflower ears.
They fight for a living.
- Don't worry about it.
- Roman.
Hey, man, I ordered
a pair of crocs
three weeks ago,
and I'm still waiting!
Where are my shoes, man?!
Man, we really need
to work on your planning.
Hey, Dom, you should
get down to the cathedral.
Dumbass here just attacked
some delivery dudes
'cause he didn't like
their ears.
Wait, wait, wait.
H-How much did you say
you paid for that again?
You know silver
ain't magnetic, right?
You know what?
Sh... just shut up.
Just shut up.
Ramsey, say we had
a big electromagnet
turned up right around here.
Wouldn't that disrupt
all electronic signals?
Including security systems.
That's it.
That's how Jakob's
getting into the vault.
Guys?
Okay, we've got police
coming from all sides.
- The area's locking down.
- He ain't using roads.
I got eyes on Jakob.
I see Otto.
I'm gonna tail him.
He's heading towards
a blue Jaguar.
Okay, follow him.
Me? I can't.
Why not?
Okay, this is a bad time
to tell you this,
but I don't drive.
Okay? I never got my license.
I don't know how to drive.
And, you know, no one
really drives in London.
Okay? And that is not
my contribution to this group.
It's you or no one.
Shit.
Guys, come on, man.
I feel like,
between the six of us,
we can work this out, right?
Okay. I've got...
Ramsey, shut it off!
Shut it off!
Go, go, go!
Okay. Uh...
Brake is on the left,
accelerator right.
Oh.
Shit.
Hey!
Oh! Sorry!
Whoa!
Oh, no!
Move!
Hey, that was not my fault!
Okay, that one was my fault.
See?
What'd I tell you?
Not even a scratch.
Otto, sending you
new pickup location.
I've got it.
I'm headed to you now.
Otto, where are you?
Jakob, I'm there.
I don't see anybody.
It's because you're
on the wrong street.
That's my car, pal!
Dom!
Go!
Damn it.
You're a natural.
Of course I am.
Okay, listen up!
I want 50 of the best men!
I want guns!
I want wheels, freaking
x-wing fighters... I don't care!
The millennium falcon,
Chewbacca if you can
get a hold of him.
Money's no object. Go.
Go!
What?
What's so funny?
I...
I was thinking,
if this was a movie,
this would be the moment
where the villain has
an unexpected setback,
overcompensates without
thinking it through
and gets crushed
by the good guys.
No offense, but you have
no idea what we're about to do.
And for the record,
we're the good guys.
Me? I'm Luke freaking Skywalker.
Are you sure about that?
I mean, I get
the daddy issues, but...
Look at what you've built.
Really? Luke?
You're right.
No, I'm more of a Han Solo.
No.
You're Yoda.
- Yoda?
- Mm-hmm.
No. The little green guy?
- Yeah.
- No.
Ah, shit, I'll take it.
Because he's
a powerful jedi, right?
No.
Yoda's a puppet.
With someone's hand up his ass.
So what now, Dom?
No one outruns their past.
And yours just caught up to you.
Man.
There is
literally zero industrial
or weapons-grade electromagnets
I can find
that are this powerful.
Look at the pull strength
level here.
- It's crazy.
- Yeah.
Wait, watch this.
Every time. I can't believe it.
What are you doing, bruh?
I'm hungry.
- Hey, guys.
- Oh, damn.
Surprise.
Nice clubhouse.
'Sup, man?
Nice to meet you.
So you got my postcard, huh?
I'm just still
trying to figure out...
How are you still alive?
Well, after Gisele died...
I didn't know what to do.
I was aimless.
- Lost.
- Absolutely.
But can you get
to the part where
the car exploded
and you're still alive?
- Like, I'm trying to...
- Roman, can you...
Can you just be quiet
for one minute?
We made plans.
We had dreams.
You know, it's funny,
Gisele led me there,
and I wasn't even
looking for it.
But it became home.
Then one day,
Mr. Nobody came calling.
And all I knew
was that I had to steal
some tech from the home
of a scientist couple.
But as usual...
Mr. Nobody didn't
tell me everything.
In fact, he left out
the most important part.
I was 11.
My parents would take me
to the movies on Saturdays
if I tried hard in school
during the week.
I was so excited to go
I forgot my raincoat,
so I went back in.
At first, I didn't see it.
By the time
I looked out the window...
Mom and dad were gone.
Turns out I wasn't the only one
looking for this thing.
Han saved me.
Wouldn't leave me behind.
He knew I'd always be a target,
so he taught me how to survive.
We became a family.
"Always be a target?"
Why?
'Cause she is the key.
Everybody's been looking
for a thing.
It was a person all along.
My parents didn't want
project Aries to fall
into the wrong hands,
so they locked it with their
own DNA, something we share.
And then, one day,
Mr. Nobody gave me the heads-up
that one of his best agents
went rogue.
So when Deckard Shaw
came calling,
we used it as cover--
But you got killed
in a car crash, Han.
Mr. Nobody had a way
of making things look real.
My death...
Became the best way
to stay alive.
- What's happening?
- It's some kind of
hidden subroutine
the system follows.
That's it, right there.
Yeah, nobody moves...
Everybody lives.
Jakob.
I'm sorry, Mia.
I was the rogue agent.
Me.
Dom, you ever think about
how Mr. Nobody found you?
Think he just dropped
out of the sky and chose you?
I ran missions with Mr. Nobody
out of this place for years.
I've been looking for that key
for a long time, Dom.
And you just handed her over.
I told you.
This is my world.
Got it.
Got a lot of guys here.
You trust 'em?
Trust this.
You know the only good thing
to come from dad dying?
If he hadn't, I'd have spent
my entire life in your shadow.
And now you're gonna spend the
rest of yours living in mine.
Only good thing
about dad dying...
Was he didn't have to watch
what you became.
You never deserved
the Toretto name.
You think you knew dad, huh?
What, 'cause you were his
favorite? You don't know shit!
Okay?
You want the truth?
Dad died 'cause he was trying
to throw that race.
We were in deep debt.
'Cause of how he felt about you,
he had to ask me for help.
How was I supposed to know
that car was gonna blow?
A good son would've said no.
And a real brother
would've come to me.
Come to you?
He made me promise
you would never find out.
And through all of it...
I kept that promise.
The girl comes with me.
Jakob!
I will stop you.
And that's my promise.
Hey!
Sue. Sue. Ah.
Come on. Come on.
Down!
Go! Go!
Come on!
This way!
I'm always here.
Tell him.
No...!
No!
Dom.
Tell me what you see, son.
See, cars like this
are immortal.
'70 chargers are
designed so well
that if you take care of 'em,
they'll run for 100 years.
Immortal?
Just like a family, Dom.
Build it right,
you take care of it...
it'll live beyond you.
Daddy.
Little b.
When are you coming home?
Com...
No. You know I'm good for it.
I promise I'll deliver.
I'm telling you,
I got intermittent miss.
- Last two laps.
- On it!
Get those plug wires!
Jakob! Now.
You're good!
No!
You came to me, Letty.
None of it is worth a thing
if I lose you.
Do you hear me?
Is this who we are?
Yeah.
From here, things move quickly.
Jakob has all the pieces
he needs.
Once he activates Aries,
all he needs to do is
send the signal global.
And then there's
no stopping him, ever.
He'll have to launch
some kind of pirate satellite,
something that'll act
as an amplifier,
infecting other satellites
in orbit one by one.
So we find him, stop him,
and then we get Elle back.
Our odds are zero here, Han.
Satellite equipment is
easy enough to track,
but we're not gonna
beat Jakob to a launch.
Which gives us
a two-target problem:
Jakob on the ground...
With his own private army.
- And the satellite.
- Which can't be hacked.
Not remotely.
We'd have to do it physically,
50 miles above ground while
the satellite is in orbit.
Orbit?
We need help.
Otherwise, we have no chance.
We do it ourselves.
It's where we've been
that got us this far.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Do y'all not understand?
Clearly, y'all don't.
Because if you did,
you'd be pissing your pants
like a normal person.
Orbit.
That's outer space.
That's another level.
What we gonna do?
Hijack a space shuttle?
Put rockets on our backs?
That's exactly
what we're gonna do.
What?
There goes my father's
diplomatic ties
with Eastern Europe.
This place is
going to be crawling
with every cop in the city.
Time to get the hell
out of here.
Keep her close.
It's activated.
As soon as the satellite
reaches orbit,
we start the uplink.
Ah, damn.
What?
You see that?
We can't have an air leak, man.
Are you really patching
yourself up with duct tape?
Yes.
I don't know
if you noticed or not,
but this whole operation is
band-aids and duct tape.
Man, this is insane.
We are headed to outer space.
You acting like
we on our way to home depot.
This is ridiculous, man.
I'm about to abort
this whole mission
and take my black ass home.
We're literally gonna be
in a perpetual freefall.
Freefall?
What does that even mean?
Roman, it means
numbers don't lie.
As long as we obey
the laws of physics,
then we'll be fine, okay?
It's just all math and science.
I knew I should've listened
to my teachers.
Four minutes to launch.
You fellas good to go?
Yeah, we just up here putting
a bunch of duct tape on shit.
You know, that's what Tej do.
Man, please hurry up so I can
stop hearing his damn mouth.
- Yes, we're good to go.
- We're not good.
This is the same car
that we watched
do a test run and explode.
- This is not smart, Tej.
- Don't worry, man.
With my ceramic polymer coating,
you're gonna be just fine.
You're 100% fireproof.
Exactly.
All eight thrusters
fully functional.
Hey, please don't tell me
you're still running
launch simulations.
Virgin galactic launched
at 36,000 feet.
The space shuttle tests
around 50,000 feet.
Our last test run
with this load means
we'll have to go higher...
Way higher!
If we don't get them
high enough,
these guys are gonna be
pancakes at IHOP
before the coffee
even gets to the table.
Hey!
We can still hear you!
Don't worry, guys. We got this.
We do got this, right?
I've run thermal imaging.
Elle's in the armory truck.
And I've got a lock
on the Aries signal.
It's coming from
the beast up ahead.
We need to get in there
to deactivate it
by the time Roman and Tej
are in position.
Ramsey, power us up.
Satellite is in low orbit.
Begin.
All right,
we're passing 50,000 feet!
Time to get ready, boys.
What we supposed to be doing
with these old-ass suits
that ain't been used
since world war I?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Astronauts "r" us was closed
for shopping today.
Listen, these suits are
just like space suits.
They both account
for pressure differential.
Only thing is we may
blow up like balloons
just a little bit.
- That's the only difference.
- What?
We just hit the launch altitude.
- You guys ready for a five count?
- No, man!
I'm barely ready to go scuba
diving in this old-ass thing.
Don't listen to him. We ready!
- "We?"
- Yes, I said "we!"
I thought you was invincible.
Let's see how invincible
your black ass is after this.
- Punch it!
- No! Tej!
Oh, my God! I don't want to die!
Ignition!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
We're in outer space!
Told you numbers don't lie.
This is crazy, bro!
Man, how much candy did you eat?
Well, I-I... I eat candy
when I get nervous.
I thought you said
you took care of this.
Yeah. Hey.
You take them back to the
freaking junkyard right now!
All right, Han, Mia, you're up!
Now.
Letty.
Han!
Not all of us.
Now, the satellite we looking
for should be somewhere...
There.
Right there. You see it?
Got it.
Tell me you know
how to work the thrusters.
Tej, numbers is
what you do, right?
Driving is what I do.
Two dudes from the ghetto...
Outer space.
You know ain't nobody
gonna believe us, right?
You're right.
Something's wrong with
the satellite array.
It's, uh, interfering
with the uplink.
I'll handle it.
Han?
Grab the wheel.
Something's up.
I think I can link
into their feed.
- Something you want to tell me, Otto?
- My bad.
Satellite uplink is
actually going splendid.
Oh, and by the way,
I have a new business partner.
Maybe you know her.
Guess who's
out of the box, Jakob.
But I did try to warn you.
You were never my competition.
- Otto, there's something you should know.
- Yeah, go on.
- Lay it on me, dude.
- You're a spoiled rich prick,
- and I'm gonna kill you.
- Oh, man, I am so sorry.
No one told you, huh?
Spoiled rich pricks
run the world.
Come on. Come on!
Go.
- What's happening?
- Uh, well,
we appear to have lost
our escort and Jakob.
And, well, Dom is making things
a little bit difficult here,
but it's fine.
Really, it's peachy.
Don't worry, don't worry.
I'll finish this myself.
All right, let's see
what that beast is made of.
You ready, Elle?
Crank it.
If we can't break through,
we stop it.
Guys, that thing is
not slowing down
and the download's almost done.
Dom, we don't get
out of here now, we're dead.
Letty, drop back and line up
with the front tires.
What?
If we can't slow it
and we can't punch through,
we flip it
and we hit the underside.
Goddamn it!
Why do I have to say this?
Flatten these clowns!
- Letty, the wires.
- You read my mind.
Han, get in front of me.
Dom, I can't get to you.
But I can.
All right,
the satellite is in range.
Let's power up these magnets
and fry it.
All right, take our time.
Okay. All right.
- Tej!
- Hold on. Come on, baby.
Power up. Power up.
Shit.
- Shit, shit, shit.
- What?
Talk to me. What's going on?
The pressure of the launch...
It must have jammed the cables
to the power source.
Damn it, how did I
not think of that?
Guys, where are you?
The upload is almost complete.
Why don't you just kill it?
Let's smash it.
Let's run it over, right?
No. If we crash into that
satellite, we'll probably die.
And even if we don't,
the fuel that it would take
to smash it...
We'd be stuck out here forever.
You got to have faith, bro.
Faith? Faith is not numbers.
You know what, Tej?
You're probably right.
We're not invincible.
We probably just been lucky
this whole time.
This might be it.
But you know what?
If we're gonna go out...
let's go out
on top of the world.
Guys, what's happening up there?
We've got seconds left.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
We did it.
We did it!
Let's go.
Yes!
Shit.
Not bad, man.
Not bad at all.
Hold on!
Dom!
Yes!
Got to be kidding me.
Shit!
Think these belong to you.
There's gonna be a lot of
people coming after you, Jake.
Yeah.
This is the world I chose, Dom.
You know, dad wasn't perfect.
And he loved us all the same.
Someone once gave me
a ten-second car...
As a second chance.
I owe you that, little brother.
I lost you once.
Don't let that
happen again, okay?
We come in peace!
Hey!
This was the last place
I saw your grandfather.
This is where he raced.
Did you race here, too, daddy?
No.
But I'll tell you something.
Everything I needed
to know about life,
I learned on this track.
You did?
I did.
- Fellas.
- Hey.
What?
No way.
What's going on?
I couldn't believe it
when I heard you were alive.
It's a long story.
But for now, let's just
enjoy the moment, huh?
Guys, this is Elle.
Hey, Elle. I'm Sean.
Just call me "T."
- I'm Earl.
- Nice to meet you.
Mia.
Hi. Nice to finally meet you.
- Hey, guys.
- Mm. - Hey.
How much longer on this food?
Like, I'm-I'm...
I'm ready to eat now.
I've been eating space food
for weeks.
Oh. So tootsie rolls
are space food?
'Cause that's all you ate.
It was fat free, bruh.
Snickers and Twix fat free, too?
- My forehead hungry.
- Yeah, okay.
- I'll see you later.
- Y-Your forehead is overweight.
Oh!
You drive just like your dad.
- I do?
- Mm-hmm.
Do you know, this is...
This is where I met your mom
for the first time.
Right there.
She's watching over you
from heaven.
- She is?
- Mm-hmm.
I think daddy has
a question for you.
You ready to say grace, kid?
But I don't know what to say.
Oh, it's easy.
Just say whatever's
in your heart.
You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- Come on.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Little Brian's ready
to say grace with us.
- Uh-huh.
- Nice.
Now, hold on.
There's still an empty chair.
He's on the way.
Thank you.
Please.
I tell you where the drive is,
the plans we stole.
I tell you where it is.
You mean this drive?
These plans?
But you already got it.
Yes, mate.
How else do you think
I stay in this good of shape?
Don't go anywhere.